Hi, I just saved password to air table to our last
class. So I want to show you a few things in the air table
account. So this is the thing that he used for creating forms and
yeah, so we're interested in these other ways, DTC org and in this,
uh, so this is where all the things that you create,
this is where they end up in. And here,
I wanted to show you how to change an event title that you submitted
through the form. So here I'll click on
expand and here the event type you submitted here,
um, well, it should be different, right?
Or that's why I go to Devon drive to get the correct title.
The one that you ablated
Come on.
Yeah. So this one is productionizing the feature store for fraud detection.
So copy the Euro
And yeah, you can get the title and
click here. So this is how you update a form that you're already submitted
through air table. And I think they don't do,
I can just close it. Yeah. He told them why the case has the
updated version. Let me check a FedEx.
So it's uh, 6 0 7 0 7.
Yeah, this is the correct one. Um,
and then once I processed this, the status will change from,
uh, uh, empty to Dan and here in grid view,
you see all the past events that I already processed.
And by the way, you accidentally last time you edit two records
for the same event, please be careful.
And now you can actually log into air table and see in check or
what you actually submitted to use inform was actually better.
But yeah, this is in case you accidentally put something incorrectly through the forum.
Now you can log in to this account and,
uh, yeah, she had the data.