Okay. Yeah. So in this video I want to show you who from this
website, uh, we should put to the crm which
sponsors are, oops, relevant.
Um, so this one. Okay,
this one. Let's say mid lower relevance.
This one, lower relevance.
This one also, let's say lower relevance.
Um, I don't know what this company is.
Um, yeah, let's say also lower relevance.
This one, Lower relevance. So this one,
let's not add until medium.
Relevance. Hewlett Bakar.
Let's say medium. Relevance to,
um, I don't know what
it is. Um, looks somewhat relevant.
So let's put medium. Relevance. Invest.
Yeah, let's keep that. Meta platforms.
Let's say medium. Relevance. Who have a medium?
HT O. Medium. So general or we can skip them.
Ians, Let's skip them. Um,
training data platform. Okay.
Let's say lower relevance. Telecom Cloud.
Let's say lower relevance two.
Uh, um,
I don't know this one. Let's say medium.
Relevance.
I don't know. Let's keep this one. So this one is medium relevance.
This one is low relevance.
This one No AI plugin.
Read email. So let's keep them. Um,
okay. Well say medium. Relevance.
Well, yeah,
let's skip that one. Also.
Skip.
Skip. That's medium.
Relevance?
Mm. I don't know.
What is that? Let's skip this.
Uh, what relevance? Skip.
Low relevance.
So skip. Um,
low relevance.
Uh, skip, skip,
skip, skip, skip,
skip.
And skip, skip, skip,
skip, skip,
skip this one too.
Skip and I,
Yeah. Maybe lower elements.
I don't know. Maybe medium. Relevance or? Now let's go with lower elements.
So medium relevance.
Um, no lower elements.
Let's say how many sponsors they have.
Must be earning a lot of money with this.
Uh, lower relevance? Uh,
I don't know. Skip this one.
Um, skip, skip,
skip. Um,
lower ones. Uh,
let's say also lower ones. Well,
I think the rest are, I think from some other,
Let's also at Watson. Watson we already,
I think we already have ibm. So IBM Watson and ibm.
I think the same, but these are past,
um, well past partners.
So let's not add the rest. Just those.
Okay. Yeah, I think that's, um, all who we need to add to the
relevant CM to the content sponsor crm.