Hi, so we have this event on next Monday.
What we also do for course events is to add them to the course
calendar. So we have a bunch of course calendars,
I think I added you to all of them. So here we have Data
Engineering Zoom Camp, LLM Zoom Camp,
Machine Learning Zoom Camp, ML Ops Zoom Camp.
So these are calendars for the respective courses.
And what I want to do now is to add this thing to the
course calendar. So this is a reminder for course participants.
To those who are subscribed to the events,
so they want to also get notified. And by the way,
when we, when you create a process document, like all the context information I
give at the beginning, do not forget to put this in the process document.
This is very important. Later, it will help us to actually understand why
a certain process document exists, what kind of thing it's used for.
Anyways, so I wanted to show you how to,
how we create events for course calendars.
So this one, I think it's, It's called MLZoomCamp Pre-Course
Q&A, right? Then the link,
the location link, as always,
is our YouTube.
We don't have any guests. And then when it comes to the calendar,
you select Machine Learning Zoom Camp,
because this is for Machine Learning Zoom Camp.
If it's for another course,
then we select the course, right? So right now it's for Machine Learning Zoom
Camp, so we make.
We select this calendar. Okay, so I
think that's it. We can also add descriptions.
So in this case, we actually have a Luma event.
We can also add that.
Where is it? I don't remember actually what we usually
write there, but the important thing is like at least we have a
rebuttal. Mind that for people who are subscribed to the calendar,
they see this. And also the actual start over
here. I've already created them.
I also amp course launch.
So I'll add it and
then of course I also need to add this.
Okay, so this is how we add course how
we add events to course calendars.