So I wanted to show how to add images to articles on our
blog, in our blog, on our website.
So here's an article by Evalerio and we want to add
this image to the article.
So I want to show you how to do that. First,
for that, we will go to the website for
repository, GitHub repository for our website,
which is Datatalks.
So this is the whole URL.
And here we have posts.
So these are all the posts,
and this is the article that we have here, and this is the article
that we have here, and this is the article that we have here. And
this is where we want to add the image. Data engineering zoom cam. I
will now click on edit. We will edit this file right now.
And this is how the article looks like.
And this is how we add stuff.
Wait, this is how we add images.
So this is how images look like. And you see the path to
the images. So all the images are in the images folder in the posts
folder. Then there is a folder for the,
article. And then this is the name of the image.
So this is the file we want to upload.
So we will need to go to that directory.
So this thing here is the,
the same as the name of this file. So we want to go there.
We want to upload this image there. So first of all,
I will rename it. I'll call it course over here.
And I will go now to images. Posts.
Then this is dating genie zoom cam.
And they want to upload the image. So I'll just click on add
file, upload file. And yeah,
I think I can just drag it here, drag and roll.
Or you can select the like choose the files here.
And this is the name. This is the name of the file.
I don't know if I can rename it,
but it doesn't matter at all. So I just commit the file.
Go back two times.
I pressed back two times. We will have this new file.
Force Overview to back. Right. So this is the file.
Now I will click. First,
I will take this thing. So this is how Image Stack looks like.
And this is where we will put it.
So we'll put it, let's see here. But we can change the position later.
And from there, I need to know the file name.
Of course, over here, JPEG is the file name because the rest stays the
same, right? What if,
in an article, there is no image?
There still will be a folder, it generates automatically because
we will always have this cover, so a folder will always be there
with the cover, but we might not have this figure,
image, whatever. I think so,
you will need to copy it. So we will make sure I was included
in the loom video,
so then when we if there is nothing to copy paste from,
then we'll copy paste from the process document.
It's a course over here, and then we can call this,
this p here is kind of optional but since others have it,
let's include it here, so it's definitely in,
in, in this heating. So,
I'll, you know, copy it we'll post it in in
the comments, but the important part here is the caption,
the title under the figure.
The image and I'll just take a course over here.
I think we don't see here.
And I just click commit changes.
So in total we'll make eight two commits. The first commit was uploading the
image and then the second one was changing.
And if there are multiple images, of course, like when we upload files,
we can upload multiple files. So I will not this
is just an example.
So I'll do this thing here,
right? And then,
yeah, okay. It's just a large file.
But, yeah, let's, say I can do something like that.
Let's upload multiple files. I don't commit that,
but this is how we can upload multiple images.
And then, in the second commit, we edit the file.
So right now I think if we refresh multiple times,
yeah, it takes a file to build so we can follow the
progress. Right now,
if we go to actions, we see that it's queued.
So once it has this check mark,
then the site is updated. It's being deployed right now,
so now when this is over,
then we should have a new updated version of the website.
Okay, it's done. Now use Ctrl F5 to
make sure we refresh, like,
also we don't use the cached version. And now we see the image.
Okay, so this is how you add images.
And let's say if you want to change the image,
so this image, let's say there is a mistake, and we want to update
the image, so then you can change the image, so you can change the
image. You do
it over again, so what you
can
do is, yeah, I think
I lost it, so in images, we can
Bye.
delete images, so here, hmm, how do I actually do this? There's an option,
I think, to delete it. I don't remember how to do this, from the
web interface, but yeah,
so what we can do is just upload a course overview v2,
and then yeah,
there should be a way to, to delete it,
I don't remember, you know,
I guess we should google. Anyways,
when we need it we'll find a way,
but right now this is how, you would replace it,
so you would just upload a new file,
of course, over uv2, and then you would go to the post and update
the path to the image. Yeah,
so please make process documents for uploading a new image.
And also for replacing existing images.
And please share it with Valeria, the, I mean the the result of the
process documents.