We just had an event. So you see B testing with,
um, so yeah, you see, it's still not edited.
Um, but, um, I already reached out to Jaco saying
that, um, um, yeah,
send me any links you want to include in the description.
So he sent me this, so this is a job if the company
where he works. So now I want to include this video
and then at the links.
So first I will include his, uh,
LinkedIn co-ops and
then, uh, product analyst,
uh, let me just overall
in kids. So this is what he sent me.
And then he's thinking is this one?
Okay. And that's all. And actually,
so after the team, because by default, it is not edit to any playlist.
So after this team, I add this to livestream because it was a steam
and then it's either webinars or podcast,
depending on the type of events. So this particular one was podcast.
So it here done.
And now I just click, see, I will also need to update thumbnail,
but there is already a video about that.
So maybe I'll do a separate one.
Um, no,
I think this is exactly, uh,
yeah, I'll see. I don't know if I actually made a video about that
or not. I'll check on pick thought. Well, okay.
That's all.