Um, so yeah, because mines the be paid for the invoice.
I wanted to show you how we include the invoices here.
So, um, I will open
Our,
Um, paperwork. We have this invoices income.
And so let me actually open
is where its, so we opened this payment document,
uh yeah, this document, right? Let,
actually start from maybe I did it too fast.
So yeah, we, yeah,
I think it might click on this thing on the invoice.
I will go directly to invoice, right? So this is the invoice.
I can just click to you PDF and this is what actually we send
to Costa. Alternatively, we can just,
uh, uh, alternatively,
we can just, uh, so this is the same invoice,
right? So we can just get this one.
Uh, this is the invoice we sent and we put it here and
then the pattern is plus here then.
Uh, so this is the date.
So it should be 20 22, 9 90.
And then today is, uh,
nine. So this is the day when,
um, we receive the payment. So today and uh,
yeah, so this part is not really needed. So that part was for them
to understand, uh, what they are paying for for us is just mine.
So the, the, the company,
so this is, and now we need to also add this to the,
um, to this bookkeeping.
So here, let me add,
so this is today, then this line would be when
we created the invoice date on this one.
So
Use a different format.
So this is the issue date. This is the date when it was paid,
then mine's D
okay. And then how we take this hands workshop
and then it's plus 4,000.
Okay.
So this is how we add the payments when we get paid.
So yeah, it's very important. Declare, declare this still in the,
in this bookkeeping. Yeah.
How we declare please received
the payment
install and uh, up with you and see if you will receive
any notifications. Oh,
but yeah. So this is how we, uh,
add this, uh, income for bookkeeping.