Oh, hi. So I wanted to change this,
um, sponsorship CRM a little bit.
So instead of sponsored content, I'll name it just content because
sometimes the content is, uh, not sponsored,
but still I want to reach out to the company who organizes,
uh, something and, um,
offer them sponsorships. So a good example is this Snowflake
built, right?
So Snowflake is, uh,
let me remove this part. Um,
so Snowflake is, um, a company we already have them in,
um, Oops,
here, and they organize the conference.
So I want to add the conference here so we can offer
them sponsorship, uh,
promotion of this conference. So I'll do,
uh, the data Snowflake Bill 22?
No,
Like
Build 22. What's the,
the data cloud of Summit.
The data
Cloud
Of Summit, right? So content type is,
um, conference.
So it's Event. Event,
right? Source.
Uh, it's kind of newsletter,
but, uh, yeah, here since for the source,
let's only keep the source that is,
uh, like, you know, paid source.
And so here it's their own newsletter.
So here I'll just, uh, maybe have an option,
something like, uh, organic.
Yeah, so it means it's, uh, their own stuff.
Relevance is, uh, let's say Medium and companies Northlake.
We already have them. It's Snowflake and Comment is,
uh, so when is it?
It's
November.
Just
Then. Uh, we don't have anyone from Snowflake yet,
so we probably should. Uh, cause I see that they are sponsoring
quite many things. So some of these,
uh, content is organics because it's their own.
Some of the content is, uh, like they're actually sponsoring.
So it would be a good idea to get in touch with somebody from
Snowflake and offer them some,
um, like some help with promoting content.
Okay. So yeah, the way I think I wanted to show you here is
that, uh, previously I intended to use this thing only as a,
You know, a way to capture all sponsored content,
but sometimes there is also organic content that could also be relevant because this
is something we want to help them promote. Right.
Okay. And, um, I don't think you need to,
uh, like maybe in the process doc,
when you say how exactly they need to select,
um, content, type, and source,
you can mention that, uh, like organic should be if it's,
you know, their own, um,
their own content. And an example of that would be a newsletter,
their own newsletter that they use for sponsoring this stuff.
Or for, not, sorry, sponsoring but promoting this stuff.
Okay.