So, I just want to show you how to add links to thriller.
So before the item told the links,
but now I want to show you how to actually do this again.
You don't need to turn this into a protest document.
You just need to do this as a one off.
I think so. Let's see.
We want to do is agree on day two and you have a link
here, this one.
So now let's say we want to edit here.
And for that, I use this index for, let me make it larger.
So first I use, um,
yeah, so first I use this brackets and then saying,
break it, say right link. And then I,
then I use parenthesis and then put the actual link.
So this syntax we Centerlink,
right? So now we'll you click on this link,
a topless link.
And I actually can now put this in,
in other player or Prentice, and then I kind of put the apprentice
in the link and yeah.
So for example, now change the status to confirm in this schedule a spreadsheet.
I just know we have this schedule spreadsheet.
I get a, I get the link around this
spreadsheet here, and then now I need to link
the link. Yes, it's not available.
You will need to add this. I'll just do the
link. And then Victor here, and
you will do this. And then, um,
can you please this link to all the things here,
um, and this way we can just, uh,
you know, when we do a template,
we just click on this thing and we have the process document
if it's needed and then all the,
all the forms. So for example, this one,
you put the air table form.
I think this is quite useful to have
it immediately on the checklist here.
And now when you need to introduce you just click on this link and
you fill it in and yeah.
And then you mark it. Okay.
So please do it for the rest of the templates.