I want to show you how heavy child to author.
So folks, um, so here at this,
uh, Dr. Moniker, I think he is a book author.
I'm not sure. So write about this in the introduction.
Yeah. So let's say that I saw your somewhere.
So I described where I see you. I saw him and then I say,
uh, the Tehran Datadog's cop community,
uh, what the community is about. And then I say that we have a
book of the week event. We invite book authors to ask questions about the
book. Then I sent the link that you probably saw.
This is the link with more information about a book of the week.
Um, yeah. So,
which is kind of basically, um,
what's happening there. And I asked if he will
be interested in taking part and,
uh, after that, uh, well, if he say yes,
then what I would next is I would go here.
It's just not the right thing. Uh,
um, yeah. To this schedule yeah.
To this thing. So would go here and then I would pick a no,
because lot here. And then I would ask him,
Hey, what do you think about this date? Does it work for you or
not? And if it works for him,
then we proceed with the rest of the browser.
So this is basically how, uh,
how it starts or the process of reaching out to authors,
um, start. Okay.
Um, that solo,
I wanted to show you in this video,