Hello. So what I did, I added this line here in the template.
Are there any books or other resources that you can recommend to the listeners?
So, uh, can you please, uh, go,
um, take this and put it to all the podcast documents
that we have in the pipeline? So,
for example, let's take this one. I think she actually canceled,
right? Did she? So maybe I'll come.
So what, so we, we don't,
uh, it here. So maybe also create a process
document or included in one of the protest documents,
uh, that if I guest cancels,
then we move it here. Okay.
So for Yulia, I think Yulia also canceled,
right? Did she But according to the date,
Yeah, she did. Um,
yeah, please go through all these documents and then if somebody canceled we just,
um, move it from there.
And then, uh, so for sad, I think we can just edit
it here and then you can do the same thing for all the other,
um, podcast documents. And yeah,
maybe in the future we will come up with a bunch of,
um, is the template with a bunch of common questions
for all the podcasts. And I will include them here and I will ask
you to, um, update on the existing ones,
um, with this. Okay.
Maybe to make it a bit easier, um,
I think for this year we already booked almost all the podcasts.
Uh, update the name. Okay.
Yeah, that's it. Uh, that's all I wanted to show.