Event, this one book of the week event is coming soon.
So this one, this one.
So it's actually tomorrow. So what they want to do now is I want
to ask the author to
share this thing with, um, their audience.
So like it doesn't have to be through LinkedIn.
Um, they also have Peter,
so I will write to him.
I can
and you can see here for verse this
one.
Can I please share that in a more tomorrow?
Yeah. So, because statement starts tomorrow,
maybe it's actually better to do tomorrow or today.
It doesn't say yeah,
actually, because it's the day Sunday, maybe,
Uh, it was today, some days less activity.
So let me work. Can you please share the link to this page with
your folders and connections? The one who went through this one?
Okay. Yeah. We need to work on this template.
Uh, no, maybe
it's a good idea to include some examples. I don't have these examples right
now, but yeah, I can work on the text.
What they did here is we need to ask the speaker and the book
author in this case to tell their network,
uh, LinkedIn,
um, and they daily also folders yet.
It also implies that they might share this one.
Uh, so I asked them to share
this link. It's just not good
that they noticed this, that it should be this one.
So,
Yeah.
Yeah. So this is how I do this. I asked to do them to
spread the awareness of office spent by.