I am in process with arranging a book of the week,
a event with one of the authors.
So let me take this one.
So there are actually many of them that they have in parallel.
I will ask you to take care of the next,
but for this one. So what I'll do. Yeah,
so she is, uh,
she's, uh, uh,
our contact from packed, packed as a publisher.
Um, they publish books. Um,
so she introduces me.
She puts me in contact with Roy. Who's an author of this hands on
data processing and Python, and Roy already agreed
that, uh, he is quite interested,
um, to do this. So we want now to actually agree
or to, to, to help them.
So for that, I will not reply to all of them.
I will also add you here.
Um,
And alright. Hi Roy. And she
far, so I'll finish email later because I don't want now to spend
time over this, but what I will do is I will ask will,
uh, so first of all, I will send them a link with more information.
So there, I have a link which is a book of the
week. Hmm. I think it's really,
uh, this one, DTC minus B O T w.
So this is a link with more information about this event,
book of the week later d**** club. So I am now going to send
this link to the author.
Nice to meet you serious,
more or walk off there
week I went and then I sent this link.
Um, so it has all the information about the event and I want
to propose the author a date.
So the next date is, um,
yeah, so now we do this basically. So the next date,
um, I am going to propose to the book author is,
uh, this one
We'll ask we'll, uh, the,
uh, week,
Um,
From problem to work
for you.