For the quarter for a career. So here I asked the date.
So if this week from 28th of February to March will work for you,
what else would do is they go to this document that it with the
schedule and tight tentatively at the author there.
So the offer is, um,
uh,  Roy  here.
Oops. In here.
And then also I need the name of the book,
so it's easier. Okay.
So let's also have a bit of order also at
pact and then it's,
uh, let's call it a proposal date.
So this is the status. Um,
so we have, what would the Davis records? So nobody else will be,
I will take it and yeah.
Now I will send this email that will slightly change it.
So I will also introduce you and I will ask Shifa to contact you
my food, then next events now the weekends.
So you will be entitled to here that you will be helping with,
uh, organization of them. So,
yeah.