Um, hello. I wanted to show you,
I don't know how to do it from the web,
but in mobile version of telegram,
you can forward multiple messages.
So let's say, um, so I sent you a bunch of things,
right? So then I just,
I think you just need to hold it. You see, I hold and then
I can select so I can select multiple things.
Um, well,
up to this point, right? So I selected multiple messages
that I sent, and then you can just click forward and
then two to do two, these two,
right. And then I click send and you see that's all
the messages now to do, do think.
Oh Yeah.
Okay. I just wanted to check that and this
lower, So,
So corporately. Yeah, here it has all this things.
Oh no. So probably something useful.
You can balk a forward and bunch of events,
a bunch of messages from me to the boat,
and then we'll be edit. I don't know how
to do this from a bio. Probably. It's also possible.
Maybe you can figure that out.