Yeah. So I, uh, created,
uh, so I decided to use the same thing cause we use for book
of the week and go away for book of the week.
So I just put this data match book here and here,
the handle and people started already
writing. So when I click on messages,
so it actually doesn't show up like a thing here.
Like you need to click on messages and then there is message requests.
So I click on this messaging question and this is one of the,
with the windows we need actually to check if this person is in need
the winner. So,
um, yeah, so this is I the,
for EEG. So he wrote saying that this is my email,
click accept, copy the email,
put it to this thing
and then ride, I
thank you for taking part C
or that publishers,
um, publisher asks you yeah,
last year alone, but the publisher.
Yeah, something like this. So now we need to do the same for
like others and yeah,
it's just called you to do this. So critical message.
There will be a message request if they haven't contacted us yet,
if they already contacted us previously, there will be a message here.
And yeah, you just put everything to this.
Someone will have my call,
the emails or when we have like, at least some of them.
So let's wait to you. I don't know, Tuesday.
And then on Tuesday we'll send it to, to cut on.
Yep. That's it.