Hmm. I want to show you how to use Email
in LinkedIn. InMail is a
different way of reaching out through LinkedIn,
LinkedIn. So for example, let's Say
Katrina, for example, I wanted to,
oh yeah. So I just got Catherine here.
So we still a, you sent a connection request from my account
as well. What she still have to apply it. So in this case say,
you see there's this message button,
right? So it's because I have a premium account on LinkedIn.
I can actually write to people I am not connected with.
So for some people, because it's funky five Peer
month, um, because of that,
we need to be careful when using them. So we'll kind of just use
it for everyone, but for Catherine,
maybe she just doesn't visit LinkedIn very often,
but this thing will go straight to your email.
So You can just write
here using this email, Um,
April.
So this can be the topic And we
open the template. You have a template for
When it's, Um,
Is this,
The name is very misleading. Please change it to something like,
first of all, there are two templates change that.
Um,
Okay.
So yes,
here actually we can be quite there most,
maybe we can,
Uh, say,
And then I will copy these because there is quite some information already,
Maybe,
Uh, community it's like,
All right. So we need to mention that as well.
Uh huh.
Oh,
Um,
Um, here, I'll also say that
Um, so this will be optional if Say,
And this will be well
Community, if your own name recommended reaching out to you,
would it be interested in taking barks?
Here's wonderful. Um,
So
True.
Okay.
Um,
Let's see.  would you be interested
in
Taking
My information? I was wondering if you get the, I
think it's kind of repetitive CJ recommended to you or would they be
Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. And now I just click send,
So, yep. This is how you use emails.
And remember I have only limited number of emails,
so I don't use it on everyone.
I'll probably just send to you.  using emails.