Alright. So I will show you how to create invoices in email,
um, and go to documents,
documents. And I think you can actually beginning,
so you can just click on this new document.
I think you don't need to go to you.
Don't need to go to documents. So just pick one
and then you create invoice, uh,
here in the invoice. So
we need to send them an invoice to our new sponsor called arise.
We don't get them yet, so we need to add a new contact.
So they are from, so this is actually the contract with them.
So they are from the United States. That's
the name you states
of America. Business name is arise.
AI that's the main company.
So, uh, they don't have the number they do have address.
So there is is, so this is this name,
I think,
um, I don't know.
I guess this postcode is school,
the most cold, and this is the
CT,
So we don't need, we don't change anything else.
And we see that the others make sense.
It's similar to do what do we come here?
So, yeah,
that seems to make sense. So that's
the other S and now the things we'll want to send to them is
yeah, so they are our sponsors and contracts.
We need to send them, we need to send them
voices four times. So let me check.
Um,
There's this?
Yeah, so it's 16.
Awesome invoice needs to be paid within 30 days.
So, and then, because it's important statements I will,
so are silver sponsors, the silver sponsorship is
first opened and I will.
Whoops. So for me
to put here,
so, and then the price is 16 for
just 4,000.
Um, and because they are in the United States of America,
they do not need to have any VAT.
And so it'd be at ease. You know, it's not a big deal if
they are in Europe. So for example, let me show you some
example,
This one, Brussels. So they are from Belgium,
it's European union. And if we do this,
we VAT is zero and we need to add the
notes percent charge.
So we need to do this. We always need to write these in terms
of notes. If we send to somebody within the European union except Germany.
So in Germany.
So for example, this is a German company,
then this goes away and we need to add 19% VAT,
but that's not how it works. So if Germany then VAT is 19%
in all the other cases, it's zero. And if it's
within Europe, then we need to write within,
I think we didn't get a beam unit. Then it's a VAT.
0%
Church. Yeah. And since we're writing this to rice,
because they are in the United States of America who just leave the AP zero and
two do not get any, okay.
You didn't write. I always,
I tend to make mistakes in this world.
So it's actually should be one, two.
I think it's like British too.
And then, um, in November,
issue them sometime another invoice,
which will be this one from December,
then another one from March may and so on.
Yeah, you probably don't need to, I don't know. You need access to this
one. Maybe I will try to access data.
Um,
No, I think that's for
procreation and invoices and I will later show you how to
create invoices or just let them,
or when I need to make money. Oh, maybe I can show you right
now. So you mentioned that, um, rice needs to,
uh, so I will say to me some ways I'll wait,
I actually need to edit this. Yeah.
We need to base,
like, we can always give 30 days for due date.
The issue date is today, 15 posts,
and then this is the invoice number. So usually it's a year.
And then, um, and then just,
and distinct is not updated automatically.
So the next time you create an invoice, it might be September,
but this one would motivate, so we'll need to change this.
Okay. So I think here,
and then this invoice, we can do like preview document and we can
download this and then send it to our
contacts. I will show you how to do this,
but for now, I want to show you, but I want to show you
a call to the invoices or emails or
newsletters. So let me create new document let's
and let's say we want to send invoice to,
for example, this one
promotion, because they are in Germany,
we select 19% and then we select their,
uh, the date. So for example,
And an aisle or a post,
and it would be there's 2022.
So this is all we do. Yeah.
For prices. Think I will just tell you every time,
how much we need to repeat their invoices
on maybe one more thing. So let's say if somebody wants to do two
promotions with us, so then,
uh, so they want to do two weeks and it just looked like this
search will be two items for each promotion,
which would be separate one.
I don't think it's okay.
So the next thing I wanted to show you is how to sense these
document. It is save it, save it.
Oh, awesome.
22. And,
uh, and name is
the name. And like,
I kind of be actually let's rename it to make it convenient or
S**t.
So for example, this one is sponsorship could be put
down this to know what this thing is about.
Just one second. Okay.
So yeah, I called them to invoice contact or our ice
is this one. So just pull it to
Swan until, so we will Emily to CC
Case.
So now we will send them
to
Yeah.
And then
This is cool.
Yeah.
Yeah. Um,
yeah.
Oh
Yeah. So we just send it.