Okay. Now I want to show you,
um, how I create documents for podcasts.
So Rahul reached out to me.
He wants to be a guest on a podcast. Well,
here, it doesn't matter who reached out to, but we agreed that he
will be a guest on the podcast doesn't
work. Yeah. So we talked about different topics that he talk
about and we chose this,
uh, transitioning from data engineer to data engineering manager.
Yeah. And then went on a date and
what they want to show you. So this is specific for podcast needed for
other types of plants. So for that,
we need to, I am going to actually,
I should share with video.
Sure. Let me share this whole folder with you.
Yeah. In editor, sorry.
In this four halter, what he needs is,
uh, what cost in this
podcast. Yeah. I have a lot of copies of copies,
but this is all you name it.
We don't need to put this in documented.
This is just a template that I use all this piles at the same.
So all these names, uh, they follow the same format,
August documents. So you see, this is a document that I prepared for the
podcast tomorrow. So this is that
the name is the date when it happens,
the name of the person and then the topic. So let
me take, uh, take this copy of compete,
open it. And I add in name,
item of this template. And then the date
is, were agreed on February 18th.
So it will be February.
Then the name will be a full chain.
Yeah. Please do with capital case and
then topic, uh, still to be discussed.
Um, inquiry time, we agreed on transitioning
from data engineer, data, new manager.
Um, and then, so because I already have his email
and, um, shared with him,
sorry, say it there. Or usually what I do is I just click share
and then, um, probably link.
So change to 31 with a link, then make an editor,
write them down.
And then I write know I
asked that question or are,
oh, and if you just start with
questions, there can,
now I will not send it yet because I now want to add
two special guests today.
See here. Welcome.
Um, and I think that topic will be from
date, uh, each year to date,
uh, gee, this is you.
Could we discussed, uh,
what I think this is what we agreed on and we will need to
agree on the outline. And,
um, here we will hear
these questions.
So also think of some questions and I will put them here,
but also we wanted to put the questions he wants to get
me to ask him then.
So this is what I sent,
uh, sign on
my side as well. And
yeah, so now we have this,
then we also, I also need, even before that,
I think I didn't do, I should go down this.
So, uh, I need to add him to the spreadsheet sort
of chain. And then topic is,
uh, uh,
from that engineer to that HD manager management and we
forwarded a few, the date system
is terrible.
Um, so that we have a document that
I sent that already has,
by the way, this is called the document or the final document looks like,
so what kind of title here? We accept title.
We have outlined here and we have
like some view, some interim, and then this,
uh, everyone, all the speakers get this question,
like before we go into the main topic of something that starts with your
background, and then these are custom questions that I add
to set, and then this way speakers,
uh, just know what exactly I am going to ask them on the podcast.
Yeah. And, uh, this document should attend a book,
something like that. Um,
and this is for me to do for me and for the guest,
not for you, but you will,
we'll ask you to help me usually create this document with this document.
What we need to do next is we need to create an event.
Uh, we need to send the calendar invite,
sorry. So we'll go to calendar.
And then this is something next week. So this happens.
So the title will be that at docs. What cost then?
Uh, so description is here.
Questions, questions here.
Hmm. Then I will add you as
well. So you can modify the event in case you need it
in case let's say a speaker just has to,
to cancel it or to move it. Then,
uh, it always starts five minutes before the actual start.
So this way now to make sure that we don't have
any technical problems, then I actually need to add the
guest excuse, email
email is here. And then yeah.
Then we need to add this link ups or
so I will to get the link.
I'll save it, but do not send the event.
Then I go, oops, this one.
But yeah, you will have this link. I think I already covered
it in notion, but all the events,
the webinars and all the podcasts, they have the same zoom link.
And then I, yeah.
Then I add there's one link here in the location.
And I also have, I
Also have a document. I also edit to the document.
So the ink is always the same.
I will also send you this link, uh, and knowing what's up.
Yeah. And the important thing here is that just the emissions is that they
can modify events when you will create these events at me as
a, as a guest. So then I can modify it,
define it. Yeah.
I think that's all we need. So now I click save and then now
I click centers and now the guest will receive an education.
Yeah. So this is all of that.
And I think that's all I wanted to show you. Let me check.
Yeah. Wow. Maybe I'll just,
uh, all right.
And I think
you will probably do this through email, but maybe it's really not as well.
I dunno. Or slack would be usually I use for that.
Um, LinkedIn, I use for that email I use for that slack
sometimes Twitter.
Okay. So that's how I do this.
So this is how I create the document.
And by the way, the first part of this video was specific to podcasts.
So the part with, um, creating a document and then sharing that with
the speaker, with a guest, but the second part of creating the calendar invite
this one, it is not specific to a podcast or
an African business. It is the same process.
Okay. That's all from me, please.