Hi, so here in this email Anna is asking for payment through
a payment link and I wanted to show you how to do this.
So first you go to Fino and you create an invoice as usual but
in addition to what we typically do you add 2%.
1,500 plus 2%.
So yeah, it's 30, 30 euros extra.
And then since Double Cloud is in Germany,
you will add VAT, but yeah,
that's, that's a part of the different process that you already know of.
So this is the price that we will see. Send them in the invoice
that we create in Phenom. So this is like you create invoices as usual,
but then for the payment link,
we will actually need to go to Revolut,
Revolut business. I think you should have access to
Revolut business if you do not let.
You know, it's
it was a while ago since I joined since I used it.
Okay. I'll put this on post to figure out how do I login.
Okay. So it was just not the right year.
The right URL is the revolute.com slash business and then enter
the extra business account and then login. And I
am just continuing with my email.
I think you should have your own account. Okay.
I'll confirm it now.
Okay. I can turn the login from my app.
And here I
think we need to go to merchant and create a request
payment link.
And with the payment link,
we put.
So it, it will be this one plus 19% because
it's in Germany. It's VAT,
but yeah, it will be different for different entities.
So since these ones are in Germany, this is the price.
I'll
try. Integration,
integration, and then it's next week,
right?
Something like that. So this is what you will need to create.
Yeah. So this is the payment link.
We click create and this is the link we
sent. So I will send this link to you right now and
you will create an invoice to double
data. So you will ask, you will need to ask them for or I
can know all this like
company details and so on.
Right. And yeah.
So once you have them, you send them the invoice from Phenom and then
you send them this payment link. Right.
I will send you the link right now in Slack or in sorry,
in Telegram. So you have it, then you will send it and now you
will create a document, describing how to create payment links.
And yeah. Okay.
And I think let me quickly check if when we create invoices,
we can actually add some comments.
Yeah. So let's add this to terms payment link.
So yeah, we will add this to the payment link, to the terms and
notes. Okay.
So this is how we do this. Please create a.
Process document and please send it to Anna.
That's it.