Okay. The integration with mail meetup shows up here no
longer works. It means that now I have to manually create events meetup
as well. It's very unfortunate,
but this is what I do for that. So it takes to create any
event and then let's meet what I just created.
So this is the event I just created. And then come on board.
This is the name, the name,
the title. And then let's look at date and time.
So it's Tuesday, February 8:00 PM,
Tuesday 7:00 PM.
GMT plus one iteration is one
or then upload the photo.
So they're just over the same picture we used for loosely.
Um, truly for a lack of Tokyo at
work, this is kind of too tight
on that. It's fine. And then now we need to put a description.
I am just going to compete this
format a little bit here.
So, um,
um, bullet point list. So I need to do this and it's
this elaborate X here
and luck and thank you
for your out. Fortunately,
I was f*** my data
dogs, slack each day,
and then this is an Atlanta event. Um,
and it'll link to our YouTube channel and then Muslim.
Yeah, I think that's all when you do so title
time, division,
image, and description,
and then I'd select everything here.
Then, then this is online event. So YouTube channels here and then
publish.
Okay. And now it asks to announce it.
I announced cool.
But so unfortunately there is a lot,
there is not more when you work them before because integration,
Zapier stopped working. I hope they will fix it at some point,
but, uh, this is what it is.