Um, that's another one. So here,
I want to send a calendar invite to a speaker.
Um, she had to give a talk on a webinar.
So now let me go to this timetable and TSI already featured
stores. So not yet confirmed,
uh, well, we kind of agreed on a date,
so I can probably say that it is confirmed.
We can see like it eaten on a topic yet,
so she will send the title and the outline,
but yeah, we'll have the date and she'll also give me
your email. So now I want to send the calendar invite.
So we talked about the 15th of March.
Yeah. This one March.
Yeah. Tuesday before
they weren't like, uh,
data or,
and then I guessed, so,
um, let me check more
options too, just to show you that. Yeah.
You can modify the ones. You don't have to click on more options.
I think by default, uh, depending on what your default settings
are, my default settings are include many firebrand might
not. So maybe click on this more options and here
I need to add, so since this is a webinar,
I don't need to add a podcast description.
So only need to only need to add content or just
take it once a year and just send it to you.
I think we have to include that here.
And also here
send yes.
Nope. So this is how you send calendar invites.
You probably figured this out. Matthew just wanted to show you also that far
away in us, it's a little bit different and we can also send the
calendar invite even before we agreed on a specific topic,
but we're already agreed on a date. So just to block the calendar of
speaker, I sent this calendar invite.
So this is how I do it.