Okay, so I changed, um,
the template for the, uh,
for the newsletter slightly. So for the podcast session now,
we also have a list with bulleted points.
In addition to just that, we uploaded a new podcast episode.
Then there is no line break. And then we have the title,
then, uh, yeah, name, then a bulleted list and then a button.
So I created, I updated a template here,
right? So this is how it looks like. So then for the button,
you will need to put the,
the address here. I will not do this because right now it's,
uh, uh, yeah, this is, um,
a template it, right?
And then I wanted to show you how to actually get these things right.
For that, I ask you to register here in chat,
open eye chat,
chat, open eye. Then I already have an example here that I
used.
Yeah,
Here. Oops,
what happened?
It doesn't work, I guess. Um,
yeah, so the,
what I put here is, first I open this
chat, ai, and they write, this is a transcript of podcast episode.
Alex is the host, Andrina is the guest.
So here, of course, we should change the name depending on,
um, the guest. And I can show you a different example,
maybe not with Rina. Uh,
I'll show you for example, with an Angelica.
So, and, and gay Angelica is the guest.
Please write a summary as a bullet,
at least with 10 items. Then I put this line like with five minuses,
and then I copy everything starting from transcript till
the end.
So I copy this one and place
it here, right?
That's all I do. I hit enter. And,
uh, yeah,
this is a summary, and what you do is you copy the summary to
here, to this one points,
and then this one you feel like previously,
right? So please update a process, document for that.
And also, right now we don't use this,
but I want to use it in the future. And,
um, I'll show you what I mean.
So I'll say write, um,
memorable quotes from the AP
sort.
Yeah. So I think, uh, this could be,
um, yeah,
this is, uh, like ai, right?
So not all of these things are good.
Uh, like, okay, for example, this one is not really memorable or
this one, right? But, but you see some of the quotes may make sense.
Maybe extract 20 memoir
from the, from the transcript.
So, and we can actually use this for generating some
content on Twitter. So some of these,
uh, quotes are not super, like,
not nice. Some of them are nice. And then for now,
uh, we will not do much with this quotes.
I just wanted to show you so you know how to do this because
we no, why, it's, why it stopped,
because we probably will use this for publishing stuff on Twitter.
Okay? I don't know if it's done. Maybe it is.
But anyways, this is, uh, I guess this could be the reason why it's
not working. Okay. This is what I wanted to show you.
And, uh, yeah, please,
uh, update the, or create a process document for,
for use using this chat. Um,
open eye for extracting summary.