To show you how I create events,
how I can make announcement for the events,
but the events. So, first of all,
we have two types of events. Well, actually there are more,
but two main ones are webinars and live podcasts.
So right now I want to create a lifeboat customer.
Um, there are no, there are not so many.
They are not so many different when it comes to creating announcements.
Um, but for podcasts, we have documents like that,
that, uh, roughly outline, uh,
what podcast will be about in here.
We have title and subtitle. So,
uh, for the title, this is the title of payment.
Um, sorry. I needed to answer to make it,
uh, anyways, so this is the event that we need to create right now.
So for that, I'll go to Canva. So
first we need to create a visual for the event for that we use
Commonwealth and the
title is quite short. That's why,
so there are two options, two line title and one line title.
So we need to, this is a short title,
so we need one line. So it goes here and paste it.
I already created it. Um, but yeah,
there was something different. It just double click on this.
And then based on the title,
then download selected backpack clicked on lot.
So this is how you create a visual for the events. This process is
the same for both webinars and interviews with
costs. And now next we need to go to Eventbrite
seven, right? Is the platform we use for creating events.
Um, so I'm on the ride.com/my events.
Then it rejects to this organization events.
And yeah, so these are the events that we have E upcoming events.
So this, uh, uh, this game that we have here and
yeah, none of these events you see,
so one of them is a webinars. It has this TV thing here,
and the other one is a workshop. What we need to get an event
that is what customer, but that we go to past events.
And so this product management essential is for data professionals.
This was at podcast,
we'll have microphones here. So I click on this product management
essentials. Oops, I don't need to click on this.
So you move it, I think. Or so what I wanted to
do is past,
again, what I want to do click is here,
these dots, and then I want to click copy.
So no, they went is copied. So now go back to this document and
then I quickly the title. And then I copy the
subtitle as well. The subtitle subtitle also
contains the name of the person,
and then we need to select the date. So the date for this event
is here in the title 28,
this Friday, start on.
That should be the same. Usually we have events at 5:00 PM,
but this one is a little bit different.
So we agreed to have this at 1:00 PM.
And then in time is usually the events take one hour.
So that's why it's one hour.
And then I click here, copy them line event page.
So it will copy everything from there, from that previous event.
Okay. Copy event.
Okay. Now I caught two details
in details. I need to, first of all,
change the image to click delete,
then click on this thing and go to download and then select this one
could hear coaching. And then now
I need to change the outline. So mine is here
and then information about the guests. Uh,
yeah, I don't think I, Hmm.
Okay. I don't feel like a, typically I would have a larger biography here.
I don't think I got this from Lynsay.
So let me just copy that.
That works. Then we can later updated
then. Yeah. Let's not make the gap too large.
And then I click save. So that sometimes happens
that, you know, it looks a bit ugly.
I need to clean it a little bit.
So that's more Alliance for whatever reasons I don't know.
Right. And I click safe again.
This time it should be a pain. Then
I go to online event page.
So first of all, let me check that everything's updated.
So main event images, updated description,
some of these updated descriptions of data next take or two line on page.
And here, this is a link to our previous,
to our previous event. So we need to update this one.
Uh, so for that correct link should be YouTube dot slash C slash Datadog's
club. This is the URL for our YouTube channel.
And I just paste it here, PS,
then this one, probably with the www.
It works. Yeah.
So then I click save and then
she gets a one thing we need to check in tickets
to make sure that yeah,
so it depends on, uh, January at 2:00 PM.
So it should end after the event and score later,
but not before, because sometimes there is an error and for whatever reason,
um, ticket sale finishes before the event starts.
So I always double check that it's not the case here.
So here it's not the case. It,
the sale ends after the payment ends,
which is, uh, the correct behavior they expect to be here.
Now I click on publish and here I see it's,
uh, three public published now.
So yeah, here and I think for change, I just click,
publish.
Okay, cool. Now, uh,
we use, uh, was that there for integration?
So what happens is now in slack,
we should have this announcement channel and to see that even bright
creates this announcement saying that we've just created a new event,
career coaching, and it describes everything by WhatsApp.
It also does is if go to eat up.
If I go to meet up, then I go to the group,
I organize and then go click,
click, click treatment. And
they did a saved draft, actually had recently received
an email from meetup saying that from Zapier,
saying that they are going to stop supporting integration with meetup sometime
in the future. So probably after sometime this video will not be actual.
It will need updating, but it at least to give you an idea of
what exactly now, how exactly you can create an event in meetup.
So right now we have a draft here. Now I click edit and
here is here. It already has a title. It has a date.
It has a time duration,
one hour, it doesn't have a picture.
So I need to upload a picture. So there's the same picture
we used. So it needs a bit of cropping.
And then the text here is not formatted.
I need to format it. So responsibilities
To go, coach what's called problems.
It's not then about the guests.
And then I usually remove this thing.
Can just leave this joint. And yeah,
yeah, this is pretty arbitrary, but a leave it like that,
then make this event online. And then I select our YouTube channel,
the sending cause we used in right then here,
I don't know to all guests. I don't know why is up here,
keeps creating it like that. And then yeah,
click publish. So that period here,
just copy some information. So then I need to edit it a little bit,
but not more than that. And when this integration with Zapier stops working,
I'll probably need to put this main area,
which probably will be quite annoying. But yeah,
I think I just noticed, I just clicked also on an osteo
lens. So this is also an important step because now everyone who is in
our meetup group will get an education that are one is created.
Okay. I think that's all. So this is how we create events in Eventbrite
and meetup. And yeah.
So now we have this event here, um,
and that's, that's all.