Um, I see that he already saw this document.
I just wanted to show you what is here.
So here in this document data, those clubs kiddo,
we have, uh, well, this is a calendar with all the things.
So thirst, let me start with this column.
So this is the book of the week events,
and this is, uh, these are the everyday events that we have here in
this, uh, top in this,
uh, page. Um,
so this one already,
uh, it announce, so I usually,
well, I forgot about this, uh, this guy actually didn't drop,
so we didn't agree with him on anything. Maybe I will put it to
follow up.
So this is the first thing.
Then we have webinars, the second column,
and here we have, uh, some of these dates. This is when the book
of the week thing happens. So it starts on a Monday
and then on Thursday. And you see,
we have them every two weeks before that you can see then before that
we had this every week now we have helped them less
frequently would be heightened.
Um, so we'll have one already that is planned,
but not announced yet. Uh, in the other video,
I show how to booze. Then we have another,
no another column here for webinars and we
have another column or podcasts.
Um, and here, this is how I keep track of,
for, um, who we have,
um, uh, in the schedule,
but we haven't announced yet. And do you see here,
we have status, like it's announced in this Janine,
um, with Janine, we talked and we agreed to move it to 15th of March
um, so it means that we don't have a speaker for the next week,
which is a PD and this is the podcast.
So for podcasts, actually, there is a speaker for,
uh, for next week and I will add the same,
a separate, I will show how to now I do this in a separate
email, uh, in a separate video.