So you ought to do raffles on,
uh, three, so you'll probably get a member of the circle.
So I schedule, yes. And then there's these,
um, this report with some code
for actually keeping track of who retweets the tweet.
So later we can select minutes. So what I do at least,
so I select the Euro. Then I go to this,
uh, to this thing, to this project,
I will send you the thing. So then I go to actions and then
in this actions, I most hear two EDS tweets.
And then I click around. Now I put the Euro
and yeah, important that it shouldn't start with mobile.
So it should be just the Euro from the pollution.
And then you click on, so now it will,
um, it would, I don't see it.
Oh yeah, it is here. So now yeah,
this is fine. You think?
Hmm. Yeah, it should be quite fast.
Let's say it's not important of what it's doing here.
The important part is when I go,
when it finishes. Yeah. So now it's finished,
you see this, uh,
this, uh, like a tick that it's successful.
So then they can go back and see that there is a commit from
GitHub actions. So this commit,
it's a line here in tweets.
This one. So this is that we can check that you texted,
it was edit. Then at the same time,
what's also happened. It created this d*** there with,
uh, , um,
that's not super important, but you see what actually is happening in
this file. Uh,
we have, uh, names of people who come
see it here. All right.
So these names are here. And then from this names later,
it will select five minutes. Or you have the,
I guess this is not the important part. The important part is like how
you think of the sink. And I guess let's say the most important
part. And then what will happen later is every hour,
all the people who repeated end like
to be in it. Okay. That's all, that's how you start
watching you start monitoring this thing. So it makes sure that we don't because
the problem is with, um,
keeps the last hundred liters.
So we need to pay entirely. That's why we need,
okay. Anyways. Yeah. The important part of this call you just for your information.