Oh, hi. I just noticed that the file,
this picture that you submitted recently is quite large to max.
And then if I open it, it's also open it
with a different editor.
It's also quite large. So this is like,
um, I don't know,
100, um, basically it's just a huge,
um, I think what we should do is in general,
we should prefer smaller images.
Everything like that, like 400 by 600 is enough.
Um, we do not need a bigger one. So please,
next time when you upload an image and if you get as like a
large one resize it because we do not need to be key much.
And then now I will save it saved on the,
see it's like instead of two, two gigs,
two megabytes, it's 84 kilobytes.
It's important because for the page,
but right now let's say if I open the website,
um, I'm gonna go to books,
like actually takes time to load this image.
So this is the same image and it, uh, it is to max it's
Barch. So now it will build faster.
So please, next time when you upload an image,
uh, please try to briefly size it tight to make it,
uh, not way to launch.