I want to show you how to expert emails from,
um, unstable.
So we'll have a couple of courses where people would use the full air
table. So for example,  and others.
So right now I need to go to this and they want
to save all these emails so that I click here on green to you
and click download, see the CSV.
Well, this is the file.
Then I select all these files and
I need to take towards
Yes,
Yes. And then they are to trash.
So they're not pumping. And then the assistant pile,
we just upload it. We need to change it to change the name.
So it will be 20 25, 27.
So this is the, the wrist.
Now I need to move it to throw books,
books. I have a folder called courses that I will share with you.
And then, so here we talk about  and
I put the list here. Let me share the folder
with you. Sorry. Okay.
I'll share this after this. Okay.
And now we need to upload these things to MailChimp,
MailChimp
import contacts, and then upload a file.
So this one, typically you copy paste,
but this one has different bros
and this one would have two
books for USCIS respond
and organize, then update updating existing contacts.
Um, and that would meet
Just once.
Um, now we need to specify techs. So for this farm,
the techs, um, this will be MLS.
Um, and to my lips was an income plan.
This protects, um,
continuing for lunch. No,
it says that. Okay. Email.
So it cannot impart others. I don't know.
I seen bird competing birds.
Um, the, this how you input, and then once it's imported to MailChimp,
you take this one and he put this two o'clock folder and this folder
upload folder, we keep on doing those records that are uploaded.
Okay. So for this call, how you do this? I think I will actually
move this to Google, to Google drive and we'll will go
drive. It will be also, uh,
full the courses and then the name,
because you already have access to Google drive and it's tickets easier if you
just, um, we'll keep it there.
So let me just be in Google drive.
So, um,
we have of courses,
but this is not the folder I want to use.
I want to use the folder mailing list. I will create for other courses
here. I'll just take all these things.
And so this,
uh, you will need to use this data looks pop made in these courses.
And then for example, you would need to put the files here.
All right. So the next one,
The Swan that we just uploaded, you would need to put it here and
then you would need to upload this to MailChimp. And once it's uploaded,
you would just put this to upload folder. Yeah.
This is how we do this with movies through Google drive to
keep everything in one place.