Hi, I wanted to show you how to create slack dumps.
So slack dump is, um,
like a backup sort of like,
uh, all the information. All the conversations from slack is,
uh, are exported in a file.
So I wanted to show you how to get this data and,
um, for this, um, so we click on this icon here or not icon
with the, the thing and then tools.
And I think we go to actually workplace settings.
Yeah, that's right. So, uh,
workplace setting, setting, seminar administration,
workplace settings, and then here we click on import expert data.
So then it's expert here and then here
expert data, entire history,
and then start, this usually takes some time.
So I will, um, put this on,
on pause and once it finishes,
it can take some time. So it actually says that,
uh, yeah, so that it will be an email.
So right now I will just put it on pause and then come back.
It finishes. Okay.
So I got this email from slack. Uh,
also usually they send,
um, bot notifi.
So either way we can just go links,
lead to the same thing, this page,
where we initiated here,
we just downloaded.
So I dunno how much time it took, uh,
five, 10 minutes maybe to do this.
Uh
doesn't to do when it opens.
Um, let me just go to thes. Yeah,
this is this thing. So now I want to go,
I just created a special channel. I also added a you here.
So in this channel, I want to upload this down so
other people can also use it. Uh,
so go first down with all the data
and yeah, so now I just put the down
here so people can use it. So this is how you expert
the slack data [Inaudible] and this is how you're shared with the rest of
the community.