Yeah. So I wanted to talk a bit about, um,
this thing that you Hilton. So I remember that I sent
an email, so let me find it. So ,
uh, I hope the video will actually work so sent,
so let me check out so many emails. Yeah.
You there's a lot of works.
Okay. So yeah, so what I did is I sent this email to Dropbox,
to this email and through books and waste attachment,
and the subject was sponsorship course.
Right. And that's why, when we,
this thing here, it had the date.
Right. I think I did this today.
Right. So the thing is because I did it today,
it actually, it has the wrong date.
So first of all, that's, uh, it happened on 30 August,
at least the payment. So the payment is,
uh, this one I paid. So usually when I pay,
I do eat on the same day.
That's why, um, yeah,
I don't need to change, but in this case,
um, yeah, we needed to change because I sent them the thing this email
today, right. The hours ago.
That's why, yeah. The date wasn't correct.
And now let me see,
what do we have here? Um,
yeah, so I wanted to also talk about,
so this one, the invoice was issued on this date as well yesterday,
so we can actually check it. It could go to invoices,
the sponsorship course again,
I think I need to change the date here.
So this is the date when the invoice was paid
and here we see that the invoice was created also on August 13.
So it was created and paid at the same time.
So no wonder. So here.
Yeah. I changed it to 13 and then we need here,
um, the provider, right? So they provide their,
is this
and put here and then a
description is this one and get,
and it's a course, so I'll good at something
like that. Let's say that it's actually a sponsor.
Of course. I don't think it says,
Um, of course I think it's clear and
yeah, that was the total you're depleted.
And that actually,
or why, well, why did you put 100?
So no. So this one, so this is the price in,
so this is the transaction, right? So the first thing is the price in
dollars. And then the second is the price in yours.
So it shouldn't be this month. And even though each of them,
I see where the confusion is coming from. So subtotal is at least one,
but it also has like value added tax,
which is, which is 19% in Germany.
So this guy he's in Germany and also in Germany.
And so there is evaluated facts.
Uh, I think, uh, companies from the states have simple as,
so basically. Yeah. So this is the total,
the amount I had to pay. Right.
And, uh, yeah.
Then this was the amount in, wait,
your reserve actually, it's more than the Eurozone dollars.
Funny thing. Um, anyway, so this is the amount I had to pay in
dollars and this is the amount they have to pay in heroes.
And the tan take care more about Devon and the amount they have to
pay in years, because all they will keep in has to be in euros.
And because I'm based in Germany. So yeah,
this is how you, um,
this is how you do this is how you feel.
Uh, this thing that maybe next time it will be easier.