Um, so, and I just thought you created these templates,
a copy of the template, but here,
this thing, you should replace it with the name,
Mike planning to do this. And,
um, I also asked you to place,
this Should be the name.
Um, I'll probably update the template a little bit,
but please this, the process,
doc, that all these things,
when you create, you should replace all this place folders.
So an example would be X, you cannot replace because this is the topic,
which we didn't agree, but the already know the name.
So please replace the names and I will change slightly
change them. And the place called those.
So it's clear for you what you need to change.