Okay, so I was checking the problem you mentioned yesterday about not being
able to create multiple events in one event Yeah,
so what we can do to fix that?
First of all, the reason we needed multiple events and do not forget to
also include this in the process document when you update So
the reason Okay, let me see So this is
what you should include in the context of the process document So we need
uhm Project of the week is a multi-day event
So it takes the entire week And we want
people to get reminders every day about the event and what they
need to do during the day Right?
So previously we used a multi-multi-event,
sorry Or whatever it was called, I don't remember Uhm,
so here, as you see, it's no longer available Bummer, but
we can work around that By going to emails And
then And sending a reminder So here,
we can Select Ray So we will need to manually Add
10 reminders But you can just copy-paste And we will probably have
a template from the previous Like
how we created previously. So we have a template So,
uhm We're gonna create an event which is in the template we used previously,
so please update the process document
and instead of using one event,
instead of using multiple events, create a new reminders,
so this is starting tomorrow,
it's fine, starting in one hour,
no we don't need that And
then we just need to create 7 different emails,
so this one we'll remove, so
we'll create 7 different emails,
so please find out what these emails are,
I don't remember, and uhm And
yeah, let's have a template for them. And
also for this one, so we will need to replace it,
I'll send you the link to a video,
so we will need to change the URL.
But this is, this will be later.
So let's update the process documents,
send me the process documents for checking, send me the templates we used for
checking, they are probably also uhm in
the same process document. So let's update that and this is how we do
it, do it, we add emails and do not forget that we need to
remove this uhm
And I'm wondering if we do this, this is something we send immediately,
right? Yeah,
whatever. So we are interested in scheduled emails.