Oh, hi. I am trying to keep track of payment to freelancers.
They have two freelancers book helped me one helps with podcast transcripts
and other one helps with procrastinate.
So there are two of them and they came up with this document to
try to keep track of, for what they do and payment.
So let's see here, we have title of the podcast and video to
YouTube status,
and then whether I paid or not.
And yeah, so what happened is this,
um,
uh, this one and data science, the data engineering was done,
editing was done. Um,
and then let's, this one was done,
uh, space in progress.
Um, then start started. And then also if
we need to, there was another podcast after this from a digital
analytics engineer, which was this one is male
edit here.
Is there something you will send to
transcription this link? He not started
with this. And then when it comes to editing.
So in this one I uploaded yesterday and
also the other batch or so
I need to,
um, Fridays.
So I paid for, yeah.
So this , what is the
progress right now?
He's moving to different country.
She's moving to Georgia. So that's why he hasn't finished yet.
The transcript. Yeah.
So this is the document I use for keeping track count down and next
time, um, I will ask you to,
so for example, he played next time I play for everything
I lost. You usually I'd be in your support.
I will ask you just to act or yes or yes here.
It is something also to know the status.
Okay. That's all.