Hi, I think, yeah, I think we should redo this a little bit.
Cause I think they don't really care about the overall number of clicks in
the newsletter. They more care about the number of clicks on their
content. So I prepared this,
a template that you should use so I can break down and
then let's do it in together. So go to MailChimp and
then in MailChimp. So no
open that campaign, that campaign with this
one, it was the last week.
And here we have the number of links. I
actually like huge the total number of
this. I think they don't really care if it's
a, what's the number.
So it doesn't matter if it's a, maybe we can say X,
uh, nah,
I don't think they really care. They just care the number of clicks coming
from the newsletter. And we have it here and say,
we can take here what links.
Yeah. So this is basically
the percentage, just total number.
So that's the number then we need to feel in
this one clicks in theater. So let's go to,
and then Twitter I'll quote you or data co-op account.
It was one week ago, right?
So tweet analytics and we had 11 clicks
and let's see LinkedIn.
So,
and this one probably did a little better.
So let's see. I'll do actually see this.
Maybe we need to remember that
these sticks here,
there was a way to actually Lucas.
It doesn't seem like this.
Hmm. Yeah.
I don't know how to check and also try to find it.
Yeah. It used to be possible. Like there was some sort of hidden
somewhere, I guess. So now, um,
I'll find it.