Um, hi. Yeah know, just wanted to show you how to actually do this.
So when you go to an event to dashboard,
there is this thing responses to custom questions.
So click on this. It will open another page
and in this page. Yeah. So we select the event we want.
Right. And then, uh,
so yeah, this is statement, uh, this is the data we have and we,
as you see, we actually have this thing here.
Right? So this is fair. They think we want,
right. So now I just download it as CSV,
open it, like usually, and oh,
we have this data here a while.
So like a lot of new stuff,
I guess they kind of separated it. So now we need to go to
custom questions and yeah,
you have it all here. So do this call.