So I want to show you how to delete a file from GitHub and
how to delete. So we need to actually delete a book of the week,
but what I show is actually actually works for
delete in any file, right?
So in this specific thing uh, in the process document that we will create,
we will talk about delete in 8-4,
a book of the week.
Umm.
And so this is what we want to delete this understanding ETL.
And we click on that. And actually the first thing I wanted to show
you is instead of deleting what I could do is
instead of creating a new one and deleting the old one,
what we could do is actually just edit this one,
right? So when we edit, there is beginning,
there is start and end. So we could just change it,
right? Of course the name,
the old the old name is also possible to change,
but what would be sufficient is just changing the start,
the end date. And yeah, you can also change the file name,
right? But right now I want to show you how to delete and please
also create a separate process document for showing how to
delete, umm.
Bye. How to edit the beginning and end or
in general how to edit the book of the week stuff.
Okay. So here I want to show you how to delete.
So this is where we came previously.
We'll click here and,
and uh we'll click on this thing, right?
So I need to scroll a little bit down. Umm,
for you or interface it might be different but I need to scroll a
little bit down and then I see delete file.
And also,
now we will delete it. Thank you. What is important to note is this
path to you. So I will copy it.
Umm,
I'll put it to a note right now. Umm.
This is the path that umm.
We need. Umm.
Right now I will delete it.
So click on that.
Can we change this now? Right glitz.
Umm.
So now the fire was gone. We don't see it here.
But some of the files that we also need to delete are not gone
yet. So they are contained here.
In images. So now we go up.
We'll go to images. We'll
go to books. Now we'll go to me. I can name this thing.
Yeah. So.
Let me show you the one on there.
We'll go to images.
We'll go to books.
And we need to find that book.
So see. This is here. So this is the path.
So we'll go here and that.
We can delete each file individually like we did last time,
right? So click on that and delete what I think here is possible to
delete the entire directory. So again.
So. Okay. So
you click on this dot, dot, dot.
Delete directory. So you review the list of files.
So just do files. Can we change this?
Now what the file is going? Or what the file is?
The directory is going. Umm,
this is how you delete, uhm. Book of the week.
Um, so from this video you please create three process
documents. So first created generic,
uh, process document describing how to delete a file and the
directory from GitHub. Thank you.
Then create another process document that describes how to uh,
edit a book of the week event or page
how to locate. So from the very beginning like from the top of the
repository it should go from the top of repository like exactly how to
locate the file and what to edit and how.
And also how to delete the entire book of the week file.
So they're described that um this is where the file is,
where this is the images is, are and you can refer to the first
process document for details on how to delete it.
Okay. Thank you.