Sometimes they can get this mails from people who cannot try and slack to
say, try and train community.
But haven't  I think so.
And they usually send me emails. So what I'm doing in this case is
I copied their email. Then I go to slack.
Then I click here,
invite people, and then the email could accent.
So if a sound and then I click it down,
sometimes it's actually says that this person is already in slack.
So maybe because they wrote this email,
but they received the, actually they receive the invite.
So then the slack says that person is already there.
Um, yeah, this wasn't the case.
So in this case, when it sent,
they invited it was successful.
Yeah. And then I go here and they reply saying,
um, can I just
check your email
are right?
And then they could extend. And if,
for example, slack would tell me that this person is already there in my
reply, I will say, Hey, it seems like you've already managed to register.
You still would have chemo. Right. Or go to something I can help with.
And yeah. So this is how I invite people to,
uh, to slack when they have problems. And,
uh, the reason I'm showing it to you,
because this is not the first,
uh, I have a bunch of things.
So for you,
yeah. I will not add anything here.
So you can just maybe add them on,
let me have a bit of time. So this is called an wait people
and I will appreciate your help with that.