So data stop is not the only community.
There are other communities. And I also can go in them and sometimes I
come across. Interesting people put example is,
uh, so he is, uh, um,
yeah, he built some open source tools.
So I want to reach out to him and invite him to open source
spotlight. So I will invite you to Do
this community as well. So you will get an education,
but to here, I want to show you what I do.
So next time, maybe if I see somebody interested,
interesting, I'll just Send
you a message to reach out to them.
So
One
Message
To them.
Uh, so now I'll introduce myself and say that I
At this and I will not settle certainly about,
Um,
Yeah. So this is how you can reach out to authors of open source
tools in other communities. And I will now invite you to this one and
perhaps to others. So you will get a notification.
You will get an email right now,
please email and register in these communities.