Um, hi, I am not sure where this number comes from and this
is not correct. Um,
but, um, so I want to show you how to actually show how many
people attended the webinars. So you go to the link and
then here
And then the X And in analytics,
you see how many people actually watched this.
So I usually take a screenshot of that when people ask me how many
people attended the webinars and send it,
Um, I mean,
And also the total number, what do you do,
um, Is 19.
So yeah, this is how you get statistics about how many people actually
attended, because you were probably sharing,
I'm not sure where this number comes from, but this is quite misleading.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
Please don't do that. It's better to like when they ask how many attended
actually say how many attended,
not stations because many people register,
but to not show up. So Yeah,
this is what.