Um, there is another thing I wanted to show you in MailChimp is
experts in audience to all the emails that
we have. So you need to, this is,
first of all, I usually just start with MailChimp website and
I'm already logged in. So usually when you log in,
you end up in this, okay.
This dashboard, but then you go to audience.
And so the audiences data docs,
you click on you contacts, and
then you click on experts, audience.
So click on this and it starts expediting the audience and
yeah. Then you will receive an email.
So I already just deepest,
Um,
I click on this one, so you should receive an email.
Do you think click on something.
Oh, okay.
I could take some time, um,
one minute or something like this and then,
uh, yeah, this expert, this radio. I can just click on this button,
I think. Yeah. And then he'd done lots of file.
So we open this file and we put the name,
it would say 20, 22, 0 5 or 17.
What's the day to day 27 97.
Um, members export. Yeah, that's fine.
Oh, we'll kind of just leave it like this, just to,
so, and then,
um, then we upload this to Google drive,
so we'll just create a folder that Google use for this.
So create a folder that,
uh,
Oh cool.
Least.
All right. So you're going to need to upload to this folder data,
top slot made in these backups and just take this thing and upload
it here. Now it should be applauded.
Okay. This is how you take a backup of the audience from MailChimp.
Um, yeah. And this is how you save it to Google drive.
That's all I wanted.