Hi, I want to know for you to start working on newsletter
And thread. Now in thriller,
I
Want to add a few points, so you know what them,
And
can you
Smell
We'll need to this link a doc,
I think we have a process document about that.
So this
Link it, You
Think it's.
Yeah, so basically this happens before,
Before the newsletter goes out. So
I think every week, um, sometime during the week,
maybe, I don't know, on Wednesday or Thursday,
it will ask you to start preparing the newsletter.
And then one of the points here we'll be feeding in the newsletter
announcement. So this is for the book Then
for,
Um,
And for,
Um, So let me show you
For
That
Chimp. Yeah. Excellent.
To have this podcast section this way in your podcast episode.
So this is typically available when we have a podcast page.
So it's one of the items here
That last
Page.
I think they have fun document about that as well.
Sorry.
So this should happen before. Um,
So usually this happens, let's say on Friday we make the podcast
page or on Sunday and then on Sunday,
because we already have the template or the newsletter.
We can just go there and replace one of the things That
links there. Yeah.
I don't think we need to Do anything else here
at some at this point. So I just added one more thing here
in the book of the week. And one more thing to
the podcast. We'll now separate one for,
for the newsletter. Um,
so you know how to be ordered not,
but they just want to show you how you clone it and leave it
for like when we don't get this podcast episode.
Okay.