Okay. So regarding this officer think here,
so indeed they contract with support that this is relative to the beginning
of the meeting, not to the beginning of the recording.
That's why it's all. So the recording is shorter than this thing.
Um, and Yeah,
so I want to show you, so I asked them to fix this,
but before they fix this in zoom, we can do a workaround.
So what I did Say it a
quarter to another one. So what I will do,
um, For the next months,
I will write that in the chat. So we'll have a timestamp when we
actually started recording And towards the we'll deal with this
for the staff, You will go see here,
this is the spreadsheet they just created and shared with you.
Let's see here,
This is the
Location.
And here you need to, in this,
in this cell, you will need to add this timestamp in this format.
and then minutes and seconds, And then it will change the format
of the Madigan. But this is important.
Two hours here. Otherwise Google later
will not know how to what's this. So this is
the start. And then we write the regional timestamps.
Yeah. So the regional timestamps here,
so this is the laptops we need for editing.
So,
And what we do next is we use a formula here And
we, so the formula is B2 and resell a minus
a to B cell. But when we,
we need to change eight to a little bit.
So we need to add some dollars here, Aren't you?
So the formula is B two minus a dollar,
a dollar. And the reason we need this dollar is when
we make this formula dome,
is that you see it changes to obesity and so on,
but eight to stays the same. So you don't Wait.
So that's why we need it. And yes,
it'll be spotless. Maybe they can just do all the way down.
So you don't actually need to worry about this foremost,
or you wouldn't need to do is just put the stuff here in original
timestamps. And,
um,
You know, it's, the team will,  Also,
I contacted support and ask them,
um, what was the beginning or when the meeting started and when the recording
started recording started what the, this one,
This file, but the one who said problems with,
and they told me that the meeting started at this time and important started
at this time. So here it means that the
actual meetings to the minutes,
so the start should be this one.
And now what we'll do is we will just takes these
timestamps. And The
first one, This is the second one.
There is one.
Yeah, let me check it the sexually timestamps,
make sense. So I'll go now to three 11,
We are building an, also a new language that we are building,
uh, that is called sort of seal, uh, which is,
um, sorta checks language and,
um, the tool that is going to, uh,
evaluate everything that is written and sort of seal is called sort of core.
So what is sort of seal, uh, sort of seal as a DSL for
data reliability? So
what are we going to show today? Uh,
I'd like to show, uh, a new,
um, a tool that we're building and also a new language that we are
building, uh, that is called sort of seal,
which is, um, sorta checks language and,
um, the tool that is going to, uh,
evaluate everything that is written and sort of seal it's called sort of core.
So what is sort of seal, uh, sort of seal as a DSL for
data reliability, TSLP, the domain specific language?
I do not think it is correct.
Um,
I'm wondering the why Let's check this seven
15.
Uh, you can see that
I created already, uh, with,
um, the tool installed for the sake of,
uh, time. Uh, so like me activate
Or so here, you can see.
Yeah, I think this is not working it because this is
not right. The, probably something is wrong.
I don't know what, um,
but I can see, uh, like from this calculation,
if you subtract six, uh, five,
uh, you do you pick a plate,
so this looks correct. So five,
so this should be the correct time stamp. I think the problem is with
that. So trying to figure out what the stat is,
and then you're going to use this timestamps for editing.
And then after that, or the nuance will always ankles
too, but they will always also write to that.
So then you know that this will be a,
and to see that say like when the
recording started.