Hi. So you see this invoice from pal.
All right. So I wanted to show you how to pay for these invoices.
So first of all, we need to forward this invoice to the invoice
attachment and, um,
edit subject name to, um,
transcription. Cause this is what we do,
transcription of QA, a sessions.
Um, so you see this invoice will appear in Dropbox with
this name transcription and it'll have today's date.
So I will send it right now. So that's the first step.
And then I will go to phenom and then,
ah, yeah, it's in German for me,
but you probably know like for you, it probably appears in English.
So now I need to sign up to sign in.
Okay.
So let me type in the quote.
Um,
So I received a quote on,
uh, mobile phone. You probably also have this and
we, I need to do a new payment.
So the invoice was for,
Um,
100 7170,
and then here, we already know,
so this is pav. So let me just make sure that the
IBAN the bank account name is correct one.
Yeah, it is still the same still the same.
And then here, we also mention the invoice or is the
invoice in the invoice number?
Yeah. And now, so it's 170 net review payment.
Um,
Yeah. Looks legit looks right.
Um, you know, and for you,
it'll probably look different. So for you,
when you do something like this, I will have to confirm now
we will see how it works. Actually. I don't know. So
I am confirming this.
Okay. Now
Something is wrong with, with my up just a second.
Okay. Now I confirm.
Um,
Yeah. And, uh, that's it,
I guess, so,
Uh,
Payment download PDF,
um, maybe,
uh, what we can do now is download this thing or
maybe I will just make a screenshot of this thing
and, um, could be also like you can just download a PDF and send
it. I just screenshot.
Thank you, pav. The invoice is
great. I actually don't know.
Um, so for you,
because you might actually need to,
uh, wait till I confirm it, so maybe we will need to change the
process document later, but, um,
for now we can document it this way and then we will see how
exactly, um, it'll look like.
Okay. And I think I just signed it and
by the way, I want to confirm that we have it in Dropbox.
So I go to invoices and then
we have it here
transcription. So we'll have the document and then we
will need to go to, um,
Bookkeeping.
Right. And then we will need to update
it. Uh, yeah, where it is.
So we need to update it here and you already know how to do
this. So with pav it's,
uh, we'll copy it here. So it's just transcriptions without
articles. Mm.
And then we need to fill this in.
So yeah, maybe for that one, you can do it later.
Um, when you see this video,
you can do it. Um, so here you would need to like,
let me just do this since I'm here. So it's minus 170 and for
this one, uh, please do it. Okay.
That's uh, that's how we do it. So this is how we pay invoices.