So I want to show you how I reach to reach out to people
about podcasts. So LAN uh,
I contacted her recently. I introduced myself and then I asked,
would you be interested in being a podcast guest?
And then I also say that, uh, somebody else,
uh, nor the mill recommended that I reach out to her.
Um, so yeah, if, um, if not that,
maybe I, would I meet that and just say that I'm Alexia from Datadog
spark and this one. Um,
and then yeah, she replies. Yes. And I already propose
a topic here, uh,
where this I,
uh, I said, no, I recommended, uh,
and I'd be quite interested to talk about your experience of transitioning from data
science to data engineering. So I already proposed the topic.
Um, sometimes when, I don't know what topic is,
I just want this guest to this person to be a guest.
I just reach out without proposing the topic. And then we to get to
agree on a topic. So here I already proposed the topic and then she
agreed. She said that she'd be happy.
And then what I want to do now is I say,
um, I do
hear about these, uh,
uh, and then I propose,
uh, a date. So the next available date is 25th
February. So I'll put here,
here, and then, and then,
uh, let's see,
um, proposed date.
So I'll ask your, um,
would 25 February it's
17. Em's at work where you
are,
or it's too early.
You meet more time, maybe like that.
Um, they'll also say I'll be
how, uh, working on preparing
questions for you soon,
and we'll send you questions
for you and send you at least this one.
Yeah, something like this. So I both said that,
uh, I proposed a date and then I mentioned that I will be working
on preparing questions for here. And of course,
uh, I will also ask now in the mean time,
uh, there are
Questions that you like,
um, you'd like to over something
like this, and then yeah, it's tentatively booked with yours if she says,
okay, it works then. Uh,
yeah, we can just say it's confirmed.
And then of course, once she confirms,
oh, we will do this ink with Kate and@podcast.com.
Okay. So this is how I reach out to people regarding.