I changed the structure of this suppository with transcript reviews.
So previously it was only the case in time quotes these things,
right? So these things that we put to YouTube,
I changed it a bit. So now actually time codes,
goals go to time codes,
folder. And then now there is another folder.
So before timecards were going to transcripts,
but this is a bit misleading. So now transcripts contains transcripts.
And later on, when we will process the transcript
from that, he created that something,
I will show you how to add this transcript to the website right now,
if we go to the public side, I just added the podcast
episode and you see it, doesn't have this thing here.
So there is not transcript yet, um,
with Ellen because it's not 3d. So now,
because we have these things, now I will show you later how
to use these things. There's transcripts at
the task to the website. Okay.
So just to summarize now,
time codes now, after you upload,
I think two X, two docs order,
and action will be executed. And time of course will appear in the times
code folder and transcripts will appear in the transcripts folder.
Typically you will not need to do anything with transcripts when we have
them in time, but when they are later and we need to do something
with them, we'll need this.