Okay, so the garden, the area posted.
So I see that you added Moran to the table.
So just wanted to tell you that if we already have somebody or somebody
on the website, you do not need to add them to be stable.
So you can quickly check this. If you go to data docs,
Klopp to people, and here you can find,
uh, um, Moran.
Yes. So he's here, he's already on the website and in DTO,
right? That this is the reason would have,
uh, and narrow in there.
So we have from Moran here and now I will show you what to
do in case. Now we have a user already a person
on the website. Um,
yeah. So we will need to go to data talks club,
uh, YouTube, this one, and Dan
would go to scripts and data and
hashes. So here we store people.
Um, so this is a sort of encrypted email and this is their
ID. So ID is the thing we have here,
like, uh, after slash so people slash this is the idea of a Moran
and here we have a sort of a mapping from,
um, email to a person.
Right. And do you see that Moran is not here?
And it usually what happens when you feel a forum and to execute there
is there is an Euro here to go from an email to person,
right. Um, because this thing is relatively,
like I created it recently, um,
long ago before, long before I had Moran.
Hm. Yeah. So here what he needs to do to add him manually.
So first of all, you do not need to create this record.
So we at least have somebody, you do not need to create a record
in, uh, in this database, in the form.
Um, but what we need, need to do is soon we need to have
this mapping between the email and the person.
So click edit here. And,
um, now I need to have this encryption,
right? So I need to go from this email to
this hash. And for that, um,
there is a website that I can use, um,
this one, Shaw one minus online.com.
And I put the email here that I want to encrypt.
And it's important to hear that there are no spaces at the beginning and
at the end, and it's only lowercase letters.
So let's say if email looked like this,
and then let's say a space here, so we need to remove a space
here and we need, um,
make it lowercase, right? Although that there must be lower case and
then important that it's,
Shajuan here, it's by default and then I could cash.
And this is the result. So I take this series out and
I put it here at the end, uh,
this, and then I need to have the ID of this person.
And they  everything like between people slash something and then HTML.
So they ID is distinct. So I click here and
then it's important to add another line. So always there should be an empty
line at the end. So this is what I edit,
edit this line. And then I made sure that there is any way on
the one, um, which means ya,
I'm just key tender here.
And then yeah, just,
uh, could, can we change this?
And, uh, what the next thing I need to do is because you edit
already Moran. So I will go to air table and
I will mark him as edit ah,
people and yeah,
Moran. I am mark him as,
um, Don and
yeah, by the way, since we have three, three here,
and we didn't add Twitter before, so I can also show you how to
editor.
So for that, we need to go to the root here,
narrow to three separate repository, then people,
and here we look for,
um, Mariah. Yeah. He was him.
Then we click edit and we just tried
to be thorough. And then this is his Twitter handle.
And yeah. And just say,
let me check if we have the same bio,
uh, I think this is the same buyer,
right? Yeah. It is the same buyer.
So I just click commit changes.
Yeah. Here we mark him as edit already.
So I changed the status. So this way,
this clip to have, will not try to process this record.
So it will only process records that we need to add.
And there is nothing because every, everything is processed.
Um, so yeah,
probably. Yeah. So we have this event with Ryan.
This is email. And now, because we edit this mapping manually,
now it will be able to see that for this email.
So it will apply the same thing to the sea mail.
And it will find the record for this email,
but this is the ID and it will just create an event.
So let me now go to actions and three
gear generate all,
and now in three minutes, each should hopefully work fine.
Okay. Let's uh, this is what I wanted to show you,
how, how you add emails to this list if people
are already, uh, on our website now.
So by.