My creative thrill board. So what I did is I created this for
templates and to use the pro this whole time document that you created.
So what I did is the week thing here.
I created the checklist. First of all,
I put to the description, did they link to this document?
Because it doesn't seem to be possible to add links to the checklist and
yeah, maybe let me show you. So for podcasts,
what you can do is you can take this document.
Then I clicked here and then to put
this to the description,
and then now could eat checklist,
which quick on call just to please, and
then think this is not needed.
Yeah, indeed. This is, um,
We'll just copy this thing here,
then paste and then click.
And now it's been,
So now we'll have all the things from there and then now
you move this well, can you see all this link here or
not do it right now? And then there are a couple of things
that this is in mind for this one.
Um, so we can try to do,
do, did what it seems to like it's on the weight.
So what I do is I add a task
that says reminder or item,
um, next,
And then I put them in front of them in front of these to
remind the guests.
We don't need to add any other reminders.
Yeah. So you do this for the rest of the other tool and by
the way, you do not need to create process document for that.
This is more like one think.
Hmm. Okay.
Yeah, we'll have that. And let's say we want to now
create, uh, we'll need to create these templates for all the
things we'll have in our pipeline. So for example,
um, this, well,
we'll have a walk with, uh, with Roy that
happens next week. So for that,
what we can do is click on the template,
then create click created, cut from template.
Now for the book of the week, we can do,
um, let's think perhaps just
Monday will be enough.
My, so create your cards and then yeah,
it shouldn't be, I need to hear
it is announced. So put it here. And next time I create something
from template. Actually, I should have done this,
a good clear plate. So the least you,
instead of keeping template, you select something else now
with withdrawing, what do we need is,
you know what, each top I'm gonna eat on the lead.
We did all that.
Um, so I, I asked him,
you've always email
On links in the description. I actually don't know
What this thing is.
And should we share?
So we did that and then yeah.
Reminders. So when we are already here,
so you mentioned that this book is not coming in next week.
So what we do is,
um, this reminder for the next week,
you just to dates and then this
call would do, yeah,
I think you can set it to date that
yeah, no Wednesday before they went. So if they went on 28
February, you would put him reminder here,
doesn't matter. The time doesn't really matter, then I save it.
And then yeah. We'll, we'll cover remind
you to actually do this, reach out to the author.
Hm. Yeah.
So, and they did try to remind her just today.
I asked them and yeah,
so this thing is the announcement.
Then I invited the author to smoke.
Yeah. So before this shouldn't let me change this a
bit. So,
uh, once
then this is,
uh, yeah, so ,
and after that we invite them to slack,
which would happen on Wednesday. Okay.
Here. Now we can rearrange these things,
uh, as we see better.
And in general, this is the approach and wonderful,
I guess over time, we'll figure out how to best organized.