Um, hi, I wanted to show you in plan on what to do when,
when people get sore authors ask more information about events.
So Stefan, I reached out to him.
I asked if he wants to take part in our podcast
and then yeah, he he's asking.
I would, I would be very interested. How would this work?
And well, um, so it took a bit of time to get back to
him, but now I want to send him a document that describes what exactly
is it? I have a document here.
So just briefly describes what kind of programs would have .
And one of these things is,
uh, is ProQuest, uh,
quite detailed. So then here in this,
um, in this Google document and this Google document display away in,
uh, in this shared folder and documents,
and then there's this data dog's opulence and
year. Yeah. To get this link,
to get this thing that, uh, is shareable,
you can go file.
Yeah. This one published Philip, and then there is link,
but I will just send you this link right now.
So you don't need to do that here.
And yeah, actually in this link, I will select because this,
um, this person is interested in podcast.
So I would, uh, click on this podcast Inc.
And I will probably,
you know, maybe I'll just send
the whole thing. Um,
and then I'll send you
the, we
Probably
pretty split. If you need more information
also, I want to ask him his email. Then I will send this email
to you and ask you to do take care of that also.
Nice. All your
email so we can,
um, uh,
yeah. So the main thing here I wanted to show you is that we
have this document and if somebody asks more information about events
and what exactly, let's say, what is it,
what exactly is a podcast that will help this document that we're going to
just share with guests and hopefully answers all the questions.
Probably add more information to this, um,
document at hand, uh,
important. What is important.
You also have access to this document.
So if you,
if we need, if you need to change it,
you can also do that. Okay.
That's that's all I want to do.