And now I want to show you how to, um,
reach out to authors of open source libraries.
So this is the library and they want to reach out to people
who work on this so they can come to open source spotlight and do
them about this. So this is the library I'll be
detect. And then to understand who works on this,
there's this contributors top.
So click on this. You let's
go with the first contributor. So I do a control
click, and then I'm trying to look for contact
information here. So usually, um,
you know, here we don't have contact information.
So let me open the second one.
So for the second one, at least we will have the name and we
have a website. So this is the contact information I was talking about.
So I open this block
of this guy and here we see you,
you see what email, or even if we don't this
link team that is Twitter. So there are different ways to reach out to
this person. So now we have a way to reach out to him.
So I'll go email and then I'll,
and then I'll just press you an email,
or it could be also LinkedIn connection request,
for example, um,
here, um,
I'll talk about, uh, so I want to invite them to even demo about,
um, this library.
So I ,
I think I talk school.
Oh, okay.
Yeah. And now I want to say that open
source offers,
give them most about their tools.
I saw that you did,
he viewed to either be detect
I'll link it. I have pressed control key
And you find
here and then I give a link to open source
check.
Okay. So you contribute to
contribute. Would you be interested in giving a demo?
Yeah, we can.
They reach out to mundane to
invite them to do now open source spotlight.
Thanks.