Then now I want to show you how to edit it,
to remove the beginning from this team problem solving analytical skills.
Here's what I mean. So there is some stuff and some stuff,
Lindsey, there's some, this one talk,
this one, I would want to share my screen with
this editor
editor. And then in the editor,
I need to find the place where should we start the translation?
I'll just do a short introduction and then we will start there
event. So let me share my screen should
have been somewhere here. So now I click to
select to cut the thing I want to him to select the thing
I want to do before I say hi
everyone. So here I want to click split,
and then I will do this.
So we'll just take this.
And so this gray thing will be removed.
Click on preview then.
Hey everyone. Welcome to our event.
This event is brought to you by the great thing will be gone.
Now, click save. Now in a couple of hours,
say Speedo has been protest. Please check back later.
So in a few hours it will remove the beginning.