So, we have a problem that for Tanya it's just a name and
it will appear like that. Usually this happens when we don't have
a profile. And I think I showed you last time.
We have this link, slash people,
Tanya. Let's check.
Yeah, so you see, actually, if we look at the the URL here,
it's Tanya Wald.
Like there is a first a typo and then not here.
Full name, right? That's why it doesn't match.
And here it's just Tanya Vuh-Volt,
right? So this is not right. And we need to make sure that this
thing and this thing match.
And if we go to, uh,
first let's open the events.
I want to show you what I meant.
So here, so this is the ID for people that we have,
right? Um, so the room,
we, it's so slow like we have so many events.
And we have, uh, Teresa,
uh, I think should be here,
Tanya Berger, right?
So, uh, here we have this one,
but as you saw in people, we have a different name.
So to fix it, we need to go to people,
and we need to make sure that, uhm,
the name we have here, Tanya,
matches the name we have, uhm,
in the event. So in this particular case, uhm, this,
or what we need is just to rename this,
but we might also, uh,
create another file. Let's say if we don't,
if we don't have a profile yet, and then this problem appears,
then the reason is we don't have the profile.
So in this case, we just need to edit the file.
So this is how we change the name,
so this is where we update it, and you just can make changes,
and that's it. So right now, this should match, and, uh,
yeah, and also,
uh, wait a second, so this thing and this thing short should
match too, so it should be identical,
this one and this one, because I think it
doesn't look at the short,
and also I see already the image is not correct,
so I will also change the name for the image,
and now we will also need to go to this images slash authors,
and update it there. to,
so go to images authors,
so if you, if we need to add a person,
then we just follow, we just use the form, right, so you don't need
to create a these files, so this thing is only for updating
the, the these profiles,
so this is how we should call the process document I guess,
so now let me look for Tanya,
and again we need to rename this to,
okay,
so now you know if you accidentally make a typo or use
incorrect name or whatever for all the whatever reason,
we cannot match the profile,
so this is what you need to look for.
So the file names should be the same as here and the short,
this id in the file should also match.
And right now I think it shouldn't work anymore when
we update, so it will probably take some time but um like
in a couple of minutes it should work.
Yep, so this is how we do.