Yeah, for Hootsuite connect to Twitter,
because I'm where I am on the free plan.
I don't want to pay money for that. Um,
so I just want to show you how to use this simple Twitter interface
for scheduling. So the process is the same a
kit title. We get a description We'll
probably here because
we need to limit the
first. Let me copy it.
So then instead of the text here for free,
uh, You send emoji
and just less space and then take the link And
yeah, actually, No,
I'll just call data engineering conference,
the date, France
And data engineering Solution
and challenges, Um,
books.
So something like that. Um,
and then, Uh,
we'll schedule it For
Three Or 4:00 PM,
two days, four days, five,
Uh, three, 4:00 PM.
And then I just click confirm. And then now I
just scan. So this is how it was scheduled things,
um, with Peter. So this involves a bit of creativity.
So maybe before posting, you can run it by me to see like
when it doesn't fit and you need to do some things,
you can kind of run things by me Before publishing,
but yeah, this is how you're scared of things with Peter.