So what the book of the week,
um, the author said that he wants to slick the purse
in there randomly. So first they want to take part
in the discussion or ask the question,
c****** area name.
Then after I do this, we need to select to have,
And already it's there since keeping,
we also ask the question,
We need to slip the unique names. People will ask at least
one question.
So then it's me
A few people ask questions.
Um, Tim already asked the question and then we're doing this up to this
announcement. So from this announcement to do and
expect, we'll ask the policeman question now
a little bit, so that actually
any more, and that was kind of important.
So I wanted to know as I want to take this list and what
this tool is, the random work list here.
So this thing shuffles back a compromise,
and then yeah,
they are in that order. So I take them and
now I select the first five. So this will be the winners of the
book. You can see that the order is actually around them.
Then when you think the
damn stamp, okay,
the winners. So this people will get the book and now
I need to get an announcement. So this will be the announcement.
They start the windows
In this announcement, in
their score month's book.
So the author on this week is there is so much way
that is now.
So I'll add, so this way it's like attack
them. Please send me your emails in team.
So this is the usual phrase that we have when we have books from
publishers. So month's book is self published,
so that's why I need to collect these emails
myself. I think so. Um,
and you know, she will arrange the book.
So usually it's the publisher.
So thanks so much for taking part. And thank you.
So we need to take the author here and now I'm just going to
leave this and Austin and
to see I liked it there names.
Yeah, this is how I announced winners form.