Hi. So, um, I wanted to show you how to send emails through Luma.
So we use Luma remember for Project of the week.
So I wanted to show you how to send this message.
Uh, so we want to ask people who registered and participated.
We want to ask them for feedback. So I want to show you how
to do this. So go to Luma then.
Yeah, I think Luma Studio, then pastor.
Then what I do is I select the last,
um, this GitHub actions the last one.
And yeah, then I go to emails and
yeah, I think we just need to right here,
um, um,
I'll do project of the WIC GitHub
feedback project of the GitHub actions.
Something that, hi everyone.
Thanks for, for parti participating ing the projects with.
So I would like to hear in as well,
uh, release a fill out this feedback form.
Now, I don't know why it's red.
Um, you can fill it out in [Inaudible].
It will take [Inaudible] this
of your time and time
and it'll help make the future variations better,
future projects better.
Thank you. So now let me fix grammar.
Um,
so something like that. Hey everyone, thanks a lot for participating in,
In our project of the week about it
help actions.
I would like
To
Get your input. So yeah,
probably if this text just, uh, I'll send it,
uh, to you too. So for feedback it'll probably be the same text,
but in general, like if we need to send something,
uh, to all the participants,
this is how I do this now.
Let me double check that. Uh,
okay. Okay.
Yeah, . Anyways,
it'll take five minutes. Thank you.
Okay, now it's not
a link. Should be a link. Okay,
now, yeah, now it's a link. Just let
me make sure the link works.
Okay. So now just sent,
yep. So this is how we sent emails.