No, I want it to talk a bit about event.
So here, actually, I dunno for some
reasons and brought me in LinkedIn,
but the, the flow is usually, um,
before announcing the winners, like at 10 on Friday,
I contact the author and they ask the one or the author or
the authors, if they want to select the winners themselves,
or I should pick them randomly in this case,
actually, if I go to your secure,
drop me in LinkedIn, not in slack in a way I usually slack.
So yeah, she said, is it chosen by randomly?
Or they selected, so actually selected
the winners himself. So we should ask the authors if they
want to do this. And if they see that random is fine,
and then you coachable that procedure that you did for
this, in this case as well. Right? So you select,
um, yeah, but we need to ask the authors and
then I make this announcement for the winners.
Um, and then after that, I say that,
please send me your emails in text messages,
and I will pass them to here to me.
Uh, but let's say this book course with pact,
I will dry, uh, or with some other publisher that would write something
like, uh,
let me just scroll past them and
they will show the book.
Uh, I'm not sure if I mentioned that in the previous video,
I just wanted to make sure you will know it. And then now they
start sending me their emails.
So for that tank or fuel our schedules in
this spreadsheet, we have these,
uh, yeah,
look up the week emails and here for this week,
I need to add. And he says,
uh,  learning.
Yeah. And I need to take the names of the winners without the ad.
Um, so that was,
yeah. Oops. So
now they start sending me the emails.
So for example, uh,
Allie sent me the email,
sent the mail, so then angle here and then check out Kim,
this is Holly here.
I can flip your case. And then I acknowledge same
thing. Then Dustin
also wrote me, Dustin's
email here as well. I also
wrote his email
And, and do I have any other emails?
So from doing,
And then we also need email from,
I don't know how to pronounce this actually,
but what I also do because you see,
I have emails of other people. So what I can do is control the
controller and check if this person already one before
and the fee already provided their email.
So in this case they didn't, for example,
if this was, um, DDM,
then I would sometimes write to William saying,
Hey, I got your email. If it hasn't changed that we'll just use the
same one. Yeah. So this email is still pending.
And after I have all five emails,
I will pop it down and send them to the author,
the publisher. So maybe I will record the secrets
email for that. Okay. So this is how we collect emails.
So we notice for the book of the week about.