The announcement about the book was published.
It was published for some reasons it's this
thing here, even the way I ask it to.
So I review,
so it looks a bit cleaner and yeah,
of course this, uh, uh, the most important thing,
but it goes at a freestyle,
so people can start asking questions after I make announcements.
And then usually I remove the preview it later,
and I'm also making an announcement. So clicking on this share
message. Think peers.
Yeah. When you just hover over the message to share message,
then I see channel announcement and then join
the week
or so sometime
in course, two announcement.
Yeah. So this is how I post the announcement.
So people know about the week. Think not everyone knows about this because
you see somebody 3000 people,
not 12,000. So it's Miami it's announcement and now people
will see it and they send us mail or some questions.