Okay. Just wanted to show you the difference between workshops and seminars,
some workshops, concerts. Um,
I think the difference here is not between workshops and webinars,
but an event we sponsor.
There is an extract that I usually once
don't have. So, um,
I'm in, um, Eventbrite event right now.
And if I go to options and order form,
Since there are some custom fields with some custom things that we add to
the forum, when people sign up for the event and usually the
think we'll have is do you want to subscribe to data talks,
newsletter and receive updates about new treatments?
So these are lands, have this Bent,
um, sponsored ones.
They have Options and torture for Sponsors.
So This other thing,
what do you like to share your email with ThoughtSpot? Our sponsor?
The thing is that a, this event is not sponsored,
but since you quoted from the sponsor from the workshop,
Yeah, it hasn't been, so that's why we need to remove it and
Yeah, no, it's gone. Um,
so this one is on data monitoring with biologics piece
Cert. So that's why we're here.
And we think we'll be there. This is something I
didn't mention to you. This one,
I, the machine learning pipelines with Kendra is not sponsored.
So this is a workshop it from a workshop.
So this is fine. And just to mention,
you
Need to go on to actually from the workshop, but we check the duration.
Yeah. What's it been going on to order options?
Yeah. We still have this, then this thing here,
would you like to share your email with us? So we don't need that
Because this is not as possible. Um,
This,
Okay, so this one is sponsored and the ones
This.
So let me make it clear for you, which one is sponsored.
So this one sponsor,
Um,
This one is sponsored
And
This one is sponsored. So now you will know that,
um, usually these workshops are sponsored.
So now you will know that these things,
you need to go on it. Other, another sponsored event,
which is duplicated workshop. Um,
next time, when they asked you to schedule a sponsored event,
I will make sure that I mentioned that the
sponsor.