Hi. So yeah, talking, um,
about Taylor. So I asked,
um, not to do it yourself. I wanted to show you,
show you how to do this. So go to LinkedIn.
I have his profile. He actually accepted my invitation sometime ago.
So just find him, Taylor.
All good. So I'll get his profile
and then I will go to our,
um, air table.
We have this sponsorship CRM there,
and I'll just open it, uh,
sponsorship, CRM contacts and
mm, you actually, you already edited this,
right? So he's,
uh, called, uh,
because I already contacted him, but it's,
it was a call email, so nobody introduced me to to him.
Um, so it was just, uh, I found him,
I sent him a connection request. Actually let me open it here.
So I sent him a connection request, uh,
um, on September 18th.
I don't know why there is too.
Can I,
This weird. Should be just one.
I will, I cannot remove it.
Okay, well what's going on?
Okay, so we already have,
have him and the last time connected was yesterday.
So let's just go here and we
select the date from yesterday. Um,
then status of the company.
Yeah, we don't have any status here.
Um, we don't know this one,
this one. And uh,
so I will also go here and I will say,
so I usually just write, sent a connection request
and then here in the comments it shows where was it done,
where the connection request was done. So for example,
for this year, uh, we can see for Yearon the comment
was done 12 days ago on September 30.
Right. So we know when we sent the connection,
Um, yeah, but here I can edit it.
Can edit it, send the connection request on September,
uh, when was it?
September 18th.
And yeah, so we was the last contact and we were just waiting
for him to check and he didn't seem to like usually,
for example, um, let me check it.
No, we don't, I'm just trying to see how
we can see that they saw the message.
Cause now we can see that it was sent,
but I don't know if what it was actually a received.
I,
Yeah, probably it doesn't show this information,
but at least, uh, yeah, at least, at least it was
sent. Okay. I'm really worried about this duplicate.
Um, but yeah, I think it's fine.
So what else did I want to show you here?
Yeah, the sponsorships here. There was another woman I talked,
he, so is from Varu.
So let me add here to,
Um,
LinkedIn. Then your name is this
one.
Um,
Account executive. Usually.
Account executive is somebody from sales. So this is not a super relevant role,
but she invited me to some LinkedIn group and they thought since she initiated
the contact, I would, uh, pitch back and say,
Hey, like there is this nice community that you can sponsor.
So the company is for our room,
so somebody will already have them.
Good. And wondering why for like,
uh, what kind of contact
we had with them. Was there some,
I'm just wondering, uh, was there some content that we,
Okay, nevermind. So the company is already there.
Last content contact was,
let's say today. Um,
I don't have your email yet. And lead status,
let's say, um,
contacted, she's kind of still called,
but, uh, hm. I'm still trying to figure out
what's the best way to think about this.
Um, this lead status. Um,
so let me just show you what we have here. So prospect is when
we, um,
Uh, prospect is when we just add them to,
um, this spreadsheet to,
to this table. And then maybe we all sent a connection request
in, uh, in,
in LinkedIn, but nothing else. So they're potentially interesting.
Cold is when we contact them, but it was,
it was a called outreach.
So we don't know them. Nobody introduced us to them.
And uh, yeah, so we just found them on LinkedIn and wrote them a
message. Then contacted,
I think, yeah, it's kind of not needed because it's the same as called
Hot is, uh, when somebody introduced us to them.
Or for example, um, if I go on a conference and
meet somebody. So then we already have,
uh, established contact. So then it would be a follow up from the conference.
It would be already hot lit, uh,
proposed is, uh, when we talked and when we had,
um, on discussion.
And then I sent them an offer saying that,
uh, this is what we can do and this is how much it costs,
then it's proposed and then deal if we they agree and
then introduce colleagues. So oftentimes, uh,
we talk not to the right people.
So for example, this, he, he,
yeah, he probably is,
uh, not the right person because she's,
um, account executive. She's not in marketing.
She's not in partnership, right.
So probably, um, she does not own the budget for marketing,
but if, um, she can introduce us to her colleagues,
uh, who are in marketing, who are in partnership management,
then, um, yeah,
then I, It's good.
And we can just change, introduce colleague and then we can,
uh, link who is the colleague or just add the colleague here and then
write and comments that it was introduced by he.
So this is what happened, uh, here,
uh, with, um, let me see.
It was a company, um,
Snow Plow. Yeah. So then I met Jordan at
the conference and then she introduced me to Eddie.
And then, uh, we already started talking,
um, with Eddie, but yeah,
I actually need to follow up with him.
Yeah, that's, uh, the table contacts in the sponsorship
serum and when we find people in,
uh, LinkedIn that we want to contact.
So we just add them as prospect.
We sent them a connection request and then,
uh, yeah, we add a note when the connection request was sent.
And yeah, that's pretty much it.
Okay. That's all for this one for.