Um, hi, I just wanted to show you another website where we can share
stuff. It's called data towel.net.
So in Datatel, so I already logged in,
you can create your own user here then
here in Datatel. Let me in the larger,
good little bit. So click submit. And then here you can say,
like, for example, for any events that we have,
for example, if we have events, teaching data engineers,
you can ups, you can write teaching
data engineers, um,
uh, hopefully being our, or so,
um, let me think what we can say it's podcast and through you cast
interview data talks go up right on down.
Euro would be this link,
right? So this is how you can, uh,
create things, submit things on data.
So we can try that maybe for a couple of months and see if
it works. Okay.