So I've been working on this tool that can edit podcasts
for us so we don't need to rely on freelancers and
this is how it works so I will send this link I will add
it to loom and then here again it also works
through GitHub actions like other things we have have used before
so you go to actions and here we have two
actions first is submit and then the second so check to submit
is what we use and check is automatic but we can also trigger it
so the way it works is we use an external service for creating a
transcript uh and these transcripts are not
really good we need to edit them later so first
i'll show you how to submit a transcript job so i click
here run workflow and we select
the video we want to transcribe so this would be a podcast episode uh
let's see uh yeah so i wanted to take this one
with savina right so now we are interested in
this id that goes after e and for this
so basically this part everything going that goes uh between v and this
ampersand this is what we're interested in right so we can check if
this is the right one by using this url without anything
just a question mark v equals and then oops putting
the id there right so this should work still okay
it works and now i again i am here actions
i select submit transcribe job i click on run workflow run
workflow and put the idea here and then i click run what
will happen is actually i run it already let me do it for another
one but i want to continue all it already finished so i want to
show using this example but let me also do it with another
one so let's say
we want to take um i'll just take some so
one i'm just thinking which one did i not because i did some experiments
and already uh processed i think this one ones so
uh let's take this one with daniel
again we're interested only in the part after b so
i put the id here and click run run workflow right
now it will appear here okay so it
appears here uhm and then yeah it
does some technical things well at the And it should success,
succeed out.
Let's just put it on pause for now and then let's wait till it
finishes. Okay, it took some time,
so it finished. Now I go again back to
the repo. And what happens is
it creates a file here in the jobs directory.
So this is technical, we don't need to know what exactly it is here,
this is some technical information,
but the fact is that we should have a file,
podcast, miners, and the idea of the thing that we want
to transcribe, right? And now there is another action.
Right now, we just submitted a job and then in the background,
the transcribed transcription. will happen,
right? And then this submit transcribe job runs periodically,
like every 5 to 10 minutes, maybe like every 20 minutes.
Uhm. I don't know, well,
it runs periodically, right?
So what can happen is maybe you submit it,
then you can uhm do some other things.
Then maybe in 10 minutes,
uh, it should run, uh,
it should run automatically, if it does not,
because it sometimes may take longer, like after 10 minutes,
the transcription should be on. So you can go
and click on this check transcribe jobs,
run workflow, again run workflow. And now it will use this file,
this json file that we created previously.
It created automatically this with some technical information.
In order to check the status of the transcription okay
let's see if it run anything so
um yeah we can see that this is uh is still in progress
right so I'll put it on pause give it some time and come back
like in five to ten minutes and then we'll see what to
do after that okay hopefully enough time has passed
let me see what happened uh so it was still a manual job that
I run so it didn't run the scheduled job
um so what I can do now is try to run it one more
time one more time so run workflow and
then let's see see what happens there
should be here we go so we just check
again the same like this one is not interesting uh
let me just collapse it so this this one is interesting so
it says that transcription it uh transcript saved to
this directory right so now this is the location where
it's saved let me copy paste it to my clipboard
now i go here transcripts
row and this is i just use search and
this is now we can also see that it is updated now right so
this is the transcription and
this transcription is not really good so we need to edit it and
for that i have a prompt for charge bt uh
so this is the prompt so there are multiple options prompts here we are
interested in the first one and we will probably keep updating
this prompt so i create a new chat
and here we need to uh replace a few things so
there are placeholders first guest name i think it was
uh
daniel right um the one so
let's put his name here guest name is
daniel and here we take the entire document
that we uh prepared and
put it here questions right and
now we execute that so
now it says okay i'm ready to edit the transcript so this is the
transcript all and i'll just copy the entire transcript
i actually haven't tried to run the entire transcript let's see
what happens before i did this in chunks uhm
but let's see, okay
so typically yeah
we're not really interested in that part so we start from
from this one right um and okay I'll let
it finish so I'll put it on pause right now and I
don't know how long it will take um but let's wait okay
now you see it stopped generating so it did not take finish and then
it offers me continue generating so I just click on that and
now it continues yeah so probably
it will finish soon so it of course we would we gave it a
lot of text so that's why it takes a bit of time uh
to to do that what I did in my past previous experiments is
I took it in chunks of 10 minutes so let's say I go to
I don't know 15 minutes maybe up to to
that point doesn't matter right so I take chunks and then I feed it
chunk by chunk so if in the future um
it happens that ChargerBT cannot take the entire thing we can split it into
chunks and do that okay so it finished
now uh I go here and copy
it I will create a new file uh
so we can call it like do we have a place where we store
transcripts maybe we do but we'll see transcript daniel
we can also put season name and episode name whatever
I don't remember which one and I copy the entire thing here or I
use ctrl um edit paste without
formatting right this is not
uhm yet ready ok so first I
remove the intro ok this week ok
apart from that we don't need to do any editing this is not ready
yet where is the name script
daniel uh something like that okay
it's saved um it's not ready yet i will record another video
of how to finish it what okay
um so we still need to add a few touches it's
almost ready uh we uh remember in what Pavel says
do we have uh his transcripts okay
so in his transcripts what he also makes is he
adds these captions right there for each chapter there is a caption so
this is what we will do next I don't have a video yet so
I will prepare uh that and we'll share it with you too but this
is how we create uh this is how we submit a transcript job this
is how we get the results and this is how we edit
the results with chargebt and by the way one thing i did not mention
that the file remember we had here this jobs
uh one of the jobs this json file with daniel's podcast it's
gone so after it successfully processes it it removes that
from this jobs directory and it places © The Bulletproof 2013 transcript in
the role folder okay so that's uh
the main part i would say now we just need to i'll just need
to figure out how to add um captions the titles for sections
and then from that we will be able to create the same documents
in the same format as pavel creates so then we will be able to
use it for the rest of the flow that we have so yeah,
see you around