So I just noticed that this URL does not work and
the reason for that is that we forgot to put the right link.
Things happens, but Yeah, of course you need to be more you
need to pay more attention to detail. You know that So next time please
add this to one of the things to the this document where you
keep track of things to watch out for Anyways,
so this is actually fixable so I already sent this e-mail to the
in the e-mail to Elisabetta but actually it does
not work cause the real URL is this one we
forgot to update it and uhm
so the way I found out is I went to all campaigns in MailChimp
so this is all campaigns then I go to uhh
it was in March, right?
so I find one in weird where
is the one in March?
should be somewhere here it's
weird
meh meh meh uh ah k
Yeah, so I think this is this one 4th of March Right,
so this is the campaign This is 4th of
March And this is the campaign.
So I go to details, and this is the link that we've updated.
It's actually still editable So we can write 103,
160, and now it works.
So if we forgot to update the URL and send the campaign anyways
it's still possible to update it. Now I also want you to go through
all the campaigns that we have here and check that
all the links are work. And if they do not,
update them using what I just showed. And of course we need to create
a process document just in case it happens again.