What was already in our,
um, he was on our events.
He showed up, he asked to modify his biography.
So did it company. Okay.
Yeah. So you sent a new biography.
So I want to show you how to got to get up and
down. Actually, it shouldn't be up.
And then I select this data docs,
club, guitar player. And this year we
have this underscore people and we need to find the
ranch. So he wanted to change
his biography. It could,
and I had a place in these things that we'll have here with a
new one. It'd be Atlanta
breaks if you land breaks here. Okay.
So this is his new meal. Oh,
can be changes. And in a while,
if we'd gone to actions,
so now this thing will, is cured,
but someone, it will push an updated version to,
to our website. So that's all.