Hi. So I noticed that in most documents that we have,
uh, for podcast, so it seems like instead of using a line
break, uh, instead of just heating enter,
you do shift enter. So these are two different things.
Uh, so let me show you why it matters. So when I click on
this thing, you see the entire paragraph is selected.
Mm. So here it thinks that this is the entire paragraph.
So when you do, um,
shift enter, it keeps it as one paragraph,
right? And when you just do enter, it's a different paragraph.
So you see when I double click on this, this thing is not selected
anymore. So we need to split these things into multiple paragraphs.
So let me actually do this now. And then you see when I just
double click on this, I select only this sentence,
this paragraph. And here, yeah,
the entire thing is selected. So typically I need to redo
this. And then I thought, Okay, like maybe I should just record,
record the video where I show you how I want you to do this.
So please just use simple enter.
And then again, I think I mentioned that, um,
when something does not make sense,
not grammatically, but uh, you know,
from the common sense point of view,
like I know you are having now.
Like it doesn't make any sense, right?
So in this case, maybe heaven is not the right word,
right? So maybe in this case, uh,
that would've been nice. Uh, if you can just,
uh, you know, highlight it, it's not a problem.
I fix it. Um, but yeah,
like sometimes before the interview starts,
I forget to check the document and then it might be confusing for the
guest, um, what we mean here.
Okay, Here, uh, let me,
it enters again.
So you see, this is how I check if this is the,
the right line break. You see now?
Yeah, it's select everything.
Yeah.
And the last one. Okay,
cool. I think now is good.
So please, uh, just the process document that we haven't mentioned,
what kind of line breaks should be there when you put,
um, the content, uh, when
you put the content of this document, uh, for this podcast document.
And in general, like unless you have a reason to use,
uh, shift, don't use it.