That's that we use for our events.
So now I want to show you how, instead of, so previously we were
using for doing this.
So maybe you remember, I showed it in one of the previous videos plots.
Yeah.
Yeah. So this firm, this is what we used to previously.
Now we'll have, um,
templates. So now I want to show you how to actually do this in
a new template. So we use Figma for that.
Now we have this event banner thing,
which we need to change. And so they
went with is a lot testing microservices.
, let's change this. Um,
this is quite large title.
So let me and do something
like this. And then we say,
why is it? Oops,
microservices or robustness,
scalability. And we
can just be Kenny part of the title.
Then we pick this one and microservices and
change the form to this blue one.
So it looks a bit nicer than the name of the speaker.
We need to also change. So previously we didn't have the name of a
speaker on the banner.
Now we need to change that. So the name is,
and my nail and
update is here, and then we need to change that.
U-turn. So to change the picture,
just go to speaker,
um,
yeah, it's a big kind of person photo and yeah,
yeah, yeah. It's a two,
this photo control these year.
So we go here and then there's this few image and click on this
and they choose a different image. And then we have all the images in
our GitHub. Repo could be other place right now,
all the images. They have, all the images there,
certainly the sort of data docs club, GitHub, IO.
Then we have even just folder then.
Um, and then here I type in,
uh, and then it can cope and
then we'll have a picture here,
close it. And this is the amount of,
of her. Um, and now I just
click here and
then at the bottom here,
I click expert, but mother saved
and see here.
Um, I think I want to change it slightly.
You will probably not need to do this.
I will do it now. And then,
uh, you will eat, will be adjusted.
So you want to move it a bit,
so it's like  yeah.
Yeah. So properly centered.
I think we sort of
sought proper decent there. Okay.
No,
no. Okay. So you will want me to do this.
You will just need to change the title to picture and right.
And different in the future. I want to write a script that will generate
this. So you will not need to worry about that. This is what we
have. So now that likes sports
and now I use this for creating an event.
So this flow you already saw,
let me just quickly not go into details,
but just want to remind your car exactly.
To, uh, uh, chop this.
Okay. So we already have spoken the relationship something.
So now I click copy.
And then now that the title there,
I'll just copy it across. Yeah. And
yes.
And somebody, sometimes I need to think,
because I didn't prepare this lesbian.
Look at the outline. E
S
I think something like
a lot,
something like this, I don't know. I just came up with this.
You will not need to do this. You will probably have a subtitle or
ready. This is something I should have asked this speaker and the guest.
Now the date is actually
next week is the date
is also Tuesday. So start.
And then the staff time on time is not changed.
Could prevent
no it's created, they call to details.
And I LD that image.
Look at this new banner and here it,
this is how we'll do this at your order. So the rest of the
form, um, one thing though,
that was different,
um, boundless. So for events.
So this is for events and like,
this is for webinars and this farm for different.
Okay, nevermind. We can just use this for everything.
And then maybe that will update this instruction,
uh, to tell you what executives do. But for now,
this is how you use Figma to create even.