Um, K if you comments about the,
the, the podcast document we create.
So usually we already know what we talk about and all the topics.
So this X you need to replace with recruiting lead engineers,
the topic we have the special guests today.
So we already know who the guest is.
And, um, uh, yeah, it's also his name.
Then also this X is the,
basically the same thing. Cause here.
Yeah.
And beyond by this is something that Nicholas needs to put in title
we're ordering and all the title, including the engineers with
this one, the titles, not clear position, digital subtitle.
We need to think about this, but usually the format for that is subtitle
some subtitle then minus that it's happened.
And then the, the full name of the guest.
So it shouldn't be like that. So when you create a document at the
very least, you can already feel that and that,
and that, and the set up, because now you can also put the title
here and this thing and this and
other things. Yeah. Thanks a lot for converting my handwriting into proper text.
You don't need to put numbers here. They're there.
So yeah.