uh so we have this new article by Valeria,
a guide to free online courses. And here we have this table
with information about the courses, right?
And here in particular what is interesting right now is the starting date
of the next cohort, which quite,
which changes over time,
right? And I now noticed a mistake here,
so I wanted to fix it, and I also wanted to show you how
to change it later,
let's say when we run this course.
For the next time, this course, this course,
and so on. So we wouldn't, we would need to change it,
so I want to show it how to find it, so for that we
need, we go to our repo,
website repository, we go to Boston.
And we go to this article,
so this is the, this article,
Guide to Free Online Courses at Data Talks Club.
All right, and you probably know,
we click edit, and this course.
mess is the table that we saw.
So what we need to find here is this,
this is what we want to change, Machine Learning Zoom Camp,
and we need to update it. Actually,
it was right, it was September 2024. Of course,
this is now 2024, um so actually I don't need to change
it, but uh yeah,
yeah, so this was right, but now you know how to,
if we needed to change it here to 2025,
this is how we do this. And then we click and it changes,
right. And my mistake,
uh yeah, we don't need to change it,
but yeah, so this is how we update the,
this article.