Hi, so I wanted to show you how to check if I
can do a podcast on Monday.
In general, I want to show you how things are organized
in my calendar. So now you have access to my calendar.
You should be able to edit everything there and see what is there.
So I wanted to show you an example when I cannot do a podcast
at the usual time. So this is the usual time for the podcast.
It's happening. It's 5 p.m.
So this is my time, brilliant time, 5 p.m.
And I already have this event block.
So it happens. I have the block on every Monday,
so it's always there. So this is just to make sure that people do
not accidentally put anything there or,
um, look allenly.
Okay, so here next week I'm busy. And by the
way, yeah, we need to just get all that to noon,
for example. Okay,
so here the block is there.
It's always there. But I have another event there.
So this is the event. That's why I cannot make,
cannot do a podcast on this time.
So you should be able to see this, and you should be able to
see if I can do on this Monday at this time.
So by default, we should try to do this. What should be the default
time is Monday,
5pm. Like previously it was Friday, 5pm.
Yeah, but if I already have something in my calendar, then we should try
to maybe have it on Tuesday.
If there is nothing on Tuesday or no.
So Tuesday would be preferred if the speaker can.
And not do it in the morning or in the at noon.
Because at noon, uh, yeah,
like let's say if they are from Central European time,
then noon should be fine. But if they are from the States,
they can not do it at noon. So then we can try to find
it Tuesday. And then on other days I am not available.
And uh,
yeah, here is another example where,
uh, so here, this is an event, right? So,
let's make something. And here is another example where I cannot,
um, I cannot do it on Monday
15th, right? Then we will need to schedule the broadcast at some other time.
So this is the after how it works. You should be able to have
access to this if you don't let me know. So this is my Gmail
account. And yeah,
so this is how you can see.