I just realized we might not have instructions about adding
videos not from our channel to the playlist.
So if this is a video we want to add to the playlist,
to the Data Engineering Zoom Cam playlist, but it's not our channel.
And you probably know how to do this, but just for the sake of
completeness and we also can create a process document for that.
I want to show you how to do this. We click save here and
then we select which playlist we want to save and then it's
date engineer. And then like as I asked you in
telegram we also need to put it in the right location so then we
you know how to do this we should already have process document for that
you would need to. Yeah,
so that's how you add a video from different channels to our playlist.