Here. I want to show how to add timestamps,
uh, chapters,
uh, time codes to any YouTube video.
So speaker guest for one of our events.
So he, I asked him to prepare a timestamps,
uh, 10 quotes for the video.
So he sent the video. So let me know from the video where we
want to . So I go to YouTube studio,
then it is content.
So this is the, this video is this open source spotlight or cast.
So, uh, he did this presentation and then he prepared
the time codes. So now we need to put these timecards there.
So the times called 10 quads, he prepared are not,
uh, this is, uh, the format is slightly different,
so I'll need to adjust it slightly. So we only need the beginning.
We do not need the end. So now I will need to remove to
the end.
So I don't anymore. Would I use a feature from visual
studio code called multiple or serve?
You don't have to use this. You maybe can digitally by a one by
one, whatever is convenient for you.
And yeah, so I think this time codes,
uh, I'm good enough. So now I just copy this,
um, based this to the video in that click save,
and now let's check that it actually works so I could hear
it's nice to meet you as well.
And we see that, uh, it edit this chapters production pipeline
demo and so on because we edit them here.
The important thing here, this, the first timestamp,
the first time code should always start with 0, 0 0 0 0 0 time.
Otherwise YouTube will not pick this as chapters.
Um, yeah. So this is how you add 10 codes to a YouTube video.