Hi. Yeah, I wanted to show you another example of,
uh, sponsored content. So this content is actually,
um, so Santiago is,
um, it's called Influencer Marketing.
So he, they paid him to,
I assume they paid him because this is like a company,
right? So this is, um, a workshop and he's promoting,
so I assume they paid Santiago to do this.
Um, so this is the company Abacos ai,
so I think I already added them.
Um, yeah, influencer marketing.
See, so this is, um, let me open it here.
So this is the name of the event,
right? And then this is a link to the tweet to Santiago's
post on social media, right? Then,
um, sort of then,
yeah, that type is event source influencer marketing.
So this is not a paid in the sense that sometimes when
you, I don't know if he used Twitter sometimes,
let me just open, uh, my home feed.
So on Twitter there is, um,
inorganic promotion. So if I scroll,
Yeah, you see this is promoted content,
right? Sometimes some of this content is also relevant for us for later talk
club. Um, so this is like,
uh, paid promotion, but here they didn't pay Twitter.
They paid Sango to post it,
um, to post it on his,
um, in his Twitter account,
right? So then it's influencer marketing.
So relevancy, again, medium. I already add a ba ai and then,
uh, yeah, I didn't put any comments here,
so I sometimes may send you, Okay,
look, this influencer is promoting this company,
and then you can just add link here.
Yeah, that's how you add, uh,
influencer marketing content to,
to this serum.