Hi, I wanted to show you two transcripts,
two pages that are already created.
So for example, for this, for data science,
from the science and data engineering, public was a bit late because he was
moving countries. So he just sent this transcript.
So let me just, uh, show you how to,
Uh, to process this. So I first am done unloading this as
Microsoft docs. Now let me open it.
And by the way, I want
to,
At this point, so,
because Powell sounded, I need to say that it's done,
But this is not what I wanted to show you. Um,
yeah, so I downloaded it. Let me to name it.
I also want to quickly check what is the season seven episode
eight season seven,
episode eight. And,
uh, Of course from the
S E D S do You
just the short and now what we do is,
uh, Applaud to that and get that you
remember This transcript,
Um, and then just
a file, Upload it.
Okay. It is committed. Now we see,
or sometimes there is a delay,
but we see that now that is a check.
We go to action and to see now it is being executed.
Sometimes these things might turn with one minute delay or something
here. We got lucky. It was executed immediately.
You see, it's already a green check,
So it would go to a transcript.
So we're not interested where actually we'll also need to think what's right.
So I know we need this one.
Um, this one goes to YouTube To
you. You already know that Because he already so hard to do this.
Um, yeah,
this one and it's
Okay,
But this is not the main thing I wanted to show you because I
show you sound speeds. And these big coming from
dating, saying science, debate engineering.
So now let me crawl and then I will just click Selecto.
Can I do this? Well, we'll just do control a to select all you
see, I selected the entire thing,
So I copy. And now I go to,
Um, a website, the website,
I go to podcasts, And
then you find the podcast. So remember,
this is a season seven,
episode eight. So we find season
seven, episode eight from data science, data engineering.
And I click this pencil, this pile,
And just then I take this thing
that I copied. So I press control and now
I'm press paste and just to control it.
So it basically,
I couldn't come in changes.
No, this should update the website.
So, you know, it has been executed. So in a minute,
we should have the transcript.
Okay. Say this already. Let me just,
I'm just checking that the chapters and the chapters
are here, but of course in this,
Yeah, it is still being executed, man.
Mentor finish.
Well, it's doing this. Let me open this page and then
I'll just finish it. What cost they
spawn
It is being deployed.
Yeah. Okay.
Now we'll have transcript. So this is how we add transcripts to,
um, To a podcast event page
that we already have existing.
So this is called.