Hi. So, um, thanks for,
oh, what's going on? So thanks for preparing this link,
um, in Luma. So I wanted to show you what to do next with
this, uh, link to Luma. I already showed you this project of
the week thing. So this is the, the week,
and I just sent you an and white this thing here.
So please accept the invite. Once you do this,
you will be able to edit things here, and then you will just need
to click on this, uh,
pen pencil. And then now we will need to add
this link to the button. So here, this is the button.
This one is the button. So we need to replace this to do with,
oh, the first thing of, to do. And then put the link there and
yeah, that's how you put the link to this project of week.
And now let's check it. So now I click on this and we get
to this page. So next time when I send you this page,
you can create an event Luma, and immediately edit this and
add the link to the event you just created.
Okay.