Hello. Yeah, so I noticed the,
I don't think we add links to YouTube.
Um, like for example, this was Tomash with Tomic,
like we don't have YouTube link.
So I think it would be a good idea to actually not forget adding
this link. So for example,
for Andre, Okay,
this is not the link. Okay,
so just do this.
Right? So then it's just simpler. And let's say if I want to go
and edit it, I just click here and then I
go to edit it. So I don't need to find it.
It's, it's there. Another thing I wanted to ask you is,
um, right now the interface here is different.
So they changed. Okay. This one is, uh,
being processed. Let me, let me take another one.
So maybe I don't know this one I will not edit
it of course, but till when we do trim,
you see, Oh, oops, sorry. So when we do,
I'll go back.
So when I, when I click it and trim
and cut, you see that there is this, uh,
new thing that we can just, oops. Uh,
where it is.
Ah, right. So it's here. So I think they were,
the way to get it is we go to Editor Dream.
It should appear here. Oh, I don't,
I don't know why it's not appearing. Maybe I just need to refresh
that. You probably know what I mean. Like that there is this,
uh, bar that we can,
uh, just, uh, move.
Ah, yeah. Here it is. Right. So then it's usually just,
uh, you know, moving it here.
So maybe you can, um, show it.
Uh, let me make sure I don't accidentally say it.
Maybe you can update the process doc, because I remember previously it was different.
Okay. And, um, , that's whole.
And I will record another video now.