Okay. Another thing I wanted to show you, um,
is, uh, companies who sponsor conferences.
So typically if a company is sponsoring a conference,
then they might also consider a sponsor in our community.
So there is a conference called Data Natives and they have a bunch of
sponsors. And for this,
uh, oops. Um,
so they have a page, special page with, uh,
sponsors Go
Away.
I come back. Okay. Um,
so they have some sponsors here,
right? Um, Diamond Partners,
uh, whatever. And uh,
yeah, so I wanted to get some of them that are relevant for us.
So for example, uh,
I don't know, quick maybe is relevant.
So we can, uh, let's add them.
So I will just go and add here.
Date, uh, natives 2002 conference.
So here Link would be, I don't know,
just this one. This one.
Then, uh, so that's product service.
They are, yeah,
it's actually, I have confidence sponsorship, right?
A special, like a separate category for this.
And then, so this one, Data natives was an offline event.
So the category, category is confidence event offline.
Then relevance is, um,
I don't know if they're super relevant. Um,
I think if something is high relevant, uh,
relevancy, then I will edit here is high.
Okay. And then the company I wanted to add is this Quicks,
Let me check the spelling.
Quicks,
How do I, It's like capital and X.
So I don't have, I don't think we have them quicks.
So let's add anyone, right?
And uh, comment is they are a diamond partner.
So this, uh, what kind of partner they are,
what kind of sponsorship package they have might be important because actually for data
natives, I know how much it costs them to,
to do this. So that helps.
And then maybe what you can do now is,
uh,
this sap, I don't know what Persis,
SAP amplitude,
uh, native, what is it?
Blockchain? No,
Native, Uh, what is that
Also
Not interesting. And ibm.
So this two sap, uh,
amplitude, ibm. So Amplitude,
uh, maybe elements.
And this ones are like medium relevance.
This one, I don't know. What is that? Yeah,
I think I checked that. So you can add them.
And the way you do this is,
uh, because we already have this thing, right? So we can just duplicate records.
And then here, instead of Quicks,
you add, uh, I b M,
right? IBM again,
not here. And what kind of partner?
They're just partner.
Partner,
Right? So then you will need to let me remove copy here.
So then you'll need to do this for SAP and
uploaded the rest.
I don't think they're super other one. Okay.
Yeah.
Let me just check what, what do we have here?
Yeah, I think that's all for this. So I will sometimes send you conferences
and we'll say, Okay, like, these companies seem relevant.
Please put them in the, in this thing,
in this table.