So I thought it's faster if I just record the video about that
So we go to
Why it's here anyways
How to make it go away Okay,
um So we go to data So
first of all what I want to show you is how to add two
people in one event, right?
So we have this events.yaml and the way it works is we
uhm when you fill a form there is only one field for adding an
author So let's say we,
right now what I will do is I will just remove
this thing So this is what happens when
you create an event through the form,
right? So a record like that is added to events.yaml So
if you want to add a second person here,
what you do is you click edit in the same way I clicked here
right now and then you add the second name here,
right? So this person should be added too through the form and
yeah that's pretty much it so you just add another person here,
commit changes and now I hope
this is the right one, let me check
yeah no, so this one is the right one,
so let me update it,
okay yeah, so this is
how we do it, and please find,
I think there must be a process document for that,
if not, let's create it.