Um, Hey, I just want to make it easier to find documents.
So here in this schedule document,
we can add a link. So just click on this insert link or,
And then I think it doing suggests to find it,
but if it doesn't then you know where to find them,
right.
And then we have these things here. So it suggests to Use
this link. So we'll just apply This
way. We'll have links for that's pretty convenient.
Sure. Actually,
I wanted to ask you to feel the same for everyone,
but it seems to be so easy that it's just faster for me to
do this. Just press control key, and then for others,
it doesn't. Yeah.
So this way it's simpler to,
To do this and they wanted to ask you to add,
this is another step in the some process document,
Um, that we need to, once we create this document,
uh, this podcast document, we also link it in the data.
Docs stops Cato.