And here we have an example of a paid promotion on LinkedIn.
So you see this is a company data stacks,
and you see that this content is promoted and it appears in
my feed. And so they are advertising the book,
Cassandra, the Definit, the definitive guide.
So I would typically copy link to this post and send it to you.
So for you, when I share this link,
you will not see it as promoted, right?
Because it was promoted in my feed. Um,
but yeah, this is, uh, promoted stuff,
right? So here, if we fill this in,
um, this, uh, crm,
so I think I already have them. Let me quickly check,
uh, cause um, there are, yeah,
so we already have them. So let me just show you how I did
this. So I, this is the title of the book,
then the link. I think this is the same content.
Yeah, I think it's, it's actually the same link that I,
uh, put before. So content type is ebook,
because this is an ebook, right?
And then source LinkedIn. This is LinkedIn,
right? The source is LinkedIn. And if it was a paid promotion on Twitter,
then the source would be Twitter, right?
Then uh, the company and then comment.
So we already have data stacks and here I think that's
the only content.
Uh, we have this Cassandra,
definite definitive guide. Okay.
Yeah. So this is how you add sponsored content,
uh, promoted content from social media like Twitter and LinkedIn.