Oh, hi, sorry. I started the free trial or Trello.
So with this free trial, um,
with premium, um, we can add reminders for specific
items of in checklist like this one.
Um, like if mine two bought, they went on Wednesday.
So I said it to today because today's Wednesday before the event.
So to make sure we do not forget, um, we will do that.
Um, so for example, this one, so select winners,
so this should kept them on next Friday.
So the reminder here, and you see that there is a reminder,
so this way we do not forget to actually do this.
And I edit these things.
You see the first element of the checklist is reminders to the checklist
items and the way we will use it.
So let's say I want to create a new book
and it will be some,
some book. All right.
So this is not the real book. I just want to show you what
you need to do. The moment you create a from
the template. So you create a card and yeah,
you have this first item. What do you need to do to,
to check it is you need to set a reminder to
this one. So it will be,
let's say this is,
um, let's say if we want to do this book for I'll
take 28, March 28th
March.
So then the minder.
So if it's 28 March, so the reminder should go on 21st of March.
So this is a Wednesday before they went.
And then another reminder will be this one selected on Friday.
So on Friday or event week,
I think for this one, that's sold the ones, I think at the reminder
for the next item, we don't need this anymore.
Well, I will say the more from the template.
So for the book of the week, I think these are the two things
you need to have a reminder and
also invite the author, but something also you shouldn't do on Wednesday,
but because this thing has a reminder,
um, yeah, I think it's kind of clear that I don't think
you need to set reminders for both of these things.
Um,
Yeah, maybe this one for Monday,
maybe it's a good idea to also set the reminder.
So let's say this is 28. So basically
every thing that requires a particular Dean should have a due
date to make sure you do not forget this.
You can also assign it to yourself, for example.
Yeah. And this way we don't forget. And I think I wanted to remove
this thing that reminder.
Yeah, we do not need this because we now will be able to set
reminders for each item.
So I don't think,
and then the same thing for podcast. So let's say podcast
and this podcast is, uh,
let's say also for, uh,
I'll go with first of
All, first of all,
On some topics on guests. Okay. The card.
And then the first thing here is reminders is
a reminder,
oh, sorry. Do you mind to the guests about the event one week before
they went? So we, if this is for the 1st of April,
then we send a reminder set reminder one week before,
and then we set the mind that are one day before and
yeah, actually what else?
Um, we, we need in winder.
Yeah. Maybe after the stream, we can figure
out where exactly we need to set reminders.
Um, at least four for
these two
To make sure they don't forget. And then the same thing for the webinar.
Right? So this is, we've got these two things we need to send a
reminder one week before and one day before.
So this is what I wanted to show you. This is how we add
reminders to our Trello card.