Hi. So I wanted to talk to you about this sponsorship CRM table that
we have, an air table or database.
So here, what we do, what I do is I keep track of all
the sponsored content I see online,
like in LinkedIn and Twitter, um,
everywhere. And, um,
like an example of this would be, so for example,
when I look, um, a world of Word demos,
you see this advertisement,
right? So potentially all these companies who run their
advertisement, they could be hm,
um, potential, um,
potential sponsors for the community, right?
Um, so what I do is,
um, I capture all these content,
sponsored content in this table.
So it's called sponsored content. And then here we also have companies.
So these are the companies who, um,
who produce this sponsored content, you know.
And then, um, so here we have links. So I know that,
uh, um, so Neptune,
for example, had this sponsored content,
right? So we can link this databases,
um, we can link this, uh, um,
tables in the database,
uh, with each other, right?
Maybe platform.
Okay. So yeah,
it's, it's linkable. Did I save it or how do I save it?
Okay.
Yeah, I think it was saved. Um,
and then also we here,
so we have a list of companies and, um,
each company has a status. So Prospect is a company which we have not
yet reached out. Um,
remember I was showing you how to reach out to companies.
Um, so this companies we haven't reached out yet to then
contacted is when we reached out, but we didn't get any response back.
And established contact is when they actually replied something back and we started talking.
And then client is when they actually decided to sponsor us to pay for
a newsletter or to run, um,
a workshop with us or sponsor the community.
So for example, scale, um, we run a campaign with them like a couple
of weeks ago, maybe you remember? And,
uh, then we also have past clients. So people who are,
who were our clients, but in the past.
So perhaps we need to reestablish contact with them.
And then we have last, uh, statuses loss declined is when,
uh, yeah, when we made a suggestion,
but they, uh, made it didn't answer anything or explicitly declined the,
um, sponsor in the community. Okay, So we have that,
the sponsored content I already showed you.
Then we have contacts. So this is the information about,
uh, um, about contacts,
about people who we talk to.
So like, I actually need to populate this more,
like, to add more data. I will probably ask,
uh, for your help with this.
Um, yeah. And then finally deals is,
uh, when we actually managed to somehow close,
like with, who was it? So here maybe I will add,
um, uh, mines to be workshop,
right? So the type would be workshop,
then company would be mines db and
contact would be Costa I an execution date.
Was it, um, last week?
Oops,
let me check. Yeah, it was six days ago.
What's the date? So September 21.
So would be September 21,
right? Um, yeah,
so this is called like CRM or client Relationship
Management. I think it stands for that.
Um, or customer relationship management. So here,
um, so I just want to keep track of,
um, everything we do for sponsorship.
And the way it starts is I find some sponsored content online,
and then I, um,
so this sponsored content belongs to some company.
Then we try to find somebody from this company to contact,
um, I already showed you how to do this, right?
And then, um, sometimes it goes well and we get a deal.
Sometimes they don't reply and then yeah,
well we, um,
no, well, sometimes they reply and decline too,
right? So it is just to keep track of all that.
And I wanted to show you how to add content here to sponsored content.
I actually wanted to show you,
So I recently saw, um,
some sponsored content from a newsletter.
So here I would probably just,
uh, forward you, mm,
now I need to find it. Uh, I would just probably forward you an
email or send you a link, and then you will fill it in and
uh, um, where it is,
um, sequence. So this
company that I'm looking for, they run,
um, a paid advertisement in a newsletter,
in some other newsletter, right? And, uh, because they did this in the other
newsletter, mm, I want to offer them to do it with us
too. So I will pause it for a sec.
Second, uh, I will find it and then I will continue.
Okay, I found this. So this is the guest post.
So this is, uh, is a sponsored post,
even though I don't think they explicitly say that this is sponsored,
but yeah, I think, um, yeah,
we thank a Leo for the support of the sequence.
So this was a sponsored post. So yeah,
I, um, I will not forward it right now to you because,
uh, well I will in the future, but,
so I will open it in the browser. So I will take this post
and I will go and open it in,
sponsor it content. So this would be the link,
actually, let me open it in this.
So then it's uh, let me just copy
for types of data errors. You can fix it now,
Content type is,
uh, hmm. Uh,
let me go with article. So it's guest post,
so kind of article. So then it's newsletter,
right? And then relevancy, let's say medium,
then company [Inaudible].
So we don't have this company, so we will add this.
So let me make sure I type it correctly.
So gle, so I just,
because, uh, there is no record in this company table with
Galeo. So I just created, and then content is,
um, let me just say guest post in the,
Oops,
A guest post in the
Sequence newsletter.
Okay? Yeah. So this is how we add content
to this table. And,
um, yeah,
perhaps I will also show you this one.
Mm, so how to do it with,
uh, um,
with Google search. So I will,
so this, so I will copy
this link and I will just,
um, put it here too. So probably
I will not send you this, uh,
Google search links. I will probably send you links from Twitter or LinkedIn.
Um, but uh,
for now, let me just, uh, also for completeness,
um, put this to, in,
in this spreadsheet. So I will,
so how do I do this for Google searches?
So I think here we have a source with Google search,
right? And then I usually write here in the comment what kind of word
search term was it? So then it is product
service here. This is not go away.
So this is not an ebook,
this is not an article. This is like a landing page for day product,
right? So then that's why the classification is product service.
Then source would be Google search.
Relevance is, um, well let's go with Medium.
And then company, Company is,
uh, let me close this one company.
Is Google Aios such
a long hero
And go com. Yeah,
I guess this is how you type it with,
I don't know if I have them. Did I type it correctly?
Yeah, so we create a new one because it doesn't exist.
And then the term ML ops search
journal. And then I will do the same for other things.
And then maybe at some point later,
I will show you how I do this for mm,
for LinkedIn, for Twitter, and also for YouTube.
So for YouTube, sometimes I get advertisement like,
do I have it now? No, but sometimes,
uh, like there are some I am watching for some videos,
and then there is an advertisement also for some relevant company,
right? And then the source would be YouTube in this case.
Mm. Okay. So yeah,
I think that's, um, that's what I wanted to show you.
So, okay, go away. So that's what I wanted to show you.
So this, uh, CRM table and that we have
four tabs, um, um,
here, four tables. And then maybe what you can do is you
can create an overview document of all these tabs and what they are needed
for. Um, and then also create process document
for, uh, adding stuff to this,
to sponsored content tap. And then for contacts and for deals,
we will talk about this later. I will also record,
record the video and,
uh, yeah, we will cover it there too.
So that's a.