Yeah.
Hello. Yeah. So, um,
I already showed you how we do raffles.
So I wanted to show you how we announce winners.
So I already have  here.
So I will tell, I will show you later how to actually collect this
list of winners. Uh, I needed to set things,
set things up, but when all,
yeah, so there's this, this list of winners,
and then you go to the state and you right
here, click on retreat. And then you say,
quote, tweet. And here you say,
uh, the winners of John
Locke's book.
Um, um,
congratulations, please send us your
emails in them. Thanks.
So nobody one for taking part.
So something like this, so you do this and then people will that,
right. Uh, in diem, in direct messages,
I will show you, um, way through, maybe I'll record the video about that,
but for now I'll just click on feed and people
will get notified and they will start,
uh, writing messages on why it's not working.
Yeah. Messages. And then there will be messages,
uh, here message request.
You will see it. I will show you so you will need to periodically
check this and see if there are,
if emails are sent to us and collect this email somewhere,
and you can create a spreadsheet or something like this. And once you have
like four, four or five emails, you send it to Kevin.
You probably remember the email chain I started.
Let's say it was, um, that mesh.
Yeah, this email chain you are here already.
So you can just send the list of emails here.
So that's all. Yup.