Um, sometimes I share,
announced the community. So for example,
the system envelopes community,
sometimes they share talk events there,
and this is what I wanted to do now, the name.
So I want to share this amount And
it's on data monitoring, bylaws and
Moral and amazing with
Amy. So Danny is there it,
is there the speaker Worse?
Um,
Yeah, I'll just copy the link.
Interesting
Here.
Um, Yeah,
so this is how I share Announcements
in other communities. So I might also ask you to do the same,
for example, it is a community, this channel where you do this,
be shamed, is there is another community, um,
vocally optimistic. I don't know if they need is there as well.
Um, so there Is the commitment.
This is the special events. This is the place where it was shared.
Danny is here
Well useful. It looks for  system,
Um,
And pay this.
I'll also do now in other communities.
So this ice you're part of this or not,
but, um, be there as well.
Yeah, promotionals. Right?
One.
What else do we stick in this one?
Open data. I don't know. Think they're the ones
that I showed you and the hopes community,
local optimistic and this ice, because
you share events in other communities.