Um, Hey, just wanted to mention,
to do, give me a comment about this email.
So we don't need this LinkedIn to interrupt site.
Typically we already have this. So if we go to data top stop,
which I mean, so I think it's faster.
Yeah. So we already have this information like LinkedIn,
for example, but after the webinar or after events
or what they usually ask is,
uh, any links that, uh,
she shared during the presentation,
she over here, but for the speaker, um,
that should be included in the description activity.
It's some blog posts or some tools that speakers mentioned or anything
like that. So yeah. Maybe update the template a little bit.
Yeah.