Oh, hi. Yeah. I wanted to show you how to bond people.
So first of all, um, I prepared this message.
I will send it to you. So you have like a copy.
And then I go to settings sending me station
manage members. So you are also an admin,
so you should have it. And then this is the user.
Want to Goodman will now
find your month.
And, uh, yeah, so this is how we bond is like just
click here and deactivate the account.
So of course we need to make sure that this is the person who
want to bond. So we need also to check that like the name and
then the pictogram, this is a person because there is only one that of
Goodman. So we activate the account.
So that's all. And now I will send to you this message.
And this is how we want people.