Um, right. So I wanted to show you how to add the expenses
to this spreadsheet and this spreadsheet keeping,
send this spreadsheet. I keep all the expenses.
Yeah. So this is basically a bid date. When the
invoice was issued, this is the date when it was paid,
but typically, um, for all the expenses,
the dates, you shoot them. Date weight is the same.
Usually sometimes, uh, my it's invoice from,
for example, um,
Bayer or invoice from Pablo.
Sometimes it takes a date, but usually that way on the same day for
all the automated services, like the one I am going to show you now.
So for all these sources, usually the date is the same.
So what I want to show you is, uh,
right now I paid for this thing, Uber suggest,
so this is a service, almost like a uterus
for that. And it's actually, you can see it here.
Hope you can see it on how it looks like on your end.
So this is the payment and how I want to now add this to
this spreadsheet. Right? So of course it's possible to do it manually,
but I want to show you an automated way to do this.
So there's the full I will probably,
when you get it, it will be like,
I will.
So when you will get it, maybe I will forward it to you or
something that is so let me just do four words.
Uh it's and I'll forward
it to myself to,
yeah. So I we'll do that now.
And yeah, so now you see the payment and usually the,
what you can do to turn this into a PDF.
So we need PDFs here,
support each line here. We need it with the actual expense,
like to, uh, to prove that the infection,
somehow I want to create a video from this.
So in g-mail I just do print,
um, yeah. Uh,
save it
Sometimes. So for many things,
EDF will be generated automatically by the service in something stable,
not so you need to, um,
pay it immediately. So,
um, I will save this file and now I
have a special email channel.
We'll now use it's called voice.
So respond through books in west attachment.
I will send you the, this, uh,
um, this email. So this is an automation that will automatically
say file to pro books. I will show you to occasional and Alliance.
Yeah. So now with this invoice,
I will attach it, this invoice,
we just paid it
and here in the topics I need to drive to.
So what would it be also file name.
So I will show you throw books in
drug books,
voices folder, you see the way invoices look like the
way I own names look pike he's first is date then minus then there
is a to here I would suggest.
And what book the file in Dropbox
with date minus. So
let me just send it, uh,
I will, uh,
so it might take a bit of time before it works.
Let me see, like maybe one minute or something
like this.
Yeah. We'll just put it on pause.
Okay. So we see that this thing appears here.
It didn't appear yet in a Dropbox.
Maybe they just need to adjust the question.
So now either in robots I'm
open it
and we see them some ways.
Okay. Now you see like
edit this line here. So I need to change it's five minutes.
So Uber suggest. Yeah. And then,
so this is the provider. This is the company that they should,
the invoice in this form,
what we need to write, what exactly was the thing that,
so I will open it and I will see that we paid
or this month set up.
Um,
So now we need to do this. So this one,
the invoice is in euros. That's why we don't need anything in this column.
So in this column would have the price in the United States.
So we only care about response. So for this one,
the price is 419.
So I need to write minus four condoms because
this is paid for this.
That's why it's negative. So when it's income,
it's positive when it's expense,
it's negative. And so,
yeah. Let me also show you too.
Uh, you will be seen. So usually the way I do,
I just send email to this address to
be S suggest, where
did they send it to
this one? And then,
um, I send it and then let's say at the end of the day,
or the end of the week, I come to the spreadsheet and it will
be sent. So now I want to show you how to deal.
So go and I want to do,
oops, sorry.
I want to take care of this one.
So I want to care this slide. All right.
So in norm we see slide off and we
pay
again. It was uterus since here.
Let me check here.
I just opened the inwards,
All the noise and here
is engage in OPA.
Um, yeah, let me show you how I feel.
So MailChimp should be like
capital. So usually, so this like automatically gets their file
name here, and then I manually change it in the spreadsheet.
So MailChimp and what's
so standard plan.
Yeah.
And then I want to show you these two things like how I see.
So it's actually in the, I think
it should be here. So MailChimp, you see,
because MailChimp charges in the dollars and then there is a
conversion to uterus. So I take this one and
we'll here and it seems is European.
It's a German thing. So it dots in
numbers. So I need to replace the dot.
And here, I think here
I've looked at things in uterus. All
the bookkeeping was
in Germany and in dollars.
And then for this type of fury, let me see what's into,
um, it's update,
email updated.
And then for this one, unfortunately I didn't pay it wrong.
You know, I paid it from my other car,
just my personal one. I don't know for some reasons or high-purity it
was attached.
Um, it will save.
So I didn't use this one so that one I will have to,
uh, to feel and myself.
Yeah. So this is how this looks like.
Um, they have a system that they use for even the same,
usually. So for example, let me show you how I do with this with
MailChimp. I don't know if you folks have access to this.
Maybe you will,
students in MailChimp.
So when I get the notification that MailChimp charters,
something, so these is the MailChimp,
right? So then they usually send invoice.
So the invoice is often billing,
reading history.
And I can see this one,
I suppose, be the latest payment.
So I can just click view.
And then like, it's the same, the same thing as we did last
time, as I showed you, you see my,
to, uh, you send this email to this email,
so I will actually send it to
you right now.
I will include this. Yeah. So you send
it to email central box.
So I think that it will be moral. So what I think when you
now make sense to you, maybe be R and
R documents in our process
docs, come on log.
So maybe the older keeping
Voices and let's start there.
And I think from this video, you will a like
Tuesday may be, so yeah,
I hope it wasn't too much. Yeah.
Diesel.