Show you how to add extra information to book of the week pages.
So I created, I created a page,
which for this book as one visual direction,
and I added this one so that the author give
to our community. So first they wanted to show you how I edit this.
So for that, you need to go to book and
then there is a long case, two books, and then,
uh, you need to find the proper one.
Yeah. I'm by the way, on get half sweat beach or
upset, this is the location.
Location is get hub accommodated and data docs pop up.
And then there, I selected the folder and physical books.
And then here, I need to find this visual introduction to the permit.
And usually it will be one of the last books, right?
Because this will be the books that we have in the pipeline.
And you can see the date here.
So this is the book of the week on 14 February and here,
okay. This date, after you find this book,
click on us, then click edit.
And so, and then there was some texts and this
thing wasn't here. So what I did is I added a few line breaks
and we did there and then click commit changes.
Okay, I won't do this because it's already done.
You just wanted to show you how I do this.
And then the other thing, all right now,
or sent me a sample. So he sent me a PDF file.
I cannot just include a PDF file easily.
So , so what I did
is I asked him,
can you please support this samples somewhere?
And then I will add this to then the one page  page as well.
I needed direct link. So I can just take this,
uh, PDF and, and this. So that's why I need a
direct link and your edit this link to
his Google drive. And now I want to add this
direct link that he created to the website,
to our page. So on that page,
we have please think this section talk links,
and there's a lot of the one link to the website.
Say, I want to add another one. And yeah,
it was called each would hold the same structure.
So first it will be link. So business link,
uh, actual income, and then there will be,
um, so, so she us the same structure.
So first minus indicating that this is a new item in new link,
and then this new item has two things there,
the link itself. So this is where the in goals and then,
uh, the, the title.
So this will be here, another bullet point.
So bookworm site is created using this thing,
and then there will be another bullet point.
Now it'd be this here.
So now let me click can be changes.
So now, yeah,
then so now we created a comet and now if I go to actual
2, 1, 2, sorry.
So now I go to actions. Um,
and then yeah, I, I want to see,
to monitor the progress what's happening right
now. He hasn't updated yet and
she hasn't once we get some
attention and just one second. Um,
okay, so it is cute. So it will be to give it's one.
So yeah, we just need to, it's a progress now.
So here, the purpose of this thing is to see,
well, actually it will get updated. So right now I see an actions.
This thing is, as this check needs to be inserted this updated.
Now we'll have this on the beach. So this is how you get extra
information. Like this is a picture of the book and this is how
you, it links. Yeah.
So.