Show you how to add books. So in the previous video,
I show you how to add authors or people in general.
Now I want to show you how to add books.
So, uh, there is another, uh,
table here, another form. So this form is eight in the book.
So let me copy this. I will also send it to you.
And here we again, meet author CMIO.
So this way I can match, uh, in this author with,
uh, the profile we just created so I can close it.
So this is the same person we did last time.
So email is here,
uh, and then since he's the only author we live with
empty, if he wasn't, then this is how we would add them.
So now let's feel the rest of the things.
Of course, you can just ask the author to,
um, to give you all this information,
like the title of the book description. Um,
but usually you don't need to do this because all the information is available
on the book page. So first of all,
the title, visual introduction to deep learning.
So this is the title then description.
Um, there's no worries here. Um,
Yeah, maybe this fine. So,
uh, this is not super concise. Uh,
I think it's fine. Let's give show then a book page.
I think this is the main book page. So these a book is self-published
so there is no, uh, publisher speech,
but, uh, yeah. Publisher is this mining or pact or a righty,
usually on their pages. So this would be a publisher's page
on mining. Um,
came about here. We did not feel it then books,
patron, Amazon, actually, I don't know if this book has a patron,
Amazon. Okay. We can check it on Google with usual introduction to deep learning.
Uh, no, I don't see it.
So, uh, and this in quotes to make sure that,
uh, we get it.
No, they're just not on Amazon. So this is actually this book,
but this is not an Amazon. Okay.
I think it means that this book doesn't have a patron,
Amazon, uh, books.
Good cop report. Yeah. We can also check that quickly.
Uh, let me get hot again.
There is no page on GitHub, but, uh,
yeah, if there was, maybe this book is because this is a self-published book,
this is not a good example, maybe for another book.
Um, I will show you how to find all the other fields.
Um, but yeah, so this is how you add this.
You click submit and then now I should see it
here. Yeah, no, I have it here.
So this is called you submit a book. Um,
actually this is weird.
Um, the date is invade is missing.
I don't know where it, uh, what
happened, but let me quickly add, uh, so here,
um, you ignored this part, so this is not something you need to document
you just fast forward this,
uh, uh, yeah,
so I want to edit date here field.
So don't pay attention to this.
So this will be the start date.
And, um, we need to end this,
let's see here, book breach.
Yeah. That description, um,
their week, then one day a week
when the, uh, around how class.
So yeah, so this is pretty important.
Um, so let me open this form again,
and that will show you how to heal in this particular field.
So you just click on this field and then we have the schedule two
and schedule, we have this mentor who is on 14th of February.
So yeah.
So then here you select 14th of February.
So this will be there Monday of the week where it starts.
So here in, uh,
this schedule, we'll have it here,
send these is when it starts. So you just need to put it there
and yeah, no, you click submit and yeah.
And I will just manually add this and you can pretend that they added
this through, uh,
through the form. Okay. So now I have this and database,
so it's actually through the form. And then the next thing you need to
do is you need to tell me, forum is there for ready,
and then I will execute the script. And then after it script is executed,
we have, sorry, we can mark
this as announced. So now maybe the status could be a forum
or something like this. So now I know that forms fields.
I need to execute this my best after you do this,
you just ping me saying, Hey, this is field and you will
wait for an action from me. I do this,
and then I will pick you again. Um,
you can just change it to announced after I do this.
Okay. That's all I wanted to show you. No,