Yeah. So tomorrow we'll have, okay.
I wanted to show you how I make announcements there.
Sorry. Now it's evening.
So usually the announcement is for a morning,
I'll show you all. I do this. So this is the announcement
last week. So what I usually do is paint properly,
but then instead of copying from the previous,
we could just put a template in Fluxus doc,
but this is how I do it right now. And then I incorporate
the name of the book, which is this one official introduction and
basically place the book name, and then,
uh, this name.
Yeah. So I, I talk the guests,
um, the, the mucosa, if it's one that could smoke the play,
I talk to them, all of them. Now I need to
place these, um, this discussion.
So for that table here,
and then I take this, so this one about discount,
uh, yeah, this is not really part of the description
here. It should be Mandrake machine here.
We kept playing great, but here we do not.
And then I don't this one link to you and I had a picture,
so I already downloaded the picture.
So if I didn't have it, I would maybe just do this same
has Colver,
whatever. So just any name?
Well, not the name, because the name will be actually visible.
Like you see here for funders, there's this name since
I'm just put any name, something sensible,
and now I could see here to the cover apart
from the computer. And then I selected.
Yeah. So this is stepping and
instead of posting it right away,
I schedule it for later custom time.
So I usually schedule it for 7:30 AM,
uh, central European time, and
then it just kicks kid off and yeah,
the message will be sent to, to this channel.
And then what
I do the morning, I also,
once these messages, uh,
probably I also make an announcement like,
um,
like this one. So we'll show you how to do this,
but also I make an announcement in their announcement channel,
how I schedule their announcements for the week events.