So I wanted to show you how we do this what
you what you asked like how we check Revolute and Phenom.
So here we have money in the section with money and this is our
history the transactions right. So we go to the month we want to build
a report for and this is July and you look at all the expenses
and incomes right. So here we have some incoming transactions
and I don't know if we actually have
them in the spreadsheet
check
yeah I think you figured this out right.
So first of all um uh
the ones that I sent to me,
we don't,
no yeah we don't uh include
so this one please remove them all
right so this uh TK, Technicare Krankenkasse,
this is my uh health insurance so this should go to this
thing so let's uh move it
so this Community Launch, I'll just call it Alex um
it's not OpenAI Invoice, it's OpenAI so the correct spelling
is um yeah so Valeria,
Phenome, Phenome, Phi, Phenome Sound,
also make sure that the minus sign is correct here so
right now here what we have is uh um not a minus but
like I don't know.
Dash or whatever so it has to be proper minus and then for Valeria
I think am I looking at the last month yeah this
one zero then
OpenAI should be OpenAI,
AI Usage um so
yeah and then like for each of these records So we should have an
invoice, right? So I think you already figured it out um
I cannot just so as I said it always has to be
minus like that and then uh
yeah like that so yeah make sure that the
formatting is always like it treats it as a digit so here instead
of comma you use I am right now a bit confused
with what you did and what you did not do here so
again records this is when I sent money to me it
shouldn't be included so replace
all the minuses all the commas with dots and
when a comma is here you don't you remove foot.
1 so here remove dot here remove
zeros dot here and yeah either remove zeros or just
put a dot there so it has to be like American formatting
so this one uh their name is
like where does it actually come from? Like 7-3?
Do you take it from here or?
Okay, I don't understand.
Okay, yeah,
right, so they
create invoice. Okay.
So you remove,
you don't include this. This one. And make sure that for each of these
records, we have a,
we have a document, we have a PDF. So this one,
I think their right name is like, you need to find,
um, incoming
voices. Yeah,
like you need to, you put what, why,
what is actually here. So for Southern Cloud,
like when you find the invoice, you will find what it is for.
So you need to add here. So this is consulting.
This is actually taxes.
So here you put, uh,
taxes, uh, July,
July. Now yeah,
you can always look at the previous months, right?
and Southern Cloud, yeah, you also write.
What for you will find it in the invoices,
uh, Google Workspace,
Cloud. Um,
do we have an invoice? There, there should be a process document for finding
the invoice from Meetup. Uh, virtual assistant,
um, business launch. If I use
community launch. Yeah,
this looks correct. So this Cambridge Mercantile Corporation
should be, should actually be here. Be, um,
Arise Inc. They just use,
uh, some sort of proxy for which they pay.
So the invoice was sent to Arise.
So we need to rename it to Arise.
Where is Arise?
Can't find them. Arise.
Yeah. So this is Arise AI. And
then check the, using the invoice number,
what it was actually for. Right. Uh,
so here again should be dot. So now we can check that everything
works. If we can look at this, if we select everything and we see
the sum. Right. So something is still wrong.
So this one is wrong. All right,
so now when we select, something is still not correct.
Ah, here, the sum.
So I don't know what this R is.
So you need to fill this in and this in too.
Uh, and
like these ones are needed to,
um, be able to. To know how many documents should be in the zip
file that we sent. So usually this one,
uh, we don't include invoices from our accountants.
So this, uh, uh, is consulting is our accountants.
So we don't send our accounts, accountants,
the invoices from our accountants. The rest of the invoices we sent.
So then it's all ones here.
Right. And then I just look at the number of ones here.
and I see that's okay. There should be 20 invoices.
And when we prepare the zip archive, we need to make sure.
So for example, this is for the previous month,
right? So there are 12 invoices. And I can check in
this folder that there are also 12 files,
right? So this, this much, uh,
these two numbers much, right? So we want to have the same.
So we want to make sure that we sent all the invoices to our
accountants. and then for Finansamt,
we'll put it here. So please put it in the same,
uh, format as here. And
to know what it is for, you can go to Finom. Yeah.
And then, um,
this is the thing we need to put here.
So this should be something.
Something like this. Yeah,
right. And then the same with Tekka.
So, so this here,
this Tekka and Finansamt are that access.
Yeah. So you need to fill this in for incoming
invoices. And I think you figured this out,
right? So how do you go through all the payments
here? And the same with Revolut.
Come on. Well,
it's basically the same and I think you figured it out.
So like there's an overview of all the transactions and you go through them
and see if any of the incoming transactions or outcoming transactions are missing.
And if they are, you make sure you add invoice to the Dropbox folder.
Okay, this was a long video. I hope it was useful.
So let me know if you have any questions and let's please document everything
that is not documented yet. So then it's way clearer,
let's say, when we want to onboard a new person.