Do you use veto? So for some reasons, I didn't have a couple of
fields there. So the fields that are also important,
but missing is this book, cover URL and book power.
Um, yeah, this is not the best name.
I will change it to, to look more human than
that. Um, but here their ideas is very similar to what you do with
speaker profile. So you need to,
um, now either put the book,
cover URL or upload a cover. So Miller actually gave me already
the cover. So I need to download this let's say from which
yes. Yes. So now let me check on
the size of this thing. So pretty
weak. I don't need that big, so I don't know.
You can use whatever program you want for resizing the image.
I will use X and view.
So then, uh, I will change it to,
Hm, well, this is pretty small,
maybe 300 by 400.
Okay. And this is button. So now I save it.
So in, um, actually to the size,
it, what I did is I did shift S then,
uh, shift, test opens this window. Then I choose this one,
this one, and decided, I don't know if you need to document this,
you you're free to use whatever two,
you are comfortable with 40 size images anyways.
So I do this, then I click safe.
Yeah. This there image.
And now I can go to this form and
this one, this old one. So yeah.
And the book cover, and I upload this.
So this is how you do this. I'll click upload.
So this is how you do this. Uh, so it's either Euro for some
books, for example, for mining books or books mining.
So let's see for mining, I will show you how to do this with
mining books. So for mining books,
it's a little bit tricky. Um,
so let's take this one. Um,
this is not a book, so,
uh, for example, least exploring a data science career.
So this is a book, um,
and the, when you click it, doesn't show you the safe as,
uh, like a safe image.
Yes. So what I need to do is click inspect,
and then in inspect,
um, and SPECT this,
this image, right? And then the,
the Euro of these things here.
I don't know if it's visible, if it was clear what I did.
So I clicked on this link, then I click inspect,
and then it brings me to this image in HTML,
and then it has this SFC think this is the thing that we need
to, uh, copy and then paste it.
And then here, the book is, it's already quite small,
so you can just take this and
just take it and put it here and then for
pocketbooks. Uh, so let me check pocket books.
So for pocket books, I think you just try to click on this copy
image address, and, um,
uh, what did here think there's just an actual hook
and then we have also Reilly books.
Um, so for example,  publications.
Yeah. So this is a book on Australia. So open this in incognito,
because for you, it will look like that for me to different.
And then yeah, for our island book, uh,
we'll just do copy image address as well.
And then, uh,
put it here. Do not copy.
Yeah. And you can check that this is actually information from,
uh, for pact, for Riley and for mining.
Usually they have small images,
so you don't need to resize this. Yeah.
So this is how you feel the image or fields in.