Um, okay, so now it's September the beginning of September,
September, so it's time to file a declaration.
So if they need to do this at the beginning of every month,
um, for the previous month. So the first thing is
first thing they need to do is to add an extra line.
So I separate every month. Um, let me see,
like, so this is by the way,
it's sorted by the date when it's displayed by the date.
So this date is when the invoice is issued and this
is the date when it's paid. So yeah,
for my invoices, that for our invoices that we issue usually
like the date when it's shoot and if it is different,
because companies takes a bit of time to do this.
So yeah, it is sorted by the date when it's free and I separate
each month with a lens here.
Yeah. So we'll have all these things, right.
And I need to send this to my bookkeeper,
to my accountant, and then she will file the support tool,
um, tax
tax, tax office.
Yeah. So the important thing here is to make sure that all the income
is declared. So, or,
uh, like this spending
Of course spending is also important, but if I don't declare spending nothing
bad will happen, but if I don't declare,
uh, income, then I might go into jail.
So yeah, it's very important to make sure that we declare all the income
properly. So this year I have like war
five plants income. Right. So there are, there are things that,
uh, I received this month,
so I need to go to clinical and then go to,
uh,
so not all the money comes to Sonoma county.
So some of the money comes to, uh BuyPower or my other bank
account, but most of this comes to, you know,
so that's why, uh, we will check this and, you know,
so there should be five payments up
to where it is almost. So we check in August and then
we just have income
In, by money coming in and
in August it was,
um,  here.
Um, so checks than soda,
soda checks for COVID yeah,
the next, uh, uh,
yeah. Perfect. There are actually two payments from protect.
So this one and this one,
so they pay two times. So that's why it's one lines.
Yeah, that's perfect then.
Um, or else we have this follow-up by,
yeah, we've got follow up here. Um,
we've got some money from this AI infrastructure,
Lance, Lance,
and then finally there was 5 cents here,
you know, so they return some money or some services.
So what's important is you see somethings here that
you don't see here, that it's very important to let me know if
you see some income, some money coming in here
and they are not in the keep keeping spreadsheet,
then we'll have to look at that step. And
so when it comes to voice in the,
or income invoices, so all the invoices.
Yeah. So we have all the income invoices,
all the invoices that I send to companies
that are here. I don't know why.
So, um, uh,
let me just check that. Uh, so we'll have,
we'll have soda because I,
I, I, you know, yeah.
I think, uh, all of them and,
uh, yeah, so to make sure that everything we need,
um, um, well there is another folder invoices,
right? So this is, these are the invoices for the payments
that we had and what I do to make sure that I don't forget
anything. So I enter once here.
So this invoice to invoice to my bookkeeper,
it's, uh, I don't have the invoice conviction was because it's a
automatic payment. So she just issued one invoice telling me that I need to
pay every month. That's why I don't look more like a physical invoice
here, but for the rest of they have physical invoices.
So that's why I add here once.
And what I do here is see, I select ones.
And then I see the sounds. Yeah. So 18 invoices.
And what I do now is I take all these invoices and then add
them to,
No, I will change the name of this thing to data talks,
uh, uh,
in a month. I don't actually remember really name it.
So let me take this will,
what would hear? Yeah. It's data toxicity. These are the previous things I said
and okay, so here, insight,
12 items, and then now I will open
it
Thing.
Okay. So now I'll go to incremental basis and take all
the invoices with plus.
So I take them, I copy them and I put them to the same
compressed zip folder. You see, they're kind of separated with the plus.
These are the invoices that,
where I got to money and Bisa,
that's where I paid. So in total we have 18,
which might just the number here, 18, right?
So we get all, we'll have all the invoices we,
we need, and this is how we prepare a file.
Um, and this is after this has prepared.
So what I do next is I go to invoices and then select all
the invoices for August.
So they send the same invoices I put in their file should be,
yeah, it's the 12th.
So I moved down to protest. Alright.
So the next time I don't see them,
but I prepare something for September and then the same
with income. So I take this on and I'm not
sure.
Um, and then these ones, we underscore these being voices that I shoot,
but they weren't made yet. Okay.
So this is how we prepare this file.
It's important to see that yet it's 18,
18.
And, um, yeah.
So the most important thing is we have all the income that,
you know, that is also like fair all the invoices here
and all the things for the income are actually in the
document in this book, keeping, um,
yeah, maybe, um, another thing. So I will show you later in another
video, how to send this to the accountant,
but I see already that, so first of all,
there was the payment. So if I go to my funeral,
I see that there is a payment from, um,
to my accountant.  like
at the beginning of every month, so we need to edit here and
the way I did this,
so I will edit. And so today's date September,
September, and then, uh  um,
so, and then there is this line,
if this, the, what, the line I sent, um,
email, and usually like,
when you see it, you can go to the previous month and see how
exactly it was declared in the previous month.
So I want you to put it here and then for this one,
maybe you check the,
yeah. So you check that and go away.
Yes.
So yeah, you check this total amount, total heart.
Uh,
but anyways, yeah, for this one, you just go to genome and see what's
the payment was the neuroscience,
uh, a dollar sent here.
Okay. I think that's all for now. And then I'll record you.
I'll send you a separate video for how to send this to,
uh, tax, uh, to my account.