I received the last email. You sent
me the email, so now I will.
Thanks. So then I paste it here and
now with emails, what I will do is send them to the author since
with a memo, we communicate.
Hold on. Yeah.
I wanted to quit check my taste profile that I just
do communicating
through LinkedIn. Maybe we should've done this through email and
now I just came in
or
in a typical fluid
emails, the nurse, please send them.
Thanks.
This is how I send emails to others.
Well, usually this is publishers, but stay in space and book this self published.
And for publishers, they usually send it to a publisher.
Maybe I can show you usually it.
Oops.
For example, my conducted.
Yeah. So based on the emails.
Yeah. So this is how it looks like sometimes there is author in the
copy as well, sometimes. And then I say that I shoot things
again. And then I say,
yeah, and that's,
that's how I address.