I when somebody asks,
if they can reschedule, I want to show you how to check my calendar
if I have available spots. So go to Google
and then you're in search for people,
bright mind.com.
And then you will see my calendar. I see,
like where I am busy,
where I cannot do and sometimes
okay. Empty slots. So generally in this
serve things here, this slot, like from five to six in
your time zone, it's probably different. Yeah.
So you want me to sit in this spot here?
Um, so when they ask a what can move to a different
days, for example, in this case that is asked to do it
on 21st, I think you already created,
okay. So here you would see that I
am, and then you can apply it to the
guests, to the speaker that, okay.
Yeah, we can do it on 24th at this land.
We both have access to my calendar and you see that.
I don't have anything else, but let's say if I said something,
then it would say, maybe we can do it Thursday
31st, for example. Yeah.
And this time here, 12 to 13,
usually I am available.
So this busy thing here is lunch.
So I make it,
uh, make myself busy. So people don't put meetings well lunch,
but in general, if somebody wants to move podcast event,
then we can also do this around lunchtime.
So for me, it's fine too sometimes. Uh,
okay. So yeah, because this is how you check my apple ability when somebody
asks to reschedule.