So, I wanted to show you how to check historical rates,
so let's create a process document for that.
And, uh, we have this book.
Why did I don't tell it?
Okay, yeah, so what the? Okay,
so we have the uh the kick-end document.
Yeah, I guess it's been a while since I opened it last time and
umm so you need to check the price umm
like the actual amount they paid and then, and let's say it's not 15
but I don't don't remember how much was it? I would say 17 whatever
and this is how much it was on,
this one is big and deep big was
it but uh 12?
right so then um. Good one, good one,
good one, good good one.
we know how much was it right so it wasn't uh it wasn't
the exact amount and then when you write to our accountants
you can say that yeah you pay it in uh use.
Z but yeah the cost of like exchange rates whatever this
is how much we received so it's different from the English okay.
All right.