Um, hi. So I wanted to show you how to reach out to companies
and offer them sponsorship or something like this.
Um, like this is basically how I find clients.
So th th this is a company I want to write to,
so I'm subscribed to their newsletter, and I see that the,
uh, some events they want to actually help them promote this
events. So I want to reach out to them and asked if
they're interested in, uh, working together.
So the way, uh, the, one of the options would be just to reply
to this email and then say something.
So I will not do it right now. So what I will do instead
is I will try to reach out to them through LinkedIn.
And, um, yeah, so I will show you colleges,
sisters, they need the name of the company.
So I copy this name of the company,
and then I go to LinkedIn and then I put the name of the
company and then something like community.
So I usually try community and marketing.
So these are the people who are responsible for,
uh, these kind of things or promoting these kinds of things.
And these are people who would potentially be interested in promoting some
stuff through our newsletter, or maybe sponsor in the community.
And we have two people who are potentially,
um, relevant for this. So marketing director and community managers.
So these are the kind of people who are usually interested in,
uh, uh, promoting. Oh,
thanks. Okay. So optimum their accounts.
And, uh, yeah.
So the first thing I do usually is I,
uh, um, so I already sent Sarah
connection request. So we'll show you here with,
uh, with Nama,
how I do this. So I do connect and then note
I data box.
Well, that's all I write. Um,
and so I already did this for Maya.
So now I want to write an email to Maya and
email. Uh,
yeah. So for email, we need to write a subject smell,
right? I wrong data blocks.
And then, um, I need to come
up with a message again,
sorry, message here. Uh,
It's just a message.  people
for data without, so this,
like every, everyone will receive the same message and
here, this is like a personalized thing.
So this one will be like,
by name, then this is the,
um, the line.
And then this is personalized plan, and this is close.
The message. Uh, please let me know if it's something interesting for you and
you need so for this one,
I already prepared the line. So I was wondering if,
uh, this name I cannot pronounce,
we'll be interested in working with us.  we
can talk, you promote this lens, uh,
in hopes related content.
Okay. This is the message I will send to her.
And by the way, I see that they are organizing a conference.
So thirst, I will, uh,
check, um,
welcome to C.
And
so are they, Ryan is similar anytime soon.
I think it was last year.
Uh, I think so too. Yeah,
I think so. It was last year. So this is mark.
Can you see, so all ride share this,
um, and, and that will write something like these
near you long
will be June or June.
So this a personalized message.
This is, um, but at the beginning,
maybe I will come with these things, but,
uh, this is pretty standard, I think,
so that it will be like personalized stuff.
Um, this is some of the stuff now.
I just sent her email and hope she replies.
Now let's see now many of people
who I write to not play, but some do.
And this is how we actually find people,
companies to, um,
like to support us and promote things through the newsletter.
Okay. That's all for me.