Um, I just wanted to show you what I mean by now.
Word document, not Google. So if you,
you see there is this w think, so it means that it's actually a
word document. So if I go to the directory,
uh, you see like the sexually discuss shows that this is Microsoft word format.
So I want to open this, you
see that there's actually quite a bunch of word documents.
Um, they take some time to open in, uh,
Google drive. So yeah,
I prefer to have like native Google docs format.
So anyways, so what I asked you to do here first,
um, put the prefix deleted.
So not, not just delete first,
but put the prefix, then save it as a Google
doc. So you create a copy as Google doc.
I think I put the prefix to earlier. So, uh,
let me put it here.
Yeah. So for this one, it's kind of deleted.
So here created calendar invite.
So now we see that it's
here, right? So this is like not,
it doesn't have w anymore here and now you will
need to go to Trello. And
in thrill, I think there are two carts that use this template to
use this process document. Sorry. Um,
what has been our problem? Maybe more so please go
through these cards and replace the protest docs to point to
the new one, because they have, because they have different things.
And then after that, you can just, uh,
many more mode from here. So this is what I mean by,
um, by doing this.
No. So I'll add the loom in the.