Hi, so uhm,
we had quite a bunch of US dollars which I just converted
to Euros and I just added a fee
PDF to our uhm Dropbox,
right? And what I wanted to record in this video is That's how we
should put this, the euro amount.
So for this one, we see that there is an exchange rate.
So what we can do is uh, so this is what
we use. This is the exchange rate, and this is the amount of dollars
for the fee. So what I put,
I just multiply one by another, and this is actually what we put to
our bookkeeping spreadsheet, right? So this is the amount of euros that we put
when we bookkeep it, because we have it here.
We don't always have it, but when we do it in Revolut,
we can, we can see it.