Already talked about book of the week. So now I want to show you
how you can add books and authors.
Um, I have a special form for that. Um,
so the first forum was called people. So let me click open
forum. So I sent you this link,
so you will be using this link to add people,
uh, to this form. And then I will have on my side,
a script that pulls data from there and then publishes this to the website.
Um, so this is the link. I will send you this link.
So now we want to create a personal profile on a data,
talks, a club webpage. So in this particular case,
it will be an author. Um, but the same process,
uh, the process is the same for other people like for podcast
guests, for webinars, guests, and so on. So in this particular case,
the author is Miller.
I hope I pronounce his name correctly, so we need his email.
So this will be like, uh, a key that uniquely identifies this person because
they might have the, maybe there are two people with the same name.
And since we have email, we can uniquely identify them.
Then we need his name.
So the name is this one.
Um, then we need his . So one thing you
can ask, uh, usually for speakers,
I asked them, Hey, can you send me your view?
Um, but because Mayer is a book author, we have a link to his
book and usually on books,
uh, there is, uh, a description about the author.
Um, so where,
yeah, so about the author. So
I will just copy that. Uh,
of course he's my journey. Maybe we can ask him to provide
better, um, viewer and
yeah, of course each book page has a different layout,
so it's not always here. So for example,
if we go to mining,
so my, for mining, this is another book publisher,
the information, uh, let me take, for example,
this one. Um,
so here the information about the book,
sorry, here about the author.
So this is what he usually copy.
So for mining is in one place for O'Reilly it's in a different place,
but, uh, yeah, if you have problems finding the audio book,
authors, tell me in any case,
you can always ask them and you will need to do that for people
who are not book authors. So let me copy that.
So I am copying it here the other few.
Then we have two fields for pictures.
So there are two ways of uploading a picture.
So we'll show you the easy way.
So we can just,
uh, if the author agrees,
we can just go to their LinkedIn page and then click
one, click on the picture and then right.
Click, um, and then copy in which address and what happens is you get
an address that is copied to your clipboard,
and then this is the image. Um,
you can save it or you can put
it there.
I think you can just do that now.
So it should be either this or this.
Uh, I will show you how to also do it without with uploading.
So this is pretty simple. Um,
so this is the, I think we just uploaded so I can do that.
I click upload and then if I was there,
um, but yeah, it wouldn't be a picture Euro.
So if you provide both, so first, uh,
the first day we'll check if pictures there, if the picture is there,
I will use this. If the picture is not there,
I will ups. I will use the link.
So, okay. I think here let's go with a link and
then we need to fuel some links for this,
uh, for the speaker. So we need to get cup LinkedIn profile Twitter and
the website. The best thing you can do is just ask the author.
Um, or what I sometimes do is a,
just use Google. So for example,
I go to Google, right? First name, last name,
and then get up. And then,
yeah, it doesn't seem like , has they get help?
They say don't Google it. Doesn't find it.
Maybe we can just ask him.
No, I will not do this.
Uh, um, I will just move on.
So if you don't find anything, leave it empty,
then LinkedIn, I already have his LinkedIn name.
So it should be this part here.
Right? So not the whole URL, but just the handle then Teeter,
I don't know if he has Twitter, just use Google.
Yeah. Things like he has. Uh,
don't think this is the right purse.
Um, alright,
let me check. So at the least,
yeah. So you see the picture. It's very easy to see,
um, like if this is the same person,
because you see the picture, so I'm taking this thing after
hit or yeah. They can take it from the hero.
Um, and then the website, actually,
I don't know what his website is. I guess we can also ask him
if he goes to any website or not.
I think his website is these key dimensions.
Yeah. Yeah.
And this is his website and it, um,
so I submit,
okay, now I have this information.
So you will not have access. Maybe you will have access.
Uh, I don't know how to actually organize this,
but yeah, in this forum now I see this.
So all the data that you just submitted it's here and what you don't
see you the status. And then this is what they will use to,
uh, see the backup in different view to add.
So these are all the people who are not added.
And once I add them, the status will change to done
right now. It's up to you. So this is how you add authors to
this form. And then using this form,
I will create a page on the website.