We already have a video about creating newsletter
issues from templates. We just want,
you want to show you one more time, what you should do every week.
And the first step here would be to do the same thing.
Cause usually, uh,
as last time I showed duplicated,
Like in the previous video, I showed that you did this from draft,
Right? So you call to draft and then you a duplicate,
and this is actually a copy that I just created.
So here this one, you know,
this already. And So
here, let me see.
And then the next Monday we'll be 25th
And then so I'll leave it like that.
Hmm. And okay,
now you need to know if next week is the week we cannot.
So next one is,
uh, I think actually it is
right. It is. Yeah. So I will leave this to you to
feel, you already know how to goose.
Um, Yeah,
so subject let's leave it and changed usually.
So this is, um, so this is how you prepare this template.
So you don't change it like that for now to edit
design. And
So since for the next week we will have it.
So I live in here events,
so we can just go ahead and events.
And of course, if we add something new, if we announce something and then
we'll kind of come back out of it now,
but just in case they are kind of rating.
And then for the podcast, because we don't have the latest one between
it is not released yet. It will be released on Friday.
So that's why I was just this one.
So this one is kinda to do,
we still need to finish this, but it's almost ready.
So when
Don, we just go here and we,
this one and see, and then it's done.
It's ready. Yeah.
So this is how we create a template. So you feel in a book
of the week, if there is something next week,
if there is nothing, we didn't move it then events.
So it's really, if something,
we add something, then maybe one more time at the end of the week,
we can also be this, then podcasts,
this one and then add the previous
ones. And yeah,
that's how you create a template in the middle of the week.
So then during the week we can, uh,
could ideally populated with the content.
Okay. So have please change this.
Please modify book of the week. So now,
so now for you to edit this,
you will go to campaigns and this will be the campaign.
I just created this one and you can edit
this by the first one, your next time,
create a copy.
Now you can just immediately hated the copy.
And during the week you can come back and repeat it in the design.
Of course I forgot to respond to this also important.
Yeah. So this is how you prepare templates that we populate.
It's important not to send this. So yeah,
it saved. I'll send you all this.