I just wanted to show you how we can simplify this process.
Um, so I'm talking about this creating calendar invites.
So, um, national bar stays
like that. The second stage step stays like that Then.
Okay. Let me just read this hour.
Um, and then you add guests like guests,
it's Just an example.
And then you click on more options and then you end up immediately
in the,
And sit in more options. You add time.
So it should start usually by This
time. Well, if I click here,
Yeah, I think, Um,
I don't know if you can, I think you can sell it.
So please also do that central European time.
Berlin, if you can do this, it will help with Daylight
saving and things like this.
Okay.
So yeah, click here. So of course, to not say click on this thing,
just implant, Um,
and then for location,
like we hear this And
then here, Um,
and then get permission. Shouldn't be made if I have other secrets,
this is important.
Um, and yeah, this is why we do this. And then after that,
you click say, I will not do this because the spoken that does not
exist
if you do screenshots would be correct name.
Yeah. You click on this, but, uh, yeah,
two will not work because this guest does not exist, but hopefully it will
give you an idea how to do it without, uh,
you know, saving and then editing men do all this kind of stuff.