Hi. So I wanted to talk about creating events with Luma,
and we use Luma for this new re relatively new initiative called
Project of the Week. So for Project of the week,
we, um, let me open it,
uh,
Project
Of the Week. So this is the main repository for this initiative project of
the week. And we have different projects here.
So this one per Recommend systems was project of the week that you saw
last time when I was showing you how to edit some stuff in Luma.
Um, and yeah, like we have,
uh, so this is an event that goes,
uh, that takes like it's,
it's couple of days. It takes a couple of days. You see that there
is a range of dates from one day to another.
And then there is this link sign up here,
which leads to Lua. And then if we go through this,
there is a plan for each of the days, like day one,
day two, day three, and so on.
And we plan to have another one.
So this one was already created by me some time ago.
And then there is another one, which is now work in progress.
Uh, this one. And,
uh, yeah, this part that I show is maybe not important because the link
will, that we will create in Lua will point here,
right? Uh, but right now, since it's a work in progress,
it's in this repository. So for a second you can pretend
that this is my, this is our re this one,
this is the repo, but right now it's just,
um, a copy of the repo created by Liana.
Okay, So this is the project she created already.
So this is, um, so there are like five
days starting from day zero,
16th of November, uh,
17, 18, 19th, uh,
of November. Um,
and so now we want to create an event in Luma for all of
these dates, right? So this is, um,
these are the dates to,
yeah, it actually takes a little bit more.
That's for a week. I don't know why the dates are like that,
but okay. So now let us create events,
uh, an event with multiple days in Luma using this one.
And again, pretend that this is not, uh, that this is actually this
path, right? So this is, this will be the path for this thing.
Once, uh, we finish working on this,
this will be the path. Um,
yeah, so,
uh, let me go to, uh,
Luma. So go to are on the
main page and then here I will just click on create an
event
and change cover photo.
So for the photo, um,
I will just save this one.
So this is the previous one. I will just reuse it.
How can I save the image?
Actually that's weird.
So it's not saveable or what?
Mm.
So for this case, when uh, an image is not saveable,
uh, what I do is I go here to inspect
and then see, yeah, this is the background url.
Click on this, copy it.
Hmm,
Move this thing.
Okay, Yeah.
Hmm. That's weird. I guess you can just save this image once.
And we are basically using the same image every time.
Uh, project,
project. Or I can just send you this image if you don't want to
go through this. So that's the same image.
So now let me change this. Ah,
it's already here. So I can just click here.
I don't know if you will have it or not. And then the name.
So you see how the name is here.
So this project of the week, um,
colon and then the name of the project. So the name of the project
here is this one, Recommendation System part two.
So d i i y live out keep on the recommendation system.
Um, part two. So this will be a virtual event.
So the event euro, you can see here,
this is the project of Week channel in Slack.
So just copy this link under address and put it here.
And then it's an event series. So the duration will be,
let's say 30. Oh, it's zero hours,
I'll put it to 30 minutes. Cause these events are not really events.
They are more like reminders for people to go to Slack.
And then let's, uh, let me,
Uh, let me make them at five
30. Move this one now.
So they, they start at 16th,
right? So 16th will be the first one.
Then I add second one,
third. Uh, how many do we have here till Sunday?
Right? So for now let's just create five of them.
But then you see it's quite simple to,
to just, you know, session. Then you edit what
is it actually?
Maybe I can just do something like that.
Let me see. So when the daily
number of days five, Yeah,
, it was actually the same thing, right?
Okay. You can see how easy it is to add.
Anyways, um, what else?
I think that's for now.
That's it, right?
So now let me just create event. So in event is created now
go to hosts at Host,
and then I will add you here.
So you will probably need to add me. So the role is host can
Managements, right? So that's you.
So now you should be able to, to change this
thing. Hopefully we haven't tested it yet.
So now let's see. I will go now to details and I will
update the details. So here's the description.
And you see this is the description we had here.
So I will copy it and I will paste
this. So this is the description,
first part, this is the description about,
um, the actual, you know,
the project of week, what it is this week will,
uh, continue learning about Commander Systems because
it's part two. That's why I continue. Otherwise it will be we'll learn about.
And then this will be the topic.
Read more about it here. So we need to
Change it slightly because the link will be,
remember I showed you, Um,
yeah, this will be the link.
Okay.
Edit. And then public euro. Public euro is the,
we have this, the euro here and I will just
put it here. So it's DDC project of the week,
and then the code name for the project. So because we already had the
access one. So this one is access two.
Okay. Uh,
I think here that's all we need to do.
So we don't tick this one Access.
Um,
Yeah,
That's a part of this project of the we community.
Then, yeah, it's free except registration.
Max Capacity, not, don't,
we don't need to enforce emails.
Um, yeah. So this is the thing I showed you already.
So for this one, we remove this one,
We remove the first one and we remove the,
the last one. And we,
What did I show you last time? I don't remember.
So let me quickly check how it looked.
It's probably saved somewhere.
Okay.
Okay. I'll just go to some of our previous events.
Uh, past, yeah, past event manage.
Just want to see how emails look like.
So it was daily reminder, a reminder to join.
So let me copy this part.
So we have the emoji here.
Cox, oops, I don't need it.
Daily. Reminder to join.
Uh, too many spaces here. Daily reminder to join event name
My class.
And what did we have here in the party?
I have to remember,
Maybe,
Can I actually see it?
Uh, email.
Okay. Um,
I guess we can just leave it empty. Mm, yeah,
if, and also let's change this to five 30,
the reminder to join.
Okay,
Great reminder. And then we need to do it for
all these things. So remove this one.
The first one, remove this one and change this one.
So it's, uh, um,
daily reminder to join and it should be at five
30. Okay?
That's, uh, that's it. This is how you create events in
Luma and events for Project of the Weekend.
Remember project of the week, they are multiple
days events, right? So there are multiple,
they occur over multiple days.
And then maybe we will need to add, uh,
a couple of more sessions. Um,
by the way, just let me quickly check what else we need
to
Add here.
More,
I guess for now we don't need to do anything else.
So that's how we create events in Luma. Then I'll send
you this picture so you have it. Okay,
see you later.