Uhm, so I just wanted to show you what to do when there is
no subtitle, sometimes it happens,
you will have seen with workshops,
webinars So, also podcasts,
sometimes there is no subtitle,
right? And then I usually need to come up with something,
so this is what I do So I,
uhm copy this,
the entire thing and then I go, I go to chargepd and I
put suggest then title for
this workshop and then uhm workshop,
you can replace workshop with podcast interview or webinar and then
I'll see what happens. it comes up with uh
yeah, I'll do an up-to-date
track with DLT. So then this is something you can send me,
for example, or I think 10 maybe is too much.
Let's use 10 titles for this workshop.
And then this is something you can send to me,
right, so you can say, okay, this thing doesn't
have a subtitle, but here are the suggestions from JudgePT.
Oops. And then, uh.
We can look in Scalable Datas Pipeline.
Could be something like this. Right.
So, this is what you can do when there is no subtitle or there
is no title. You can, uh, send me already some options.
And if you don't have a ChargePT account, you can create one.
And this ChargePT 4.0 should be available on free plans.