I realized that the instructions for creating the calendar in in
the course was not clear so I probably should record the video and then
we create a process document for that so the way it usually works is
when we have something in the course calendar we create an event
and then I will go to more options where
the yeah so then here we select a calendar here so we
use this data engineering zoom camp and
we don't add guests here because this information is visible to
a lot of people so we don't want to share any zoom links we
don't want to share any emails we don't want to share anything except
the title so here we will have office hours we dont need
to add anything else because the calendar is that engineering zoom camp so its
kinda clear that its office hours for that and then the link
will be our youtube channel
so the link here will be our youtube channel and here we
will write we will stream 2 or
youtube channel and then the link right so and there
is nothing else so we can i guess it doesn't
matter so we don't need to change anything here so here we updated and
this is the the previous one i think yeah this is the previous one
that i changed so now for this one i
edited it and i didnt realize that we have two different so
we have only one event so please for this one recreate
it one more time so this so for this event
i'll delete it so please create it one more time using the usual
way of doing that and when we need to create a course
event you know now how to do this so for that for the event
with Matt please recreate it