Hi. So this is the invoice that Valeria created or template,
and I wanted, um, so we need to pay here every month.
So every month there will be an automatic transfer to your account from
our pH, right? Uh,
but for the report, for our tax report,
we need an invoice, right? So this is the invoice for the first month,
and I want to show you what we need to do, what we will
need to do every month to, um,
to include, uh, like what we will need to change in this invoice to
include it in our report, right?
So, um, the only thing we will need to do is change
this part. So this is where the invoice number and
dates are. So here, uh,
for example, for the next month, uh, when the report will be,
uh, when the invoice will be generated in March.
So we change this thing, we change this thing.
So this is the prefix for the invoice, this is the date for the
invoice. And then services provided in March would be February,
March, right?
And in, um, April it would be March,
April, and so on, right? So for every month there will be the
previous month and the current month. And then,
yeah. So these are the three things we need to change. Now let me
unchange them, and then now you just,
uh, download a PDF
And include it in our, um,
in our report, like usual. So now I will include this invoice and
it'll have today's date. I guess it's not,
uh, really a big problem, right? Um,
okay, I will just send you the invoice and then you will take care
of that, or no,
I will send it through the usual process,
right? And then, uh, you will see it in the,
uh, in the bookkeeping report.
But for the next month, when you see that there is a line in
our phenome, then you know what to do.