I wanted to show you how to create invoices in U s D in
United States dollars. So first we go to our Revolut account and
we copy this, uh, I one,
then we go to here,
main page, go to documents.
Oh yeah, we don't need to go together documents and just click new document.
Like this is the usual way we create invoices,
you know, that. And here we select currency,
not euroes. So usually it's heroes, but here we select US dollars and
here we click edit. So we don't change anything except this thing.
Oh, actually, like we didn't even need to copy.
So yeah, we can just select that we want to have to use the
account, right? So yeah,
you can disregard the first step, uh,
before, so we can just select from the dropdown list.
That's way better, right?
And then you just click save, right?
And that's enough to,
and then yeah, you do the rest as usual, but this is how you
can create an invoice in dollars.
Yeah.
And I think next time you create, you might need to change this back.
Uh, so if invoice is in Euros,
so you need to make sure that, um,
yeah, the here is the main one,
but if it's not Euros, if it's dollars, then it's uh,
Revolut. Mm-hmm.
Yeah. And yeah. Yeah,
because Phenomen model always remembers the last transaction.
So the next time you do, you need to pay attention that it's actually
Euros. So be careful about that to not accidentally send something in dollars when
it has to be indoors. Uh,
perhaps we need to do, uh,
in our process document is the last step that verifi verify that the currency
is correct. And yeah,
perhaps when you finish, uh,
uh, what are you gonna do? Instead of creating a new process document,
you can update the existing one. And there you can,
uh, mention at the beginning you can mention how you select the currency
and how you select the right account, right?
And then there's the last step on that process. You add
validating that, uh, the currency and the account are correct ones.
So please update the existing process document and send it,
um, for check.