Okay, so I played with the prompt a little bit,
uh so here the prompt I also uh
updated them, uh updated the file so when do you record, when you create,
uh sorry, when you create process documents,
make sure that you, uh take screenshots from this updated
one, um so here we have like their,
how to say, it's easy easier to spot them,
I guess, so prompt for correcting,
this is what we did before, prompt for titles,
this is what I created, right, so we copy the prompt
I put the prompt to chat.gpt and hit enter,
now it says yeah, okay, send it, and then I take the entire transcript
and send it to chatgpt, now uhm
yeah, so this is actually, we can already take
this and copy it copy this to to
youtube, right? we will just need to remove
the uh this line breaks,
right? um but okay so this is one thing
that's good we will uh but we already have
a flow for for creating timecodes which we can
reuse so we don't have to copy it here but we can if we
want so then uh
introduction and guest introduction okay yeah we can we can just do this like
it's kind of stupid but like i don't think it anyways
yeah let's not uh spend too much time checking
it so we see that for 147 this
is the title right so what we do here add oops add
the title here if you want you can make a heading i
don't think think that our uhm like
the script that we use for transcribing actually cares whether there is title or
not okay so we added this so for me it will be simple simpler
if i just remove it right so then i it's clear to me what
i added what i did not so 229 we
have it here um right then
uh or 56 I
think here yeah let's use that
so 7.35
Okay, and so on. I think you've got the point,
like 9.03.
Okay, I think I need to tune the prompt, because like,
it's actually too granular,
too small, but you will see changes here in the prompt.
So I'll adjust the prompt, I'll try to ask it to speed to make
not so small sections, uh
yeah, I'll probably adjust that, because right now it's just too,
like, basically every exchange,
uh, it marks as uhm,
yeah, but that's not, that's not important for the video.
I think you get the point, right? So now, now you basically looked,
look at this, uh, point,
uh, let me do it for the next one, right?
So you look at this timestamp, 12.45,
you find it. You it here,
you take the thing,
put it here as a title,
and you do it for all, uhm for all the titles here,
and then you just download as Microsoft Word document,
and then you go through the same process as we did before with PAL,
okay? So this is how we can come up with titles,
I'll tweak the prompt a little bit,
but yeah, so every time you do it, there will be an updated prompt
here, so just take it from here, from uhm from this part,
cause I think I might be tweaking the prompt,
prompts. Okay, so that's it,
uhm let's use it.