If I showed it last time, but before I even create an event,
what I do is I sent and calendar on the white to take
guest. So for that,
um, I go to my calendar calendar and
we plan the event on the 8th of February.
So here, and then I create an event data talks
club. So this event is a webinar,
right? I've been there now for podcasts,
they considered mode. So for podcast event is data talks,
co-op club podcast. So then I
add and guest, I just make a copy,
a copy of the email.
So when you create this, uh, add meat,
so, uh, my name would be in my email will be connect.
See what looks cool or something that was mainly in the future.
And yeah,
here for now,
we can just, okay. Time is,
it starts at 17.
And I usually send to an event for five minutes earlier,
so it will 1655 and then it ends at
18 series zero. So now I click save.
I do not sent yet because they want to add now
a zoom meeting. So I
know they went, so this is theirs. This
is the zoom Euro that we use for,
for connecting. So put it here.
And just in case I also put it in this collection.
So it's clickable and yeah,
by the way, the permission should be that guests can modify events event,
invite others and see guest lists. And this modifier events is mostly
needed for me. So when I do,
uh, when you and me, and then for example,
I need to change something. So then I can do this and
no, we edit the Euro.
So now I click save and then I note sent there,
and this is here that I haven't included a
link here yet.
So awesome. And as you see,
we have events on Tuesdays webinars,
podcasts on Friday, usually. And they are usually at 5:00 PM my time.
Okay. That's a thing called I wanted to show.