Yeah. So this email looks suspicious. You probably saw this as well.
So what I want to show you a score, a,
um, cut, no pictures in this picture.
See, it's not like a head shot it's uh,
so we're in slipped on the, in the, uh,
this part here. And so I want to show you how I
do this, but feel free to use any other week
opportunities, anything. So now I say the image I open
into with, uh, I use XMU,
but
then Nixon, you, you,
um, so you can select a,
like a square and you see, uh,
it shows here this ice office.
So just make sure that it is square.
And then because there are guidelines you can so that,
uh, to make sure that the face is in the center.
Yeah, it should be some 400 by 400 is fine.
Uh, uh, you know, maybe for this bedroom.
And then, uh, the next thing I do is a leap,
uh, first shift X,
then we have a center space and then I do a contrast
shift test to save it MPI it's,
uh, Japan,
and then I save it. So now we have a head shot,
not the rest of the picture.