. Um, yeah. So you saw that,
uh, perfect. Paid partially. I don't know.
For some reasons it's always a problem with them.
Like we probably need to make invoices,
uh, send them invoice and dollars so it's easier.
Um, because what we need to do now is either ask them to pay
500 more, but then it'll always be problems with converting currencies.
So what we can do is we can just take this number mm,
and edit this. So we need to put
here this value
.
All right. And then, uh, here,
wait, this one. But what we also need to do,
so now it's fully paid, uh,
download PDF and send them, uh, send this to perfect saying that,
uh, okay, because of the currency conversion,
uh, we received only this amount.
And to understand that it's a bit of hassle to ask you four or
500 more. So what we do instead is we create an invoice on this
number, uh,
right now. And, um,
this is what we'll use in our tax report.
And if you need, this is the something you can use in your report.
And for the next one, you can also write,
uh, that the next one we will, uh,
uh, let me think. So the next one we will issue in,
uh, esd. So for them it's simpler.
So we will do the conversion or on our side and instead of,
uh, creating invoice for 15,000 euros.
So we'll do the conversion. We'll send them an amount in dollars that
they will need to send to us. And then,
yeah, we'll figure this out on our side.
Okay, that's, uh, all I wanted to,
to say. So perhaps what you can do right now is create
a process document describing how to,
um, retroactively edit the,
um, the invoices.
Then you will need to update the invoice that we have here before
you send the report. So, and then it'll be not partially paid,
but paid. Um,
so it'll in be included on our February report.
And, um, yeah.
Here.
What else? And yeah,
please write an email, uh,
to perfect explaining what, what happened. That's all.