So I want to show you how to actually deal with issues like that
So when we see that something failed,
let me start from the beginning So it fails right and then we
click on this thing and we see where it failed on this tab,
right? And we see that it processed 0 people So ok,
there are So these logs indicate where exactly the problem
is It usually helps us So,
let's see So, processed 0 people,
so there were no problems problems with people And people come from this
tab And here we have this
to add, right? So this is the part that it goes,
it fetches So it fetches all the people People from that you add
And there are zero people So yeah,
it didn't process anything Now it processes books
Then we see that this is the book it tries to process And
it's It's successful But
because it Failed later.
We will need to re-add this book. I'll show you how Okay, but then
we have a process podcast.
So it processes processed zero podcast events.
Again, uhm it comes from podcast here.
There was nothing to process.
If we were to do it, there was nothing to process.
That's why it was zero. And then it tries to process events.
And this is where the error happens,
right? Um, so it says key error email,
whatever, right? So for you,
it's not important which error is,
but that the error is with events.
We see that here.
The last thing, events. So we can go to events,
we can go to to add, and we see that this last thing
is weird, right? So what we're going to do is we can just delete
it, or let's say here the error is that this field
email is empty, right?
And yeah, it's empty because there's nothing.
So if there was an error,
a record with an empty email,
this is what we would see.
But now I will just delete it.
It should solve the problem, though.
It should solve the problem, although there is still one issue,
right? So if we go to to add,
there is nothing. There is empty, right?
Because this thing processed, but because it failed at a later step,
it will not be added. So what we need to do is we need
to go to book of the week and we know from the logs which
book we need to change. So this is
the book from Andy. So we just go to go and change from done
to to do. And now we should be able to
re-execute it. Rename it all,
run workflow, let's see,
I think it's running.
Yeah, so I'll put a pause now and when it finishes I'll
show the results. Okay, it's successful.
Let's take a look at the logs.
So you will see how good logs look like.
So it processed zero people like last time.
Then, okay, now it's running the book.
So this is the description of the book.
So it's processed one book.
Processed zero podcasts, processed zero events.
So, um, I think what we can do is we should create a document
how to debug, um,
this adding, um, content to the website.
Events, podcasts, um,
books, and so on. Uh, and mentioned there
the previous loom that the information from the previous loom that I
added, um,
like we can perhaps. make a link to,
um,
to this loom where I show how to add people like Andy,
right? And yeah, this one. And we will,
like, if more error appears,
we, I, I will take a look and then we can
populate this document. But for now,
at least if there is an error like that,
you should be able to figure it out yourself,
hopefully. Okay,
thank you.