Yeah. So I wanted to show you the thing,
the video, I just sent you the zoom link and it's on recording.
Um, if you go there, you see that there are chat messages.
There are some places where we need to edit them and
you see that, uh, there was, uh, around four minutes,
52 seconds, and then around 20 minutes.
So only YouTube. When you walk the video on YouTube,
you probably know that not only you can remove beginning
of event, but also things in the middle.
So yeah, please checks the, these timestamps and,
uh, pretty much remove some parts from there.
So if you're not certain about some of the things,
just let me know, but he, so for future videos,
I will just try it in chat that edit.
And if you see the chat messages too,
you can check and see that they require somebody to.