Um, hi, I wanted to show you how to update calendar invites.
Every time you create an event in Eventbrite,
a calendar event is created and on Google calendar.
So we have a public public public calendar.
So if you go to Datadog, um,
events, we have this, a Google calendar,
which is a public calendar for everyone to subscribe to the events.
If they let's say don't want to subscribe to Eventbrite,
they just can't get these events in the calendar.
And one of the events that we had,
um, remember you counted, it was a bit longer.
So instead of one hour workshop,
right? And they want to show you how to,
you can edit this events. So this is the events from that calendar.
And I will make sure that you actually have edit permissions.
So you just click it and change it all one hour.
So in this case, it's simple. Sometimes when a guest asks to reschedule,
they went to Google need to do this manually.
This is not a, it's not like if you update something on Eventbrite,
it's automatically updates here. Now it's not like that.
It only creates an event when you create an event in Eventbrite,
but then all the changes afterwards you have to be done manually.
So just pick safe and you see it's um,
yeah, it's updated. So, and then others in the calendar,
in their calendar suppose see the updated.
And now I would just give you a permission.
So next time you will be able to do it yourself as well.