If you ever have a station like this,
so I just want to show you what to do. So it wasn't events.
So a few things, some information, um,
about the event. And then I click save.
Uh, I cannot show you that, unfortunately,
and then it shows me that you hated this event.
So what I do is I just click and get started.
Then I click
when this thing floats and then I click save number eight,
probably continues right now.
Yeah. And then I just say,
no, I don't know why it's doing this.
Sometimes it's sometimes it's doing that sometimes it's not,
but in case you have this problem,
um, yeah, this is what you do. Just click on button set till you
get to this clean again. So what happened is,
uh, what was it?
So it wasn't details here. I was editing this thing and then I click
save and then that's screen up here.
So yeah, if you have something like this,
this is what you do.