Hi. Yeah. I just wanted to talk about this part,
this part. Um, So when we
C
When we make an announcement about the book of the week thing,
Um,
And yeah, usually at the beginning,
we say at the beginning of the week,
we'll say that, uh, yeah,
this thing, and as a separate message,
you can say that in a dish to
the motion, You
can ask her Name and then just
put
This thing.
This shouldn't be actually like
Something like this, And this is what you do that
you shouldn't do that. So maybe when you probably schedule this as your schedule
Check,
When you say custom time, they can schedule one,
or I don't know, seven 30 and then the next
one, it will be seven 30.
One that is if you schedule it,
but then they kind of come one after another.
I don't know what actually happens if you schedule them at the same time,
if they will come in the same order, maybe they will.
I don't know. But yeah, this is what you need to do when you
now, please, if they provided these questions or this extra things
Now, so please suggest the,
this process document to improve that.