I figured this would be interesting to see too,
how to extract images from um um luma in
a general uh uh preview from any website so let's see
let's say we want to extract a preview Uh,
the one we see here uh from this page right.
I use Google promising Google from.
You go here, click inspect.
And you see the code for um the website.
You go to head. And in head
you look for uh tech called
meta name. Can I make it larger?
No, I cannot. So it's meta name equals image
property. See. Oh go. Oh g image.
So it's usually one of those.
Right. And the content.
Yeah double click on this. And this is the link.
That you can use.
can also see that this is specific to luma.
Um for our other websites it won't work.
We can also change the width and height here.
So for example if we want to have a larger image,
we can say can make it two times larger,
1,600. And here it would be 800.
Let's see if we can see.
this would give us a larger image.
There we can see this, right?
But this is specifically to Luma,
right? So other websites will not have that.
Other websites will just give us some that we can use for.
So yeah please create a process document for that.
Sometimes we might need just to extract the preview to
use it somewhere.