And just wanted to show you how to feel in sponsored book sponsored
book. So here with the visual.
So I just downloaded it, the visual.
So no, I click Show it from the beginning.
So I click here on the image upload image.
Excellent. And then I go to downloads and I
said, look, this is the image that they sent. So you just click open
And next. So bill sent me the link.
Yeah.
Oh yeah. The link goes here as well to the
button. So it goes both to then image into the backend
Here. This will be the title,
The title.
So you just paste it And
some texts. Yeah.
So this is the text. I will change the text
Later, but for now,
for example, I ask you to help. You can just, and
then like for something.
So for example, if there is no visual, you can just leave visual field.
If there is no title, you don't know what the title should be just
field. And if you don't know what the text should be,
you just feel text on attention. And then I can think,
So this is how you feel this in the sponsored
blog, That's all.