Um, I wonder the show you call this speaker pro speaker,
not speaker the event form.
So, um, this, this, I just sent you the link.
So I want now to add to the form,
uh, the first field is speaker email,
email email here,
then tight
and bright. Eileen is this thing here in
the Euro. Um,
you can also get it if you vote, you haven't bright slash my events.
So it has the list of all the events.
And let me say this, the amount here,
corporate know, uh,
it cost to your, um,
well, well you can paste it now.
And then it quite basic to my,
uh, others Euro bar. I get this and I'm interested in this number,
this number, and this number is the same
number.
Uh, I just need to paste it here. So this event is a podcast
and date is a 3rd of March,
right? And so
let's call you submit events. And then using this information,
I will be able to publish events on the website.
And of course, this is important that for this form,
um, the speaker is already there.
So you're already thinking you already created the profile for the speaker,
because if you don't do this, then I will not be able to find
the speaker, uh, in,
uh, in the database. And then I will not be able to create another.
So first you fill in the speaker form,
and then if you, in the event for.