We have a few payments to Finansamt.
Finansamt is a tax office in Germany.
So, this is when I need to pay taxes. I need to transfer a
lot of money to them. I transferred some money today and
some money last month. I wanted to show you how I
put them right now into this.
Scratch it. So, right now I created a new tab here called taxes.
And I put,
like, all this all these payments there just to keep track in
one place, causing, you know, it might get lost or whatever.
And the way I do this, so, if I click here,
it says what kind of tax.
I paid it's giverbistor. There are two types of taxes.
This, the first one giverbistor. And the second one is this,
I'm commenstor. So, I took these things and I put them there.
So, this is here, giverbistor here,
commenstor here. So, this is the money I paid last.
For 2022. And this is the money I paid today.
So, right now I need to pay like, quarterly.
For some reason in this year, it's every,
it's not every quarter, but only second,
third and fourth quarter. Anyways,
so next time you see a payment to finance out.
Here in the you can just put it there.
, in this in
this thing. Yeah. It was like, for example,
if our accountants ask if we paid something or we did not pay
how much and so on, you can refer to this table,
to this spreadsheet and tell them, okay.
That's all. So maybe you can create a small process document that
describes that, but for now you at least know what this
what these records are and where we should put them in the spreadsheet.
Yeah. That's it.