Another thing I wanted to talk about. So I noticed that you asked me,
sir,
So, you know, hear me, sir. So you said present us view and link.
So we get caught up LinkedIn, Twitter and others. So I want to make
it a little bit easier for the guests.
So I already, it's actually pretty easy to Google fittings,
so I just speak her name And
Type it in and then only see the LinkedIn account,
but it doesn't work for everyone, of course. And,
uh, yeah, you know,
it's quite easy that for example, you needed
it. So then I just put this card and then we find,
Um, so what are we going to do is,
uh, or Let me open the template.
So here are the links. So when we clone the template,
we can try to look up speakers.
So just do the same thing and,
uh, Yeah.
And to find the links to LinkedIn.
Um, so with the website, it could be a little bit more difficult,
but sometimes it's for example. So for me, It's very easy because
it shows like this personal page, not everyone has this.
Sometimes you need to ask separately,
but yeah, so typically you just Google the name of the person and then
you can already find the thing.
So, um, think you can add this to the
practice document when you create this podcast page.
The one I just asked you, So this one,
Um,
Yeah, so this one, um,
so you can add it to the same process document,
or I don't know, maybe create another document that describes how
to find to profiles And then a few of
them in. And then the next thing you need to do is modify your
temp or the template we sent This template.
And, um, instead of please send us your view and links.
So we still need to be home. It's not always easy to find,
um, and picture your picture.
Um, we don't,
we can just ask, and then we can say,
we found some of your profiles. So your profile,
LinkedIn Teeter, we can mention them say,
we've found some of your profiles, please check the page to verify that they
are correct. And for example,
if we didn't find a little place, you can say, if you have a
personal, what patient do you want us to add it?
Please let us know what it is. Yeah.
So this is how you will look up people's profiles
on the internet. And sometimes,
actually when I sent you, um,
contact information of people to contact them,
we already have their LinkedIn. So since we already have their LinkedIn,
there's no reason to ask cold LinkedIn because we already have it.
Let me just go. I actually got in touch, I think with Mr.
So yeah, please modify the template and let's do some preparation work and
few in these as much as we can before asking speakers to do that.
And I think he'll.