So we, we received the payment, we received the payment from SDB.
So I just throw it to cost. You probably saw this cost.
Yeah. So just saw that we, the payment,
this is something you also do.
I actually don't know if you see this, if you get some sort of
where notification, uh, yeah.
Maybe we can actually, uh, make sure you get some email when we get
a payment anyways. Uh,
yeah. So this is the payment,
but it's not linked to an invoice.
So actually there, there should be some sort of link.
They did not include any,
they didn't include invoice ad. That's why it wasn't automatically linked.
Uh, usually it is linked. So for example,
um, let's take this one. So the one from infrastructure lines.
So they marked in invoice here.
So there was like it automatically attached to document invoice.
So it knew that the invoice, uh,
was paid. So here we need to do this manually.
I'll show you how to do this. Um,
yeah, so go to this payment and then attach document,
and then we just select one of the invoices.
So this one, mines DB, Inc.
So yeah, this is how we attach the invoice.
And now we know that this invoice was actually paid you
that's here invoice.
So now that's how
you attach invoices to payments.