Hi everyone, in this video I want to show my course project Fitness
Assistant and before I talk about
this I just want to show it in action.
So I run it and this is an application to which
I can talk about different exercises.
So for example I can ask, what are possible
alternatives to write Romanian deadlift
and then based on the
data it has about exercises which is this one.
So there's 206 different exercises
classified by type of activity,
type of equipment, body part,
type, whether it's pull or push exercise,
which muscles are used and how to perform the exercise.
Based that it recommends different exercises.
So for example possible alternatives to the Romanian deadlift include deadlift,
dumbbell deadlift, kettlebell deadlift and so on.
Right and then I can give feedback that this is a positive answer and
I can continue talking to this how do I do push-ups.
Right and then based on the data it gives me an answer how do
I do this. So, this is the app, and this that
I built and right now I want to talk about how
to run this app. So everything that we need is
in this repo of course and yeah
here we have the instructions. I started
I thought I started a github cospace let me
see if I still have it
yeah it's a fresh one there
is nothing so
let's now let me now walk you through preparing everything
so I will Now stop.
things on my computer so then ports are not occupied
when I do this and yeah
it needs some time to open
and let me open the readme or I can just get the readme
from here and we just need to follow the instructions in this
readme. So the first thing is we need to get the OpenAI I
will do that so we need to copy
this thing and create a well this is not what I wanted
to do so I needed to rename this right and
now we need to put our OpenAI key. I will put it on on
pause put the key and then close it so I don't accidentally expose the
key. So now the key is there.
And I want to, install DRENV which is a tool for
loading this A and FRC files.
So do apt update.
So first I need to because this is a freshly created instance I need
to download all the information about packages and then install
DRENV. And then after installation I need to
install the hook.
can now when I create a new terminal it prompts
me to allow DRENV to
run allow and load the key.
So now I have the key and now I can go to the next
step which is installing PPENF. PPENF is the tool for managing dependencies
that we use in this project. So,
this is, these are all, all the dependencies we have here and
here. So right now it will,
we have PPENF now and I will run PPENF install dev.
So then we install not only these dependencies that are needed for running the
application but also some dev dependencies that we need for developing
like Jupyter Notebook and other things.
Okay, so it will take us some time.
In the meantime, I will continue doing
the next step which is running Docker Compose.
Right now in Docker Compose we have three components.
The application itself, Postgres and Grafana.
Last two things we need for logging
and monitoring. So now I need to configure Postgres.
Here, I will, just execute that.
Yeah, so we did not do dir-env-hello,
but OpenAI key is only needed for the application.
It's not needed for Postgres.
So let's see what we need to do next. Yeah,
okay, it's running and we have installed
all the dependencies. So I will do pip-env-shell.
So now I enter the virtual environment.
And I can do go to fitness assistant and
we need to do this.
So then I can connect from my host machine,
which is code spaces, to the container and
initialize the database. Okay,
the database is initialized.
Then you can also check that the database is there.
I will skip that part.
And I will just run the entire thing by
doing docker compose up. So it
might take some time to run it because it needs to build the
application using this docker file. I will now put
it on pause and then when it starts,
when it finishes and starts, I'll continue.
So it seems to be running,
so now. Now I want to check the logs quickly.
So now Grafana is doing a lot of stuff.
Let me go all the way up.
Yeah, let me just open a new terminal and do
docker ps to see docker
logs. Yeah,
it seems to be working. So let me run ppcpk.
and pipenv run python cli.py
and now I can ask my question which could be um
what I can do instead of a pull-up.
So instead of pull-up you can perform a banded pull-up where your loop resistance
bands, the band around a pull-up bar.
Okay, I think this is a good answer and I don't want
to continue. Now I just want show how to set up Grafana so
then we can see how monitoring works.
All right, so I go back and then scroll
all the way down to
monitoring here. So Grafana should be accessible
here. Probably I need to forward the port
here. So now let's see.
Yeah, it is accessible. The default username and password
are admin admin. I don't want to replace it so let's just
keep it. Right now we don't have any data sources and dashboards so we
need to import the data source and the dashboard.
All the Grafana-related stuff is here.
There is this init script that allows us to simply import
the data source and the dashboard. So I need to do this inside
the virtual environment again. So I do pipenv shell.
So then I go to Grafana.
I want to make sure that because remember when we initialized the database we
needed to set Postgres host to localhost because
Grafana will connect to Postgres within Docker Compose.
It needs to have the original name Postgres,
not localhost. I need to make sure that um
that we don't overwrite it. So write Postgres here.
I can see that Postgres host is Postgres.
So this is good. This is what we expect. And right now I will
just do Python init. it. Okay.
Right now, what I did is created the data source and it created the
a dashboard. Right.
Now I can just simply refresh it and go to dashboards
and see our dashboards.
So right now, not much uh has been happening.
But I can test
it. So let me go one level up.
And I'll just run tests. So what test is doing is just selecting the
random question. . . and then sends it to you.
The delegation and then returns the answer.
So I can run multiple tests.
So each time there is a different uh question like can you explain the
proper form for doing handling. Knee raises.
So right now if I refresh.
Yeah. So I see a partner element.
Umm.
What is that? What muscles are primary engaged during the incline?
and don't.
I don't know why it's partly relevant.
Maybe because um it has some information about the muscles
that are engaged and things that are actually other muscles.
I don't know. Umm.
There is probably uh we should have an explanation in the database we just
don't show it here. Umm.
Okay. Maybe we can actually include that.
Right now just to see what
is uh the explanation and I just need to quickly
see the name. Really not the explanation.
So I'll apply that. And.
But includes four arms as well. Which is secondary muscle.
Uhm. Yeah. I guess.
So the thing is like uhm it already knows about fitness a lot.
Uhm. That's why I mean it says the part that I don't.
But this is good, right? So then we have some uh
interesting stuff to show. Okay. So this was my project.
I hope you enjoyed it.
And you can read more about how it's implemented and what kind of technology
is used. used. In this readme file. Okay.
That's all from me. Thanks for your attention.