Uh, hi. So with this video, we still have the problem of delayed sound.
So if I go
Here like Ang and Vs, which
Is like Unsynchronized for some reasons,
um, there is back on YouTube and it takes,
uh, it's already been since Friday, right?
So when this problem proceeds,
and now it's Tuesday, right?
So like it's been for four days. And when we go here to edit,
we see that like an editor,
Uh,
Yeah, they say
in the video, this event is brought to you by Databox Club,
which is a community of people.
And that was the real value, not
The, I have no idea why this is happening.
Um, and here,
yeah, that's really weird.
This is one isn't Shimer bag.
Yeah. So what I do in these cases,
I figured this out, is when we download the video,
Um,
So I can just go to, uh,
here's this download. Uh, I don't think it works.
So I go to studio,
studio content and here live and
here I click this thing and download,
right? So then it downloads the video. And when I download the video,
it's actually, hi everyone, welcome to our event
From [Inaudible]. You
See, it's, uh, I'm wondering how did it happen that you managed to sell
something, to sell an idea? What I,
and then what I do next is I applaud it.
So like the usual process of uploading, you know,
how to do this and, uh,
yeah. Here, here,
yeah. So this is the usual, uh,
process of applauding, uh, and then the title is the same.
Fix it. Uh, I,
oops, I'll just put here note,
fix it. Sound right.
And then, um, so we,
let me download the picture from here.
Yeah, it's kind of not good. Uh, but yeah,
like you probably would, uh, use a different picture in the one that is
larger.
So
Let me just take, uh,
yeah, why it's not good. But,
uh, yeah, please. Uh, yeah,
I don't think we, I should actually use this one.
Uh, let me
See if we have this. I'll put it on pause for for a second.
Okay. I don't, uh,
know how to find it. I probably should download it from Evan Bright,
but this is how I usually do this.
Okay, so I downloaded the video. So then I put playlist data,
data doc club, podcast. Um,
now here you should put the links from here.
Uh, yeah, we don't have the links. Uh, by the way wise,
we still don't have links. We should have links here.
But yeah, please add the links once we have there.
Please update, um, the
description. Um,
and then what I do next is, uh,
my occasional stuff organization is off.
Uh, then visibility.
Yeah, off. Okay,
sorry, I got distracted. So here we select public.
So the video is public and the rest,
I don't think we need to do anything. I mean,
you'll need to update description and update a thumbnail,
but the rest we don't need to change.
And yeah, just publish it.
And then we get the link from here,
copy the link and I go here,
I think. Yeah, here,
uh, dated version in description.
So you add a note here and then
You put here updated insertion with description editing
here. Then you remove it from the playlist and you make
it unlisted and save it.
Alright? All right. So this is how you do it.
And then for everything we use this link,
not this one. So this is the old livestream
Of, uh, of, of the
Com with bad sound. But yeah,
we use,
Hmm,
Why? It's not edit.
Yeah, probably they didn't put it yet.
It's public. It should be in the channel. Yeah,
I think it'll appear now here. So then for all the future stuff,
like when we upload the podcast,
et cetera, we use this new version,
right? Uh,
yeah, it'll appear here right now. So this is how we handle this station.
When after, I don't know,
three, four days, the old version is still,
uh, has problems. We can re-app upload it,
uh, and add the link here,
right? So yeah, this is how we do it.