I want to show you how to generate generate time
codes from transcripts.
So here I'm
hearing the transcript.
So this is the transcript.
So now I don't want it
to have a 10, my download folder.
So open it. Um,
yeah. Now I need to rename it. So I need to know what kind
of name I should give it. So go to our schedule
document, and then, yeah,
please. Don't forget to add spaces here.
So this is the podcast
for which we add. And then what I do is,
so there's a season seven episode, six
episode six is four months,
and then the name is Amy tests. So this is the name of
this document. And then I go to this transcript
details. I already edit.
So I'm sorry, I'm in the code now.
So go to docs folder,
and here I click add file and upload
the file. Then I
go to the final edge of the loaded. It should be in this format.
So click open, and then I can
change this. So now the file is uploaded and
no, all this,
uh, refresh it. So now I need to go to auctions and
connections. I see that now they have to think,
I just edit this, add files,
the upload. So it is doing something.
And so you see now it's green and what happened
is now you come back to tasks and now you
go to task and now this file appeared there.
So it was automatically added. So what happens is when
you add a file to this folder,
to the equivalents, when you upload this,
there an action that is automatically ticket that analyzes
this document document,
and then it clicks. So then you go to this transcript,
you copied this, and then you called and
then YouTube.
Yes.
Yeah.
This is a list of topics that we talked about.
Then I save now there's
time coats
all the time quotes are here, groups.
Yeah. So they are here. Now I know that you also
already scheduled podcast episodes.
So because that time available when you were killing
them, and now we can add the time quotes,
let me go two episodes.
And this one I'll give you
details and then edit.
Hmm. Yeah.
That's an edge. And
then the list of things from here.
Yeah. Usually it is finding somebody online because
we talked about that every episode,
because that's the list that we put now to anchor and
to use control sheets. If I just do control
V yeah.
It doesn't do any work. Yeah.
Anyways. Yeah. I also noticed that the
Links placed it and not right.
So you see that this thinks here,
so I think you copied it from,
from here because there are these dots.
You actually need to copy this from the description when you click.
So the links are all there.
Um, yeah. So let me do this right now.
Let me fix it. So I copied and
cool and replace it.
And now I need to this next.
Yeah, I think it's fine.
So clickable Davis and
tiny too, to make sure it's still scheduled.
It's scheduled for 7:00 PM.
So, so yeah, this is how you get 10 codes.
So you use this transcript details. You put this upload a file to topics
and then to docs, and then it automatically appears in this folder
after.