Yeah, there was an invoice from MailChimp.
I wanted to show you, um, how to,
Um,
Not invoice, but email. You probably saw it,
right. So I forwarded it to you. Um,
you should receive it. I also wanted to show you how to get these
invoices from, from MailChimp.
So you go to MailChimp.
I actually don't know if I already showed you this video or not.
Um,
In case I haven't, this is how you do it in case I did,
then you can just ignore it. So go to accountant billing and
here, uh, it seems I need to upgrade it,
but for now, uh, I wanted to show you building history
and it was today.
It became cheaper actually. Yeah.
I think it became cheaper because, um, of taxes.
Right. So now, uh, I don't pay some taxes that I used to pay,
which is very good news for me then,
uh, yeah. Click on the,
And
yeah,
Indeed are not access really cool.
Yeah. I think because now taxi,
uh, it doesn't matter. Okay. So,
uh, right now what we do is just click print and then
we'll print it and then you send it to that
folder or to do that email.
Right. And then fill everything in, in the,
um, in the spreadsheet.
So that's one of the options or, uh, so because if I say here's
the email I got from MailChimp, um,
Or
Something like this, uh, so then you can go here and then save the
invoice. Okay. Yeah. So this is how you save invoices from MailChimp.
This is how you get invoices from MailChimp.