Hi, I'm just wanted to show you how to answer emails like that.
So we'll need your help, but with the,
with the answer, um,
so the male asks about information,
about performance of the complaint they run with us.
So basically this promoted, um,
this promoted, uh, uh,
ads, uh, this promoted section in the email.
Um, so they ask about 90 ML and that was,
um, let me find it,
I think it was
this one, perhaps
74, 4 73.
Yeah. So you see this nanny MLS here,
so they are interested in a number of clicks,
um, from the campaign still we can,
uh, tell us your 187
people clicked on the article and then 125
people clicked on, um,
on their link to their website. Then we also,
I think we had to,
we posted it on social media,
so we should go to Twitter
and then in data docs, club profile.
And, um, now I'll try to find it.
I think this is the one, right.
Um, Lytics.
So yeah, you can tell her that I'm like,
okay, let me find you how to properly find it.
Uh, yeah, let me just that one. So
analytics number of impressions and clicks.
So you can tell  on social media
and then on LinkedIn, I think we also have this on LinkedIn,
so 10 then go to the company,
then find it.
Okay. It wasn't well, okay, here it is. And then you click controls
that and then will tell her that it had this many impressions
and that many clicks, and then we can just send all this information to
care. Um, I think she's also asking,
uh, about, uh, YouTube videos,
600 views, but I don't know what kind of information she needs there.
So maybe you can just ask her okay.
That's all. And, uh, yeah, in the future,
there will be similar requests from others.
Um, I will ask you to help me answer them.