Yeah. Found it. So this is, let me show you how to get there.
Still. We go to their organization club and
then here, this
is for one month, the last 30 days,
I guess, because it's relatively new.
Right? And then we have this, uh, upgrades and then one of these candidates
is this one open source,
blah, blah, blah. And then one of the things here is
this one number of kicks.
Yeah. This is number of clicks. So we'll have 33 clicks.
Um, I think what is also interesting maybe is the number of impressions.
So let me open Twitter again.
I'll show you how to find it so we can
keep them like a,
so this one had 2000 impressions.
So
use the compression view and the same thing.
So then LinkedIn will have number of impressions
and then just put there
that's the open rate, basically complaints
now, but you already know how to, you see how many people opened it.
Okay.
And then now we can just sound this up.
Oops. This one,
this one. So
this would be the total number of impressions.
And let me see.
So I'll do the same exercise now with clicks plus
11 plus 33.
Yeah. So we can follow this format where we share the performance.
So number of views, number of clicks. Yeah.
Let me, because I think this is a little bit to,
because it's a high number and clicks is a lot less somebody misleading
again. That's all I want.