So I wanted to show you how I follow up with past clients.
So these companies, Norco, uh,
these two people, he's actually not,
so I already was in touch with them,
so they ran a newsletter with us, I think it was,
um, a couple of months ago in the summer.
So they had a conference and we were helping them,
uh, promote the conference. Doesn't matter.
So I wanted to touch base with them again and see what theyre,
So Dev John and there is some other
guy, Robert I who, but he was also in cc.
Um, so I want to, uh,
them again and see if they would be interested in,
uh, doing something else, Uh,
something more. So yeah,
we can probably turn this into a template.
So here it would be, uh,
personalized line and this we can probably
keep for all the, all the plants.
Yeah. And the C is Kel. Yeah,
I, uh, just added them to companies here.
We, uh, it's actually one of the companies I asked to,
Yeah, Kel. So this is one of the companies that they asked you
to add. So I saw that they sponsored the conference.
They were sponsor, so probably they have money,
so that's why I wanted to ping them and see if they would be
interested in any ation. Yeah.
So please create process doc for,
um, itching out to past clients,
I guess. Um, something like this.