I realize she's also asking for other things,
um, these Daniel's test may be,
uh, you can see them here,
like the swamp is,
so, yeah, well, just for that, um,
so you see like this, this complaint on 9th of May,
this was actually when we sent, uh, think about nanny.
Um, let me just quickly check that or,
yeah, that was a response. So she is asking what's on this
focus campaign,
Gosh,
On this campaign, uh, how many open,
what was the open rate and click rate? So you can say that a
nine thousand nine thousand six hundred people.
So it also open rate was 30%.
And then this is how many clicks and the click rate was 2%.
And then you can also show the numbers for,
for, for their, uh,
for their links and their links of asset. Uh,
this one and this one, I don't think we have other
links. Okay.
Yeah. That's uh, that's it. So for this complainant,
uh,