I just wanted to show you how to schedule payments.
So we have usual payments but some payments are occurring and for example
this one that we got from our accountants.
So they ask for monthly
payment of this amount,
right? So they say from this day to this
day we have already paid the first one.
So I want to show you how we can schedule at that That,
Infinum. So Infinum,
because we already paid umm.
So we already paid umm for January so there is no need to
do January anymore. So we start from February.
I first of all, yeah, I fill it in.
Then I click here schedule and make it regular and frequency is monthly
and then start date is first of February and date is
end of December. And they say the payment will be made every month until
blah blah blah included the starting from February 1.
This is 11 times so this is exactly what we need.
Out of 12 we paid once so we need 11 and
yeah and the reason for payment as usual is
the invoice number right.
So now I can just click continue and click schedule and
then now I confirm it. Confirm
and now it is scheduled.
So I don't think it will happen often but at least in one year
when they sent an invoice. We want you to do this and I'll just
forward you this email. Google is quite good at translating
German but I think it's more or less clear what's happening here.
Yeah we already have here in our
uhh address book.
So yeah. Okay that's how we
schedule regular payments.
Thanks for watching!