Hi, so Valeria pointed out that there is a typo in the name,
so I wanted to show you how to fix that.
So we go to our website in GitHub repo,
which is this one, and we go to this
underscore podcast directory. And we here we find,
when it loads, we find the podcast
episode. So for us, I think it's this one.
Other ones for everyone, right? So we go there.
And here we click on this edit as well.
And now we just need to find this and replace,
I think, yeah, here this is the transcript.
So let me check if this one is correct.
The part, let me open it.
So in the transcript, we usually,
like for each line, we want to show who is the speaker.
Yeah, so here there is also a mistake.
So it should be Miriam, not Miriam.
And this actually, like we can, of course,
detect this before we upload.
We can also use the transcript here, so we can ask Pavel to fix
that. But now it's kinda late. And now I want to see how we,
So right now I pressed Ctrl F and we have this
part, right? So what I want to do is to get medium
and replace it with medium.
And you see it highlights already.
I don't know why there's,
Yeah, there's also should be brackets.
But yeah, this is less important. So basically
here we can change everything in this,
In this document.
And all these changes that we do will be reflected in this page.
So basically this is the source code for that page.
And right now I will just,
Yeah, it highlights all the changes and,
I click replace all. And let's say if there was one,
One typo, right? Just one place with the mistake.
We can find this place somewhere here and just go and,
Change it. I don't know. Let's say there is a typo.
Here, Maria Magris. And then,
yeah, we change it. So this is how you find the podcast page
in our GitHub repository. This is how you edit
changes. This is how you, So, I'm going to replace typos in the
name and this is how you replace,
I don't know, maybe, let's skip it with square brackets,
this is how you just replace things in
the transcript. Now I just click commit changes,
like commit message, and you can just leave it like that,
and press commit, so now it updates the
page. And in a few minutes
this page will be updated,
when of course it actually saves.
Okay, so this is how you do this.