It's cold emails of those who registered to events and put
them to MailChimp. So caught you in the parade,
my events. And then this is usually pestilence
fast. Let's take this one career question.
The last one take on this.
Then we have this attendee summary click on
this
and then report resolved ESE.
So usually cope with CSV. Excel, I guess works fine as well.
So then I click on this thing. I use limber office,
but I guess Microsoft Excel and do the same thing and distribute account.
So documents in Libra office then.
Yeah, I just click. Okay.
And then I have this emails of those scored,
it just threat for the event. And some of them here,
the column is, do you want to subscribe to data talks,
newsletter and receive updates? So some people don't and that's fine,
but we want to select those who did, uh,
who do want to subscribe. So for that,
I do view, uh,
I think, yeah, data out the filter.
And then here, I just see that there is this dropdown list.
So then I select here I unselect.
No. So there is only yes, and I click,
okay. So we have now on get those one to subscribe and
now I select them sort
of controls here. Then I paste them to some editor.
And the important thing here is we need to check the context to identify
people who would not want to subscribe and here.
So I check the number. So here,
the total number is 52 and I have one of the 13.
So it seems so key. So usually around a half one to,
um, subscribe, and then I go to MailChimp.
So let me start with the main page of mailchimp.com.
Then I click login and
then they go to your audience, this audience,
and then my niche audience hit import contacts.
So I want to copy paste.
And then there's just what we took from the form from the Excel
file. So we've heard from a bunch of females here,
continue to organize. And then what I do here,
subscribe then update my existing contacts and then
search for tax tax is event,
then continue to match and finalize and then complete import.
And then now it will say, how many, so the six new
contacts and 24,
or it's correct. If there are more than 100 emails
on that list, you will not see that you will see only four and
these with 100 or less, then you contact.
We see these people here and they
have this, a listing Burt, I think.
Yeah. And we can actually check if one of them it's not important to,
but there should be some automation on it. Now that doesn't work
yet, but there will be a mail to them saying,
Hey, thanks for attending your events.
Here's a link to join us.
Okay. That's all. This is how you import people from Eventbrite
to mail.