I also wanted to show you a conversation with,
uh, that I've had with one of the speakers.
So she reached out to me saying that she wants to give a talk
and then we get some, the topic trying
to scroll
Australian works. So we agreed to that topic.
And then, yeah, I told her that we have two types of events and,
uh, we decided to go with webinars and then I
proposed the date to start saying that,
uh, yeah, so we have this lot.
And, uh, I,
well, after that, I said that we need to talk offline.
So basically all the information that we need for a publishing event.
So I told you all that, and you will also need to do that.
So will, you will need to ask the speakers to do
provide this information. And this is something you will be there,
put in the form. And I ask your email because she was reaching to
me through slack. Um, but I think sometimes
it makes email makes more sense. Um,
and then, yeah, we agree on day and
yeah, so now she sent it and then,
um, so she sent him a title and then I propose to change the
title and I propose to change a little debut a little bit.
So the view was I am,
and then I asked her to speak about you're in the third form,
a person, you know,
meaning good place I have with sheet.
And also give me your full name and your email.
She still hasn't sent me email. And then,
yeah. So there's other things I asked her to do.
So she gave that, um,
and I saw that one of the things was missing so that we also
need a subtitle. So if you see this as an event,
page of maybe testing and,
uh, this, that at all, we got some title and then outline of payments.
So she didn't provide a subtitle. So I asked her to give that,
and then wait, you will have a form like,
or people or books that you will need to put,
to use to put all this information there in the form,
or actually, no, you will not need to put this in the form because
you will need to put this in, right? Yeah,
that's right. So you will need to put this to Eventbrite and,
uh, we'll use seven brands or for these things.
And then after this announced to know Evan bread,
then you will need to put this in the form, but I will now
make a separate video about that. So yeah.