Hi, so I started looking into integrating like
doing this sort of integration we have, we had with Eventbrite,
where when we create an Eventbrite event,
it would automatically publish a message in Slack.
And, what else?
And create an entry in a Google Calendar. Alright.
So we wanted to do something similar for Luma,
and it seems like in Luma it works through calendars.
So I created a calendar. This data talks club events.
And you are an admin.
I sent you an invite. And here,
every time you create an event in Luma, you can edit.
Here. So this is how you add an existing one.
So add existing Luma events and then you just,
well, submit them, right? So this is how you create a
existing events, which we already have,
right? And then you can also create a new one.
So here when you click on element, yeah,
create a new event and then you can just do it
from here. It's like you can select it,
you know, whether you create it like from personal calendar or date of events,
right? So then you create it from here.
I don't know if what you see when
you create like other events. Same or not.
If it's different and you prefer the other way of creating,
then instead of just creating it like now,
yeah, we can just add first create an event in Luma and then
add it. But it's important that we add it because this way now
I can use, ah,
the integration from here to Zapier and from Zapier to
other platforms. Okay.
So, please document it.