But I wanted to show you is how to add people support.
Yeah. So how to invite people to slack.
So Miller, who is the, uh,
author of who is an offer of a book,
or like, he'll be doing the book of the week thing next week.
So I want to make sure that he is in slack for that.
I will need to do the same thing I did with you.
So I need to invite him. And the best thing is I'm.
So here, clicking here,
then invite people to data talks club and then put in the email and
then it kicks out and yeah.
So now he is invited. Oh yeah.
So this is how you invite people and then I'll write him
a little, I just in buy or stock,
please check your email. Yeah.
So this is how I do this.