Okay. So many people now have problems joining slug.
That's why I could eat this form.
They feel their email here, and we get data
here in, so let me show you how to get here.
So when you log into it, they will give you see this.
And then one of the things here is the scene right there.
And this is the first thing,
and these are the emails. So
Let me add, um,
You don't want to do this right now,
just for us to remember who invited them,
who we did not.
And what you can do now is take The
person here, Then go to Splunk
And then it's luck
Luck.
And what square Lucky usually.
Anyway, and then you sent,
I think you can select multiple names,
say up the town Newport here.
Um, and then we're set.
Okay. Some of them actually, because they already joined and
some of them,
And now this, once you Make
them done, so you just press the copy control C to copy this  was
done. Um,
so Yeah,
please invite the rest of them and I'll tell you if we
need to invite more.
Um, I will ask.