i think southern cloud paid the invoice anyway so this is not what i
wanted to show you here i wanted to show you how to in
invoices how do we specify the discount cost like there in the invoice
you sent where it is now
let me load it okay so okay
so the problem with this is that uh it's five slots but the quantity
is one it kind of looks ugly like in the previous case with the
double cloud like it was kind of weird to split it into two
uh places well we could have done this like promotion in
this letter then five or six emails and log on the website
with code zero we could have done that right anyways
so we the way we will do this the way we can do this
is new
document invoice and
then here we can say newsletter
and the price is uh the usual price 6
emails,
email, right?
And then we can add a discount.
Which would be 100,
or, Alright,
it's fine. Right,
so this is how we could do it, could do it with uhm uhm
with quack, because in this case it's clear that we're making
it. We're making a discount, so let's say if somebody is uhm I don't
know in their team maybe there's a new person,
let's say look like this was the price previously,
we could say that was a discount like this.
But here you see that on the uh on the invoice,
so this is this way it's more explicit that we are giving an explicit
discount because they are getting a large quantity.
So please do it like that.
I want your,