Hi. So I asked you to find somebody to do open source spotlight with
this company, Milano. So this is the GitHub Neuro,
and then actually in this GitHub, when scrolling down,
I saw that they have a Slack community. So sometimes they have Slack communities.
Some of the companies have Thisor community.
This is pretty similar. If you haven't used Thisor,
maybe I can show, I can record another separate video for that.
But what I, so I saw that they have a Slack community,
so I just joined this. So I clicked on this thing and then I
registered it in Slack. You have done this multiple times?
I think so. I am in their slack already.
And what I want to do in, now, instead of going through list of
committers, I just want to ask that in Slack.
So I want to say, so that they have this introductions channel,
I think most of the, um,
most of, um, Slacks, Slack communities have this introduction channel.
So here we say a few words about,
um, like people who join, we say a few words about ourselves.
So now I will type something and then you'll see it.
Okay. So I just put this on post and then type this message.
So, hi everyone, my name is um, [Inaudible],
myself, and then you can write. So my name is Francis and I'm a
community manager at Data Doc Club. And you can say we recently run across
company name and it looks really cool.
So I was wondering if you'd be interested in them in the project for
our community members. And then,
yeah, I wanted to add a link to our YouTube channel,
um, Open Source Spotlight playlist.
So we have this playlist where is open
source spotlight? Can see, Oh,
here it is, right? So this is the open source spotlight playlist.
So I just copied and past it here.
So something like that. Yeah,
actually, I don't know if it's appropriate. I'll see companies say like how they
react to this because it's like, uh, instead of,
so previously the way we are doing, we were doing this,
we were finding people from this company and contacting this,
but here we are asking the open, Hey, who from you want to do
a demo, right? Mm. Yeah.
I think that they should not mind.
Let's see. But um, yeah,
in general, this is another approach.
And or for finding speakers for specific products,
uh, for open source spotlight. Yeah,
that's it. Oh yeah, of course I need to send it.
Okay.