Do you keep reaching out to people and be more organized?
I think what we can do is use the slits,
uh, stable, um,
can use a spreadsheet that I just created in this schedule spreadsheet.
So this is what I would send to you and say,
Hey, please, uh, every child,
and so does to do a workshop,
for example. And then, um,
what it can do is take this thing here to link,
right? So then they'll have a link and then you see,
you see that this is the name of elite.
So it is somebody who for,
will want to the child. And, uh, just to give a talk or I
don't know, do a book of the week thing.
So then event type in this case is workshop and workshop and webinars
are essentially the same things.
Um, and,
um, yeah, you probably saw like the document that I sent you,
uh, that, uh, there is also this workshop and then LinkedIn,
um, so LinkedIn email,
and then maybe we can ride starters, uh,
sent a connection,
request, something like this. So then we know that,
um, yeah,
maybe we need to follow up with her.
Perhaps we need to use something like CRM,
but we're going to do this later for now.
I can just go with this spreadsheet to make sure we don't
forget that.