Hi. So I wanted to show you how to get invoices from LinkedIn.
I don't know if we will actually keep LinkedIn sales navigator cause I
don't use it very often. Um,
yeah, but maybe we will. So I want to show you how to,
um, let me start from this. I want to show you how to get,
um, invoices. So you go to LinkedIn,
my account, and then you click on the sales navigator icon here.
And then you click this thing settings.
And here this, uh, we have billing information.
So you past billing history and yeah,
we have this February two sales negator thing.
And then what I do is just click print,
right? And yeah,
save it. And then from that I will just,
uh, I guess, uh, send it to you right now and then you'll do
the usual stuff. So that's how I get invoices from LinkedIn.