I want to show you around MailChimp MailChimp to
create a campaign, a newsletter,
we need to go to campaigns and then, or complaints.
And here I have a template which is called like that.
So the easiest way to find it out.
So go to all campaigns and then we'll have this
draft. And so this template,
so let me also keep the old one from
this and a new link.
This is dropped complaints.
Okay. So to create a new campaign,
I used this template from droughts,
which started with this template and I click here
on this thing and replicate
now here, when it implicate, the first thing I need to change is the
name. So be clear email.
So usually there is a number And then the last one was 68.
So 69,
then the date, this is when it goes out.
So it goes out on Mondays. So tomorrow will be 11th,
so 11th, and then next 18th 25.
So this will be a real
2022. So this copy and
this sponsored and book of the week is,
are like features of this newsletter.
I'll explain later on for now. What can keep it out of this big
safe, and then immediately after that.
So it's 69, the goals here,
this combined link and change
This, this thing here,
2 69  will
be my old team data docs quo slash weekly six to nine.
And Yeah,
so now the template and
we need to edit design
and here in edit design, I,
there is no sponsored block this week.
Um, I will put something here, but I'm anti this.
I will not maybe record a separate video for that.
Um, and, um,
yeah, so for book of the week,
um, I think next week we'll have something,
let me check on the upside. So if we didn't
have any book of the week on the book,
so we'll click, just click delete block,
and then there will be no the week in the newsletter,
But we have something to the book of the
next week is interpretable machine learning by Christophe.
So I, what I do is I copy this link,
so I copy it. And then I go here,
click this Pen and
then say, look this And just paste.
And then it's important that there is no place with them.
And now we need to insert the image and image of the image of
the book. So according to the book, I right,
click copy image address.
And now this course away You,
we need to insert an image, the image and year,
instead of board, I click on this,
uh, from dropdown list input from Euro And
I put the other assay here. I
am important. Oh,
wow. It's huge. So we don't need it that
week. So the beat will be 160 and then
you automatically adjust the height.
And then the link is actually incredible.
So yes, open in a new window And I just saved.
So I also want to check the correct link once.
So keep pressing control and then click it
doesn't work. Okay. LinkedIn,
your top. Yeah.
So again, right-click open Lincoln in your top five
that this is the correct link. And then I do the same with the
image. So the link is correct.
So, okay. Next one. We need to feel in Lacy ones.
And for that again, go to the pub side and just copy all
the events And waste them here.
Sometimes it's paced like it and then two lion
at the beginning. And then at the end, these should,
uh, we should remove them. This happens sometimes.
Sometimes it doesn't, I don't know why, but yeah,
there should be no points here
Then. Yes. Then the next thing we need to fill in is
the podcast. So the latest podcast episode is this one
with these both click And then select
this one. And yeah, so this is the most recent one.
And then before that I get three,
three episodes before episodes,
before that, and copy them here.
I'm going to switch more or less in this thing.
So there is no sponsoring book, but they still want to
write something here. So I want to write a short description about,
Um, oh wait,
actually it's got funds from the next week. So yeah,
I will remove the sponsored book.
And for that, what I do is I just click,
delete, Think
The term.
Okay. Yeah.
So this is the newsletter this week.
All right.
And Yeah,
let me check.
Yeah. Check it,
but nevermind. So have the intro
and then join slack, then a book will check that things work.
So these links also should work. We don't need to check them because they
are presumably correct on the website and when we copy them from the website,
um, it copies the link as well. And yeah,
I think this should also be correct. Okay.
Thank you.
You want, and then also let me,
Um, show you how you schedule this.
We need to change this object And for the subject,
I just arrived in therapy.
And then I don't know. Maybe we'll get some nice emoji,
But yeah, I don't think you need to do that for the
sake of completeness. I'll just Show you what I do.
Um,
Maybe this could be In nice emoji
And for preview textile and here we
are.
Okay. So now I want to preview that things work.
So right now I want to check that this button,
this button works. You see that here in the left
bottom corner, we have the link is trying to data docs.club,
so that incorrect, and then we'll hold it and check the links.
Okay. So now we'll
do the sponsor thing because this is not a sponsor
and click on schedule. So I want to schedule it.
And usually I scheduled for,
Uh, 10, 10 him,
these GMT plus two,
Do they actually say,
Okay.
Yeah. Just double check. That campaigning is the name is correct.
Yeah. So it's actually related to Ms. Kiddo And I scheduled
for 10, 15,
April 11, Monday,
and I scheduled the complaint.
And now I have to look that I can check again that this
link is correct. Um,
So this is what people will receive tomorrow.
Okay. So for that, I want you to document multiple things from
that video. So the first thing is how you clone an event and
then how you feel in, sorry,
call your cologne newsletter campaign,
then how you feel in book of the week events
and, um, podcast blocks.
And then for sponsored content,
or maybe next week when we'll have a sponsored content for now,
you can also document how to delete things and then maybe
as a different document, like how you schedule the campaigns.
Yeah. That's it.