Um, so I noticed that in a playlist,
if I open, um,
if I open podcast, oh,
we don't have recent. So first of all,
this unspoken relationship is not a podcast.
It's a webinar, so please move it.
And then, uh, the last podcast that we've had here,
uh, was a podcast.
But after that, we had a podcast event with Ellen and then yesterday,
they went from yesterday with, um, with one with con Pablo.
So please add them to the playlist,
you know how to do this. And also,
you know, just, maybe I'll just remind you.
So this is a,
not a podcast, it's a webinar. And then,
uh, I usually force team say and them to livestream.
And then what you need to do is you need to go through channel.
Let's see, you want me to go through all the latest videos?
So this one is a webinar, this one,
oh, sorry. This one is a podcast.
This one is a podcast. This one is a webinars.
This one is a webinars. Um,
this one is podcast, please.
Oh, I think this, this one has workshop. It's already in the workshop.
So you have, let's make sure that these, they are in the correct,
um, playlists. So that's one thing.
And then the second thing is to make sure we do not forget to
do this. What I did is for webinars.
I added these two,
these two things, it links from speaker and then at videos.
So first of all, this one, this is what I was talking about.
But then also to make sure that we add links,
um, after the stream,
you should write to the speaker and then ask
if they want to share any links and then put them in it,
in the description. So this is for,
uh, webinars and the same thing for podcast.
So for podcasts, I edit the same two things.
Um, where are they?
Yeah. These links from the guest.
And then we do last thing. So these two things,
um, so this is what we forgot to do in the last,
uh, in the, for the last couple of visits.
So now we have this here. Um,
but I only edit this to the, to the template,
so I don't think it propagates.
So what I would like to ask you is to do this,
this one, right.
You know, we don't have it here, so please add the same checkpoints to,
um, all the podcasts, events and webinars to make sure
we don't forget this. And yeah,
for these ones, you don't need to a checklist,
just make sure you do this or for them,
I mean, move them to the,
uh, to the right playlist. Um,
yeah. And to one other thing, you notice that I added this thing here,
what, because document and Breitling YouTube.
So the reason, uh, the way we will use this is one you,
once you have a podcast document. So for example,
for, um, for example,
for me, or, uh, yeah, you already add this,
edit this. Um, but then, um,
we'll also have Encore link. So once we have another Encore link,
you can just edit here and then this way it will be easier for
you to share this link then afterwards with the speaker or for example.
Yeah. So this is something that,
so this is something that we'll do for the next,
uh, and for the next events for both podcasts
and webinars.
Um, yeah, so YouTube as well after this team,
uh, just, uh, uh, let's say this one,
uh, oh, you're ordered to do this.
Cool. Um, so,
well, we don't have it here. We don't have a YouTube,
but then for example, with, um,
like when we have fixed podcast page,
it's easier for you just to, uh,
copied from here and then ask the speaker of the guest
to share it with their, within that.
Okay. Yeah. That's what I wanted to show you.
So the main thing is we do not need to,
to forget, to put them to play lists and yeah,
it seems like you already got the idea behind these things and you're already
doing this. Um, yeah.
So I guess not need to do anything here.
That's it.