Um, pillow. So regarding this document,
this is very tiny. So I really have to zoom in to see what's
happening. So please try to make it not so small.
So one of the options could be you.
So what I did here, oops, say just double click on this and then
you see, you can kind of zoom in.
All right. And then, uh,
yeah, here, it's closer.
So people like, if somebody will need to look at this,
they will see what's happening.
And so,
and then next time you take a screenshot, try to make it more focused.
And if afterwards you did this,
so it's feasible, tried to Yeah.
To do it like that Now,
because otherwise it's just too little and it's not possible to see what's happening.
I think the snow to should be here.
Um, yeah, because it's not really related to this one.
Um, I think,
Yeah,
I should do it like that.
Oops.
Yeah. So please make sure that the screenshots are visible.
So it's possible to see what's happening on these screenshots when you include them
in the doc.