so we want to show you how I create events when we on the
grid on the outline, but we have agreed on a title already,
so I'll go to heaven,
right? So this is the place where payments and
then, yeah. So since we don't have podcasts that are
opinion, so I need to go to restaurants.
And then I says, come in data engineering manager.
I copied
now with the way I need Chubb dated two March.
Um, and then here,
and this is the title from PSA and study engineering.
I thought about subtitle.
Maybe I'll think about this. I will not record this.
Um, yeah, we should have some more fun.
Yeah. So maybe,
um, maybe we'll just leave it to ask your name and then
we'll subtitle later, click copy.
Then this is March 11
and at time of courses 12
and yeah. So since we already purpose your biography,
I'm not sure if personal website and Peter was intended to be as a
part of the biography. Well,
at least we can do this for day one since she's standard.
And then when we actually create a profile,
for sure, I'll do a separate video about
that. Okay.
And then I'll client a to be announced
and yeah, I'll need to update that.
But the main thing I wanted to show is that since we haven't
Seen school, if you haven't figured it out yet on the outline could say,
given, get the, that she likes to push us.
That's why there is no outline yet.
I usually kill it after we do the one questions.
That's why I will just pick an announcement because today I want to,
I'm preparing right now in this newsletter.
I'll talk about this little newsletter later,
but I need to feel this whence section.
And that's why I just want to have a place folder.
So people can only start to do this thing months later.
Okay. With, with actual details.
Yeah. Okay. That's all. Uh, I will know.
Um, I will now put image
appropriate. I'll do something quick and then I will ask you to replace it
with a good one from Canada. Okay.
That's it. So here's one.