Hi. Yeah, we had a problem. So you see for the event tomorrow,
it was not possible to buy, to not to buy,
to register, uh, for the webinar it was showing sales ended.
And the reason for that is when you go to the event,
So let me show you from the start. So you go to my events,
uh, event bright events, come on.
So then we have a bunch of events here,
and that was, um, the one tomorrow.
And then here the status was, um,
sale ended. So I needed to come here and
go to tickets. And then there is only one type of ticket,
which is, um,
this one. Alright, click on this.
And I needed to change sales and so,
and then put some, So it was for, um,
yesterday or yesterday? It was,
yeah, I think it was yesterday. 6:00 PM for some reasons.
So this is something we have to check every time.
So every time you publish an event, go here to tickets and check that
sales end is after the start date.
So in this case, there was, I don't know, a glitch or something.
So this, um, had a wrong end date.
We have to be careful and every time we create an event,
we have to go to tickets and check that the sales end is
after the, the actual lifetime.
So yeah, I save it. So now everything is fine.
Please update the, please update the process
document so it's there. And we,
uh, don't let this happen in the future.
Yeah, that's it.