So it looks like the one with Christopher was the last one.
So here in the podcast document, in the podcast folder.
And also please record it somewhere so we don't lose this information.
So here in this folder, so Dropbox podcast.
I think I have, you have access to that.
So first when we have, when our podcast
interview goes live. I also record it on my on my computer.
So not only on YouTube, but also on my computer.
And then at the end, when I stop, at the end of the
interview, I get some files and I upload these files to this podcast
folder, right? And if we open,
let's say,
this one with Christopher. So when I open
it, let me just check through the entire thing with you.
Right now, um,
okay, reach out to guests. It's clear.
Agree on a date. Create a document with question for the podcast.
Share the podcast document on the DTC podcast help.
Create a calendar invite. Ask the guests.
I think this is clear, right? So maybe even,
let me open it. So,
agree on a date, create a calendar invite,
this is something we can do.
Um,
here, so once we agree on a date,
we immediately, we can even, uh,
uh, wait, once
we agree on a date, we probably already have a document with questions.
Uh, this is the podcast document that we'll later share with Johanna.
It's not moved yet, right? Or you updated the links already?
By the way, how is it going with the migration project?
Anyways, um, so we create a calendar invite,
share the podcast document on the DDC podcast help,
and also, um,
wait, because, um,
this is one thing, but what we can also do is share,
we can include Johanna to our project.
Our conversation, include Johanna
or somebody else who helps with
the questions in
the email thread. So typically it's Johanna,
but maybe it's for some, it could be somebody
else. worse
So once we agreed on a document,
we can already include Johanna there and start preparing
questions. Ask the guest a biography and other information.
So this is something we put to the podcast document.
Ask the guest the bio to the podcast document.
Agree with author on the title and the outline.
Fill in the people form. Okay. So this is something on Data Talks
Club. When we create events,
we have these links. You already know that.
So this is why we need to create the,
wait, where is it?
Oh, here we Create a banner for
podcast event in Enigma. Okay. Create an event in Luma.
Create an event in the
community calendar. I think I
asked you to update this. So please check, please make sure that in other
that in other templates we also So,
call it DTC Community. Community calendar.
Yeah, right. This is what I meant.
Because like it could be confusing. We have here create a calendar invite,
right? And here we have create an event,
right? So it could be confusing. What's the difference between these two?
So this is for guests and this is for the attendees.
And first, yeah, we have to have a Luma event.
Create an event in Meetup, announce the event in Slack.
And here is a to-do for you. Add the link to the document.
Check if there's also a to-do doc.
Create an event on LinkedIn. This is something we discussed.
We need to update it. Fill in the event form on their table.
Add the event to the DataDocs group web page.
Schedule post on tiktok and twitter.
I think this is something we talked about already.
So instead of creating an event,
this is what we need to do. So I will remove
it.
So this one, I don't think we do it.
Wait. I don't think we do it anymore.
so we can just forget about that. Remind the guest about the event one
week before, one week day before,
actual stream. So here you don't need to do anything.
It's just after it's done, you tick the box and you put,
so every time you do something like,
for example, create a podcast document, you add a link here.
Then when you create a meetup link, you add a link here.
Don't do a link to it anymore.
Meetup link, YouTube link, podcast link.
here, it's Spotify
podcast link to do,
Apple podcasts link to
do.
Then what else, uh,
DVC web page podcast link to do.
And maybe there are some other links we should add here.
So then we have all the links here, and when you copy them,
when you create page,
you can also update this description,
so then it has other things.
Okay, uh, actual scripting,
add the YouTube link of the stream to the website,
update the recording to the shared folder in Dropbox.
This is what I showed you. So then you just check that it's,
when it's there, you tick the box, um,
you ask the guests for links after the stream, yeah,
so you just sent an email thanking them for the stream and then asking
if they want to share anything, then you edit the video,
uh, then the edit,
the editing on YouTube takes a bit of time,
so then sometimes we need to come there in like three,
four hours to check, yeah. If it's, it finished editing,
then actually I would update the cover,
uh, as soon as possible.
Uh,
we check if the video, add video to live stream and podcast playlist on
YouTube, uh, update, uh,
so then this is something to do. Uh, it
should be Luma, update the event sheet.
Ah,
yeah, this is the uploading.
When was the last time we actually did that?
It's been a while. Okay,
um, yeah, that's pity that we haven't done this in a while.
So I was thinking it's happening,
but it's not. Yeah,
so for now, let's not do that. Let's just keep this thing.
Podcast document to archive on Google Drive,
send the video to the freelancer. Um, okay,
so we don't do this anymore because the freelancer doesn't work with us anymore.
So you need to update this to, uh,
uh, edit it,
uh, create that transcript.
So please, uh, when you create that,
uh, when you create,
uh, the process document for that, um,
add it here. And this is actually, oops,
it's in our to-do list. So these two.
Uh, so these two are about creating,
um, transcriptions. Where
was I? Create the transcript.
So you turn that, uh, these Luma videos into process documents.
Update the podcast freelancers. Preach it.
Um, so let's see what is there. So
here we don't do paid transcript anymore.
We just, uh, yeah,
I guess we don't keep track of that anymore.
Uh, yeah,
so this document is needed to keep track of,
uh, um,
edits. So when we send a podcast,
uh, so for transcripts, we don't do it
anymore. So let me just delete this,
uh, or status transcript.
So you just mark it as done when it finishes.
So for a new events, um,
so please, uh, check with Dave for how many more episodes,
um, we,
um, mark it as done.
know, so what we are going to do right now is we
will, um, start from scratch here.
So I will, um, let me just
delete all these things. I'll just,
yeah.
So when we have a new episode,
let's start with three stuff. I'll show you how to fill it in.
And please make sure everything is documented. I know it's a lot of information
for you right now, and you work only for 15 hours per week right
now, but please make sure that this information does not slip through the cracks,
and we have it documented somewhere.
I'm pretty sure there should be a process document for that somewhere.
So let's try to find it,
and yeah,
and somehow we also, need to make sure that we can find an easy
way to find this information. Okay,
so I was here.
Then we add the video.
And status in progress. You will do it soon.
Status identity is done. and then please,
Let's ask Dave for how many more edits
or how many more podcast episodes we paid.
So this is yes. And then you
just include yes, yes, yes for how many more we paid because
we want to keep track of the payments.
And I will typically include you like when I make a new payment to
Dave. You will just, usually we pay for four.
So when we run out of payments, you will just add yes,
yes, yes. And wait, what's happening? And here
uh date paid.
So here we, you can ask him hey when was the last invoice paid
and for how many how many unedited episodes we still have in our um
pipeline. So then you can feel this thing.
And then next time we pay. We will
also put it here. So I just want to keep track of,
so the reason this spreadsheet exists is we want to keep track of how
many things we paid for and for how and when we need to pay
again. So, yeah,
that's why it's here. Include
encodes extracted from the transcript.
Okay, yeah, so for that we need to,
I want to update it to,
uh, open the
transcript, uh, save it, upload it to transcript utils, add file,
commit changes, yeah, this is right,
and then you get the time codes on time. Also,
please, for this one, check with Valeria if we need to.
We need to, uh,
update it. Schedulated
podcast with Anchor, so right now it's called Spotify for podcasters,
and we need to update it.
It's also to-do for you, so we need to update it with Spotify
for podcasters. So Anchor is the old name for that,
so they rebranded it and changed the interface.
add a podcast episode with the air table form.
So this is something that happens between,
as I mentioned, there is a task that needs to happen between the time
the podcast episode is released and the newsletter.
So by then we have everything,
and by the way Schedule.
So here in the schedule we have,
so
uh
um no so this one is not right.
So here we just have the link to Google and that's enough.
So the reason this thing exists is we keep track of uh
Release. So please find the relevant process document
and update them. So here we keep track of things
when we release podcast episodes, right?
So for example, last week we had um this.
Please write the the full name here,
the full name of the full title.
And then it was season 18,
episode number 9. So here we keep track of what is the season,
what is the episode. And then next time we publish something,
we would write here. So ideally we should have a plan here,
right? So this is podcast release.
So 16th of August was last week. This is when we published the episode
with Chris, right? And then next week, for example,
yeah we need to move Ella here.
But like once we have a new think with Rachel.
It will probably take two weeks. So here Rachel is this is when we
release it as a audio only version.
And it will be season 19 episode one,
right? And then after Rachel it will be Anne. It's 19.2,
right? So here we want to know and you need to put the full
name here of course. But here we just know okay now we have the
episodes in pipeline. Right,
and this is how you know season and episode number,
and then anchor your URL. This is actually Spotify for
podcasters URL. YouTube, Apple Podcasts,
Spotify. I don't know if this Spotify for podcasters still have,
I think the anchor thing still exists.
Yeah. Okay,
we need to figure out what kind of link to put there.
Okay. Schedule, create a podcast page,
uh, fill in the newsletter announcement.
This is exactly what you need to do on over the weekend after the
podcast episode is released. Right now, uh,
there is nothing to publish I think, so yeah,
that's why I, we don't need Too high with that one.
Then after it's created,
yeah, we ask the guest to share the podcast page,
add the link to the podcast page to the newsletter.
Uh, what is the difference between
these two?
Book of the week, like it's not even right.
Um,
yeah, we need to, I think this is actually what we,
come on, what's why it's book of the week?
Like please find a relevant process document and if you cannot,
uh, we need to create a new one.
So the idea behind these two is we need to,
um, we already We have a placeholder.
In the, um, in the newsletter, and now we need
to fill it in with actual information.
So please coordinate with Valeria about this too,
and let's make sure everything is documented. Okay.
I understand that it's a lot of information probably will take,
uh, you will spend the next week,
uh, on that once you finish the,
uh, the thing with taxes,
but let's make this a priority. I want you to be able to do
the entire thing end to end. And for that, I'll we will need to
work on updating the process documents.
Yeah. So please make it a priority for the next week.
Uh, schedule post overview after the event and linked it.
Uh,
okay. Um, and yeah,
maybe you can also, let me see what is
here.
yeah, maybe ask Valeria what this is.
Because it has to be a process document and what
we have from Valeria is not that.
Uh, but I think here is
the template, right? Yeah,
please ask her what exactly we need to do here and then we can
make a proper process document from the library.
Please. Okay, so I think it gives you a good overview of,
I think we also need to, what we call AnchorFM,
AnchorLink. We need to figure out what is now we have instead of Anchor,
Spotify for Podcasters link. Actually,
check it.
Now, maybe there is no specific link for this thing anymore.
Okay, so it's,
is there a link?
Oh, this is not right. Like,
this is not what you would in episode description. So please check the,
uh,
please check what we should put there. Like there is,
it's, it used to be called anchor. So you want to check the podcast,
uh, the process documents for anchor and then check what we have there.
And, uh, yeah, so this is not,
this is not right. Explicit content?
Of course, no. Like, why?
Yeah, please make sure you read the process documents before you do that.
Like, we don't want to have the improvisation here,
right? So, like, the process documents exist for a reason and if you don't
know how to do something, just let me know, okay?
Like, please don't improvise. And
so I think I don't know
how to get the link right now for a podcast episode.
Let me see.
Does this thing still exist? Yeah, okay.
So, you go to this thing, podcasterspotify.com, podshow,
DataDocsClub, and then you get the link from here.
Oops, see more.
Like, how do we actually, Yeah,
so when we just click on this, I think we get the,
link to the actual thing. So, this is what I meant by the,
by the link. So, for example, I will now go to,
I'll call it anchor instead of anchor.
Spotify for podcasters link.
Save. And then for Chris, where is it?
Chris. it's
here. Save.
Okay.
And this was actually after event, so now we need to put this here.
So with this one, we'll, we also need to do it to finish these
things, but let's later, once you figure out like the priority for next week,
we will be figuring out the podcast thing.
Right. And we'll do
the same thing now afterwards with other,
um, other things. What is podcast example?
Okay, I think Valeria maybe was experimenting with.
And this is something you created, right? Okay,
good. We can,
uh, make it a template.
Okay. So, uh, this was the podcast.
Yeah. There are a lot of things and it's outdated.
I know, not ideal, but then coming back to this one.
So usually after the episode is edited,
I delete, um, like let's say we keep Last few.
But like these ones are pretty old,
so I will remove them. So every now,
like every month we can come to this folder to clean things we don't
need anymore. And when you upload
something to, um,
Spotify for podcasters, uh,
you move things here to the uploaded folder.
So if it's not documented anywhere, please also document this and the structure of
this folder. So here when we don't have any anything
here, it means that we don't have any episodes in the pipeline.
Let me keep just in case, uh,
the edited version for the last one. But every now and then we clean
it. So here's the structure of our podcast document.
So here we have unedited things, here we have edited things,
and every time we upload something, we schedule with Spotify for podcasters,
we put it to there.
Okay,
that is a lot, uh, so please make sure everything
I shared with you is documented somewhere. I know it takes time,
but we're not in a rush anywhere.
Please take time to document everything, and let's make sure this information
is not lost.