Okay. So now we have a lot of emails like this,
like Chrome, for example. So now that she sends links,
but then these links are all in the email.
So it's hard to make my life will be easier to prefer.
We should wait. We should add
like a special section in our podcast documents where we
let's say the lines here and then ,
and then we edit here. Oops.
So
Now clean formatting. Yeah. Like that.
So let's do like that every
time when guests send some materials.
So we'll have questions here and then at the end we'll get some materials.
So this way I will always know where to find the materials.
So instead of going through these email chains,
they will always be in the document.
And then there will be a link to that.
So yeah, maybe do this and you can also update our template.
So at the lines. Yeah. And then with yours,
from the guest, and this is what we .
So for the
questions, don't think about this.
Yeah. Maybe. Yeah.
Let's, let's do it like this. And then once we prepare questions,
I guess this can go away.
But anyways, so please do like for all the forecast
we have, like, when a guest send somebody also please,
uh, put it here. And I think, uh, by the way,
we need to announce this to right now,
take a look at them, but yeah, please,
please do this. And yeah,
we modify the template and I guess it could also be
one of the checkpoints in our template.
Right. So get links from this,
the guest, if they provide any and then put them to the document.
Okay.