Okay. So I found a good YouTube video and they want to reach
out to this speaker and right here to our,
um, to our events as well. So what I do is
hear your name right by copying
his name. Then I go to LinkedIn,
I search. And then, you know,
this is here. Now you see pictures.
Well, I guess here kind of hard to see,
but this is Kara. And now I want to reach out
to your saying, Hey,
I saw your talk. Do you want to run this community?
Do you want to also give a talk?
So for that and to connect and
then hi, Meryl. Um,
see I run a co-op community.
And for you, you can say I'm a community manager at data talks club,
community, or at Databox club,
um, around Datadog's community. I saw your talk about,
um, or here
could be, I saw your talk with tech,
for example, or we can work on that template.
That's what you're talking about. I was wondering if you'd
be interested in doing a work about
us and the workshop.
So here, I want to invite your not to do the same talk.
Sometimes most of the times probably I would actually invite for that,
but here I want to, uh, to invite here,
to do a workshop about Kettering, the workshop is like a hands-on thing.
Um, but anyways, yeah, that's all actually,
I want to write with,
uh, techno for example,
or, yeah, it doesn't matter. I saw your talk about Kara.
That was wondering if you'd be interested in doing a workshop with us.
I think that's, that's a patient.