Um, hi. So I wanted to show you how to,
you probably know this, how to rearrange,
uh, videos in a playlist. So let's take this one.
So you recently uploaded this video and this one.
Okay. So for this one, uh,
I actually want to move it here.
So after office hours, and I think it will be
nice to add that it's a homework solution by [Inaudible] Taang.
Yeah. Can you please, uh, add this to the title and
then, Yeah, I think we're missing a happen here.
Can you please add it here and then when we have,
uh, homework number four and you will upload it.
So it should go after office hours here,
then with the rest of the office hours. I think that is fine.
And then another thing I wanted to show you now go back,
um, yeah, this, this one machine learning zoom camp.
So you just it to videos, right?
So these two videos are here at end and
now we need to, because you see they're 7.1 and then they're at
at end. So we now need to move them all the way up
here between, uh,  six and
eight, right? And then, um,
I'll do it the same with this one,
but then for the new ones that you upload,
please also put it here in the right order,
In the playlist, eh,
come
On. Okay.
Will not always have, like usually when I ask you to upload a video
and get it to a playlist, you usually don't need to do any of
that. But sometimes I will probably say that.
Okay. Make them in the right order.
And yeah, this is, uh, if you don't know what the right order is,
just ask me. But here, in this case,
they have numbers, so then it's more or less easy to figure out
where they should go. So for the new videos that we will upload from
here that I just asked you to upload, um,
yeah, please put them where is please put them also
in the right position. Okay.