Hi. I came across an issue today,
so this, uh, player wasn't working.
Um, so it was, uh, playing a different,
uh, episode. It was playing episode with Kai,
Kate, Katie, uh,
instead of this one. And the problem there was that we accidentally
use strong url and the reason we use strong url,
so this is the URL you submitted in the form.
And the reason this is, uh, a wrong hero.
Now, if I go to Anchor and let's
say get one of the episodes,
this is I think how we do it, right?
Um,
So open a text editor. So this is how the,
this looks like, right? So it's, uh,
different now. So what,
uh, you can do, there are actually multiple options.
The first one, we just go to our public page,
this listen on anchor, and we have,
you know, we have this one, right? So just click on this one and
use this. So when you, uh,
put it in the form,
Like
Where's k
K?
So when you fill the form here,
table form. So you put this link here.
So this link goes here to anchor,
right? Not this one. So you can compare these students,
right? So it should be not this Spotify anchor web,
blah, blah, blah, but anchor found data doc stop episodes and this one,
right? And then if the URL looks like that,
then uh, we will not have problems,
uh,
Well
With, um, you know, the player because,
um, the, the script that you execute when you submit a form,
it's actually, I don't know what's
happening with my computer. Yeah, it's actually looking at this URL and uh,
extracting this part. So that's why,
yeah, instead of, uh, doing it the old way,
go to our public website webpage of anchor,
which is, um, this one,
or it is,
Um,
Yeah, but I usually go it from here.
But this it's anchor.fm/data Talk Club.
This is our public page,
right? And then copy the D.
So in the same way you do from Apple or from Spotify,
um, we also need to do it this way from Anchor Now,
cause the, the D that anchor give are,
uh, different, they and also work.
So maybe this one is simpler for you. So you can just paste it
here in the browser and you see that it redirects and then it's,
it becomes very long. So we need to remove everything after the question mark.
So we don't need any, everything, anything that comes after the question mark.
And then at end we end up with the same Euro.
So these are the two ways you can get the right euro.
So next time when I you upload, um,
um, when you create a page, please use one of these two.
So right now, what you will need to do is update the process doc
to include, um, yeah,
you can include both, uh, both options,
right? Uh, actually maybe it's simpler,
uh, if you just say about the public page,
right? I think this way it's consistent with others like how you get it,
uh, from uh, Apple Podcast,
Spotify, then the same way you get it from Anchor.
So yeah, please mention only that one and the second one is more like
for your information. Okay,
That's fine.