Hi. So I created this table in air table.
So it's called Open Source Spotlight. If you go to Air table,
you will find it here.
This open source spotlight. Um,
yeah, so this is just, uh, you know, very similar to what we had
for the crm. Um,
what I really love about air cable is that you can add link links
between different, different,
uh, tables, different, uh, you know,
taps. So what I wanted to ask you is to move all the things
from here. Not all the things, only open source,
uh, spotlight stuff from here to,
um, it's not
okay. It's working. Um,
from here to, um,
this new table. And by the way, so here we just have one type
open source, but do we actually know which project is it?
So probably you'll need to find out, uh,
what is the project. Maybe the LinkedIn can tell what they're working
on. Hmm,
interesting. Yeah,
we will need to figure out, um, like ideally we should have kept the,
um, the url,
the GitHub url. Okay.
Like, we don't know it here.
We will need to find, but let me see.
Um, yeah, so this one,
it will be commonl, right? So this is the project
And we still have anyone present this project.
So it would be interesting to get somebody to present it.
And of course, I, I think this Joe Wolf,
we tried to contact this person in June.
They didn't answer, so we didn't fall up.
Um, okay, so I will take this thing and I will put it here.
So GitHub, then the project name would be,
I guess that's sort of be common. That's the project name,
right? Start. Uh, still ,
I don't know. Let's, let's say new.
I will need to figure out. So these are the default statuses in air
Table. When you create a table, it just comes at book ups with the
status, new in progress. Done. Let's just start with new.
And then for people we add,
let's add Joe.
So do we know Joe's email?
You know, we don't have the, he's,
He's LinkedIn. We don't have email.
And the project is Rub, but now it's kind of
easy for us to uh,
understand like who, what are the people behind each project?
And then of course, like if Joe, we,
we should follow up with Joe of course. But if Joe is not answering,
then we can see, okay, this is still status new,
maybe status could be in you,
like you didn't do any research here,
so I just sent you a link. And then it's new.
Then in progress it means that,
uh, you started working on this, you found somebody,
but they haven't replied yet. We haven't scheduled a demo yet.
So then it's in progress. And then,
uh, done is, uh, we already recorded it.
Okay. Yeah, please, uh, document everything that I'm,
that I say here, like the status system, that could be important.
Okay, so we have the people,
the project. So what I would like to ask you to do is go
through all this, um, through all this,
uh, uh, document and for those projects,
for those open source projects that we haven't recorded yet,
or we, um, yeah,
we haven't recorded yet. Please move them to this
new table. And by moving,
I mean, uh, we,
Uh,
We can just remove it from here. Uh,
and remove is like just, you know,
click on this and then,
um, this thing is not letting me. So
yeah, just delete and yeah.
Um, probably this date of last contact is also something important.
So maybe, uh, let's add it here.
Lost
Contact date.
Okay, so that could be important. So yeah,
please fill it in. All the information from here.
And then for these people like Paul Ya,
who will need to figure out, uh, what is the project,
um, that they, uh,
that they're working on.
Yeah, I don't know if we'll need to have status for people too.
For, uh, people for projects,
Yes, for people we will see. And then there is a cool feature for
airflow. We can actually have CanBan view.
So you see that, uh, we have all these two,
uh, projects. So these are these two.
Let me just remove them.
So then we have, uh, this view.
And then let's say I just sent you,
um, a link. It's here in the new,
but then you can move it to progress and then you can move it
down. So it's very similar to Trla, right?
So there are different views. Um,
and then for people, let's see if we need to add status two to
have this view of what's happening there,
to see who we need to follow up with.
Yep. So please move all the information from here to there.
And, uh, we can start following up to some people because,
um, yeah, for example, these guys here,
uh, it's been a while, so let's try to follow up with them and
then see, um,
if they're interested, if they're not interested,
we can see what kind of projects they, uh,
worked on and we can try to conduct somewhere else from that project.
Okay, That's it.