Hi. I want to show you one more thing,
but before I do this, so I want to talk about this open source
spotlighting. But before I do this,
I want to give you a quick recap of what we have so far,
what we've discussed so far, because I understand this may be causing
a lot of confusions, so have a lot of different activities.
So we have weekly life events. So this events that happen every week,
that I've ever been those events with slides that we have on Tuesdays.
And we have flap interviews on Fridays.
I already show it to you and these things.
And then we have book off the week thing. This is where in white
book authors in slack. So the event is kinda it's happening in slack.
Um, people ask questions in slack and then podcast is when we
record live in through use and take these interviews and release
them as audio only versions. You probably remember this page podcast
on the, on our website. And then the other thing I haven't talked about
is this open source spotlight. So if we go to our YouTube channel,
one of the playlist, there we go to playlist to one of the playlist.
There is this open source spotlight spotlighting.
So there are quite a few different things there.
So this are, uh, we invite authors of different open source libraries
to give a talk, uh, to give a presentation about Dave,
to, for example, the environment running on AWS
or .
Um, yeah, and now I recently had one
of the authors also who presented their tool.
And now I want to upload this to YouTube and I want to show
you that. So I have it somewhere.
Yeah. So we use zoom for recording.
So you see this link. So probably after this recording is done,
I will forward to you such a link. So you will have a link
also with passcode. So let me open it in incognito.
So you see how to look for you. So I
will copy the link and then it will ask for password.
So now I need to copy this password.
Yes. Except cookies.
And then we have this recording. So this is the demo
that, uh, uh, our own gave.
So now I am going to click on download.
So it is being saved right now. Um,
he is saving a lot of things.
We only need one. So now I don't
know which of them. So let me wait till everything downloads.
I will, uh, open them folder.
So yeah, there are two things. So one is gallery and then just one,
the other one is just recording. So gallery is when we have you see,
it's like phase by phase or like say by site.
So me on one side and then on the other side,
and there's just a,
where it's you see, it's not side by side.
I have those insights. Um,
so we are interested in this. Oops.
I don't know why it doing that.
So on one account, my, as my account,
it's not doing this gallery thing on another.
It is doing this, but we're interested in this thing.
So now I go to YouTube and then on YouTube,
there is this create and to make sure that you are in Datadog's club
account. So I click upload video lead
brings me to the studio and now I just drag and drop it.
So now it starts uploading. Now I need to give it a name.
So the name should be, uh,
let me open, uh,
other, uh, other events in this,
uh, open source spotlight. You will see the pattern.
So the pattern is open source spotlight when dash the name of the tube
and dash the name of the presenter.
So it is open source book,
LOTE, and dash the name of the tool.
Now what's the name of the tool it's cast lit.
Yeah. Cool way. Um,
let me into this nuttin Castile IO.
Yeah. This one. So this has the name of the tool cost,
uh, cost lit.
And then the name of this person.
Let me check. Uh,
yeah, so this is his name. So let me copy it and
paste it here. And now we need to give a,
some description. So usually it falls this way,
uh, that this formats months first the name of the two,
then a colon, and then,
um, some description of the tool,
what the tool was doing. So thinking get happy.
Usually they have this one liner. Uh,
so this is open source solution or diversity of solution
that helps you periodically sync the data.
Um, now let me just take that.
Yeah. Uh,
sort of CTL solution, uh,
Yeah, that's a long description, but the key who can live it like that,
and then we have some links.
So this links, uh, ask, uh,
ask their guest, Jay usually should ask the
guest, Hey, what are the links you want to include? And they sent me
the links. Usually it's the link to get her page.
So let me conclude it right away up.
And then yeah, ask the, I guess first, and then here will be time
codes, time codes.
Uh, yeah, so basically,
uh, you know, what 10 codes are, and this is something I also ask
the guest to provide.
Um, yeah, you see it actually already is uploaded right now.
I do not select any playlist. This will,
I will do all the activity end,
but, uh, the playlist will be open source spotlight.
I do not select it right now, monetization.
Or then I go to  because
ads are quite annoying. And then this isn't listed,
this isn't listed because they want the author to the guests
to be able to review it. So I click save and
then let me copy the link.
So get shareable link.
So now it is copied to clipboard.
Now we'll copy it here.
And, uh, what I want to do now,
I don't know if it's a possible right now.
Uh, maybe it is not yet possible.
I actually am lucky. It is usually it takes a bit of time before
the edit. Uh, now option is available.
Maybe this video was quite small. Um,
so I'll show it right away. Usually what I do is
no. Hello. Hi Lexi. Yeah.
Can you tell us if you want, uh where's I need to trim,
so, and then in 3m, I want to remove silence
at the beginning.
So silence at the beginning. Now I click preview to check.
No. Hello. So little bit more.
Yeah. Can you tell us a few words about yourself and about the tool
you want to show us? Sure. Yeah,
that is okay. Maybe actually to start with hello?
No. Hello. I want to enlarge it to leave a bit.
Oh
yeah. I like that. Hello? Hi Lexi.
Yeah. Can you tell us a few words about yourself and about the two
of you? Okay. So that we remove this from the beginning,
and then I also want to make sure that at the end,
there is also no silence.
Yep. Bye bye everyone. Bye.
So yeah, we don't need this bit at the end as well.
That's usually all I need to remove.
Sometimes maybe there is something in the middle in this one.
We do not need to remove anything from the middle.
So I click preview and now I click save paid
will take some time to upload, but,
uh, I ordered you not to upload to update.
I already have a link. So once these link,
once the video is updated, I will send this to the guests.
Um, so I usually do this from my work account because in my
work account, they have a zoom that,
uh, uh, that is better basically.
So it is more expensive, but at work,
uh, I can use it for, for these things as well.
Um, oh, actually, you see, I run already provided the links.
So let me just go ahead and put them, I don't need this anymore,
so, and not what
they wanted. Yeah.
This one. So in details links.
So we already asked the guest for links.
He already sent, so we don't need,
I can get her because I already did edit this.
Okay. Click save. And now this link,
copy this link and send it to the guest.
And, uh, I, I don't,
uh, because for me took a bit of time to process this.
I'm going to say, sorry.
Apologies for the delay.
Um, here is that we do,
uh, please, uh, sent me that time.
What's oh,
maybe I should be a bit more polite and say,
thanks again for presenting,
presenting the tourists,
CAS lit, please send
me the time cones. Good time. Cause when you have time,
um, yeah, have a great week. Something like this.
I will probably add you as well. So let me copy your
email.
I will copy your email as well.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, so let's all.
And because it takes a bit of time to update,
uh, for YouTube to update it.
So what I will do is I will click here,
let me check a usual Gaetan g-mail has it.
So if I click reply, the usual Jamail also has it.
So, um,
so here are the skid schedule sent.
So I do schedule time,
um, peak date and time.
So right now for me, it's 5:00 PM.
So what I'll do is I will send it at,
uh, let's say tomorrow,
uh, I think he's in India. Um,
so tomorrow maybe, um,
6:00 AM we're mourning for him.
Um, so yeah, by tomorrow I am sure.
Uh, it will be ready. Okay.
Yeah. Skillset.
Yeah. You don't have to do this for tomorrow.
You don't need to know where they are. Exactly.
This is just a thought that if I send it right now,
uh, in two hours it will be like midnight for him,
even a middle of the night. So I hope of course he's notifications are
turned off just in case I did this for morning.
So then in the morning he will see this, uh,
he will check this. He will reply with,
uh, time codes. And then I think there is a lot of the video
that shows how to add time coats.
So once he sends them, you will just need to place
them here. Okay.
That's all I wanted to show you.