Um, hi, I am checking,
um, this open-source spotlight spotlighting, and then notice that,
um, the things that aren't released yet.
So for example, this cow's genius,
uh, um, the soda cl air bite,
they are not released yet what they are already available in the
playlist. I'm right now in coding,
incognito mode. And the reason for that I think is because they're
probably already in the playlist. So let me check that.
Um, yeah, there's similar on,
for example, let me check it.
Yeah. So Emma Loran is not in the playlist,
which is correct. So you shouldn't add them to playlist yet.
Yeah. This one is a very,
so you only add to the playlist when you want three days at right
then this one is not, uh, I don't know.
Did you schedule it? You, you haven't scheduled it yet.
Right. And by the way, other thing is,
uh, I know that Michelle sent,
uh, the timestamps in this format,
so you always need to add leading, um,
leading zeros. Right. So they all follow the same format.
Maybe this one is covered. Yeah. So please,
uh, adjust, um,
process documents for that. And yeah.
So this, um, shouldn't be in the playlist until you really,
so when you schedule this, when it's scheduled,
then you should put it in there in the playlist,
because right now they,
they are accessible through, through the playlist,
even though they are unlisted. Yep.
That's all.