Hi, maybe you remember that now for open-source spotlight we have a new calendar
link which looks like that.
It's currently the DC Alexi OSSS.
OSS, right? So this is the link.
And right now in the calendar this is how it looks like.
You have access to my calendar so you should be able to see that.
So it says demo of this stack, open-source spotlight. And then it says who
is going to present? My country. In this case you can see their email
in my calendar just here,
right? So you can see it here and then you can copy it.
And then you can write them. Later on then you can also see GitHub
link and project name. So I ask them to fill this information when they
create a calendar event. So we already have this information in the
calendar. Right? And what I'm going to do is I'm going to create a
calendar event. And what I'm going to do right now is just forward use
the link. So I will forward it to you.
And I also what I usually do is forward.
So this is not something you need to add in the process document.
So in the process document you'll probably show what to do after you receive
this email. This is just so it appears in
your to-do list. And so right now you will receive this email.
And you will know, okay,
that this is Andre. And then you see the
date, right? So you see when started and then you can just go to
my calendar and using the name.
Yeah, using the time I guess and then it's also so spot-by.
You can find this in my calendar.
And this is how you access email.
This is how you access project name and GitHub link.
And yeah, I don't need to. I just copy this information to you every
time. You know how to find it right now.
Okay, that's how you find information about open
source spotlights. Videos.
Yeah, that's it.