Hi. So I received this email from our,
um, tax consultants, from the accountants and this email,
yeah, it's in Russian or it's actually like a mixture of Russian
and uh, German. So let me translate it in English.
Um,
Okay,
This is Russian, right? Um,
yeah. So I will probably in the future will forward these emails to
you. Um, yeah,
I see that, uh, Google does not,
uh, translate the there German part.
Anyways, so this thing is about V A T.
So I need to pay V a T every quarter.
Sometimes, um, the tax office returns,
VT gives, uh, back v t.
Sometimes I need to pay vt. So in this month I need to pay
v t and I want to show you how to do this.
So this is the e email and I think this is the document we
need to add to,
um, you know, our, um,
booking. So we'll forward it right now.
So we'll write something like,
um, uh, VT here and uh,
like exactly how we, um,
like the exact line you can check in the previous,
uh, you can check in
the previous, uh, months how we put it.
I think it was, uh,
this one. Yeah. Oh, oh, fin sum and then v a t.
And then this is, uh, for this one it would be four Q,
like four quarter 2022.
And then, then it's negative, right?
So it's mean minus something and fine sum in,
uh, German fin sum means,
uh, the tax office. So we need to write fin and sum and then
V 80 here and then the quarter,
and then include the, the thing here.
So here it'll be a minus.
And uh, as you see here in this document,
the, there is no, um, bank details.
So let me just first, uh,
Send
It here, right?
And then we keep only this one,
right? So this, this U S T,
um, which is ZA store in German,
which means V 80, right?
When you see U S T, it means V 80. Okay,
so I'm sending it here.
So we'll have it now in Dropbox and our books.
And now we will need to actually pay this amount.
So I'll show you how to pay it to this finan sound.
So go to fin. So put the,
um, total here and then here now I look for finance
ump. So this is, this is it.
And I will also need to put reason for payment.
Um, okay,
that's interesting. Where do I find it?
Um, probably need to check the previous
one. So let me, let me see the previous transactions.
So now you will create a process document for that,
and then you will write it down. So we don't need to,
um, to look it up every time. Finance out the,
in September, uh, we pay them 300 and
yeah, so this is how it should be.
So this is my tax number, tax 80.
And this is, um, I don't know what PJ means.
I think this is like, uh,
it should be fourth quarter 22,
So I'll replace it with four. So it's uh,
fourth quarter, 22. So, and if we do this four,
I don't know, next quarter it'll be one.
I don't know what VJ means, I guess quarter and then 23,
right? So you will put this in the process document and
uh, yeah, no, I guess I'll just pay,
okay, now I need to confirm this,
um, where it is.
Okay.
Confirmed. Now then that's,
um, that's how you transfer v a t minus to the tax office.
Yeah, please create a process document for that.
And we'll probably have like a folder with,
uh, payments, right? With all this.
So put it here. Put it there. Okay,
thanks. See you later.