Okay. Yeah. So just edit this field with links and
here for this one. So go to the YouTube video there.
We already have links or this is actually the same as we have.
Uh, let's say here.
Yeah. So these things for examples is at the same links and we have,
these links should be the same everywhere, so let's make copy them.
And so just copy them on here from a
very video and then put them here.
Uh, the forum. No,
not this one. Yeah. And then
this one would be more for this one and to make it easier for
me to parse at this thing.
So what can make it larger? So that the name of the link then,
uh, the side and then the actual link and
the same here. So this way I will be able to,
uh, parse this information here that you provide.
And then of course, don't forget the line break.
So let's say if there are three links, then it will be no link,
link, pity title.
And then I launched B um,
link three column something.
So follow this format. And then,
uh, this way I will be able to pass this information from the form
and put this as a webpage.