I short call to schedule a podcast too.
And today we need this core.
Um, so now the episode went live sometime ago.
Yeah. This one with career coaching with Lindsey.
So now I want to create this page.
So with page here and would that,
I need some information. So for each podcast,
find it links to apple podcasts,
Spotify, YouTube, and anchor, and then also transcript.
That's why I created this form. So in this form I
needed a bunch of things. So first of all,
uh, often this kid will document.
So here we see.
Yeah, sure. Here we see that this is season seven,
episode four. So excuse me.
So on, so forth, then I need to applaud
the task here. So this is the transcript of how I showed you.
So to download it, if it's a Google doc file,
we need to download it as a doc. It can already be a docs
file. Then we don't need to do this. So then done lot,
no clicks. So I have this document here in my download
folder. So then I would just attach this well,
uh, yeah, this one
cool way.
Um, and then I need to public hero to anchor something darker.
You can get public hero by clicking this three dots and then
copy public link. So then I put it here.
So we have a staff link. Oops.
Yeah. Well, you can see that it works.
Um, then I need to link to a YouTube video.
So this is the link to YouTube video.
Yeah. We have quite a few questions and then the link they need
this one. So I don't need anything that
all basically only this part that says V equals something.
And then if there is some percent and after the assumption,
I don't need anything
new to Purell, then I need to for podcast hero.
So for that to find out the Euro for apple podcast,
I need to here to podcast page and then click on apple podcast.
And then it will bring me to there, to all the podcast
episodes or for Theodore squad on apple podcasts.
Then I'm interested in this one. So this one,
it went live today. So I need this thing.
So, all right, click on this  and
this to the quorum. Then finally I need Spotify Euro support,
Spotify AGN,
open this, uh, short here with all the links and
yeah, this one is here, so right
quick doesn't work. So I need to click on this and then copy the
Euro
works. Um, and then I submit,
and then using this information, I will be able to generate,
uh, no to generate,
uh, my pitch.
I think I forgot one thing. I forgot to
add links. I will probably record
another video with that car, to it that.