Oh, it could be the board podcast. So podcast is,
I think that we'll have data pub.
We've got this inquiries podcast podcast.
So the podcast published to apple podcast,
Spotify and other platforms. So there is quite a bunch of platforms where we
publish, and this is audio on diversion.
If I click here,
We're not making money in.
We're trying to figure the is not video.
And there is a video on diversion if I go to YouTube.
So this is a with Greg,
I can find it here. This is one of the last,
uh, last year, this one do welcome to our event
Available to us
Podcast. So we published last week. So see that there are no time codes
it's already on the platform. So I want to show you,
um, not the entire process, but some of the process.
So, um,
so the process, yes, your  and
the actual event, the podcast event happens.
Usually it is on Friday, could be other date.
So then we streamed YouTube. And this is the video that you just saw
this video with Greg. So it was themed life.
Welcome to say it was  life,
uh, on January 21.
Yeah, but it's usually a bit of a delay between it is themed and
it is published on a podcast as a podcast,
as an audio on leadership. I felt this actually in the schedule.
So we see it. It was a live podcast was on 21st of January.
And then, so this column,
uh, this bunch of columns is, or where we publish this as audio
only version.
And we publish this 4th of February.
So there are there's two weeks delay between when it goes live.
And when it is published as audio, only because after that,
we need to do a bunch of things.
So that's why we need this delayed, well cut in the beginning,
you probably saw it's the easiest part.
Doesn't take very much time, but then I sent this video to a freelancer
and the freelancer transcribes it.
So it turns, want into text. And then what he sends is something
like this. So this is the video I want to applaud right now.
So there's a video from Lindsey about career coaching.
So he sends a document that looks like that.
And so this is a transcription,
and then now I need to put this transcription to the website.
So this is that transcript. So I need to turn this document into,
uh, this also from this document,
I see that the 10 quotes for each phrase,
we have, uh, a timestamp when this occurs.
So because there are others like for each kind of block or section,
and the freelancer also, uh,
use the name of the section so we can extract 10 quotes.
So this is a skier,
the title. And then after the title,
there is a timestamp. So what I do, I have a script that there
are a, that does this automatically.
And for now I will need to do this,
I guess, but then I will also need to pick it out how you
can help me with that without,
um, Kevin, around this, uh,
without, uh, yeah, maybe I can put this online somewhere so you can just
upload this file and get this.
Okay. Yeah. So you don't need to document what I'm saying now.
It's more like for you to understand the process.
Okay. So we have this document and the next
step is at the same time, extend that to the editors.
And this happens to the Dropbox. I think I just shared a access video.
It's in my Dropbox, they have this custom folder.
And then after the event, what I do is I create a folder with
the date timestamp when, uh,
the podcast was themed life. And I bought,
uh, the files there. I do this because they are on my computer.
I don't think you will be able to do this. Um,
yeah. And then there's this folder called edited and yeah,
I need to move. So this, uh, so the editors who take care of
editing the podcast, they would in this podcast folder.
And then, because they're one with Greg,
I uploaded one. We could go, I need to put this two uploaded folder.
And now there is this podcast with, uh,
uh, Lindsey. So it is already edited.
So if I open it, there is some
already. So, uh, I will need to upload this.
So first. Yeah. So these two things actually happened in parallel.
So I sent the video to a freelancer and then the next week he
usually gets back with a transcription and then I sent this
to the editor and then they also get back next week,
the app for the file to this folder.
And then also from this time scripts,
now I want to extract 10 calls. Um,
but to be done, Lord this again,
you do not need to, uh, during the scene to your
process document, because I don't think you will have to do this.
So maybe some of these parts,
but not in this form. So I got the document.
This is a doc document. I'll just rename it to say Lindsey.
Then I have a script that, and
I don't know, where did it go? Okay.
Yeah. So good to hear, um,
that term, this dockings document into a format that they can use.
So I know that leaves in download and then let's
see. Yeah. So this clip now we'll extract time codes and then
create two. So I need to say where the results
should go. So it will go to TMP slash results
again, do you see what it does it, first of all,
creates this file, open it.
This is just for your information again. So that is all team result,
but this is the file card. It looks like.
So this is something that we'll use for the website and it also
puts the timecards. So I need to take this one in
copilot to YouTube, you
to then find the video for which this transcript was created.
Some video with an engineer,
click edit video.
I think I need to follow up with her because she sent me some
links to center things,
but here, I want to show you that I need to insert of time
quotes. So these are the 10 quotes and the essay leader talked
about. And then,
yeah, I just copy the time course here. And then yeah,
let me just in case at, uh,
LinkedIn
nicotine. So we
made sure it properly spoke your name. Say
then I think she sent me a link that I needed to include this
and I forgot. Um,
yeah. Imposter.
Okay. Yeah. So these are the links, um,
here, is that the timestamps?
Okay. Yeah. Let me just save it.
Now, if I go back to the video, I studied
engineering. You see that we have a time course right now we have this
chapters and we can jump,
jump from one to another.
No. So now we are done with time codes and they want to show
you how to upload videos to Concord.
So go to the anchor and
I click on new episode. I think I applaud this.
Um, ideally this would happen not on the day.
So right now it's Friday on Friday. I usually publish them.
So ideally I should do this immediately after,
uh, it is edited. So no.
Yeah. And then I go to Dropbox,
Dropbox, I'm in Dropbox and then edited.
And this is the episode Lindsay.
So click on this. Um,
and then the title and I just copy from here.
Now, this is the title. And then since we already have,
uh, uh, time quotes, the chapter names,
I also we'll put it here. So I'll say that we talk about,
and then this will be a list of things we talked about.
Let me copy this. So we'll go to a text editor and
I have a little more this time codes. Sometimes seeing the time codes.
There is another one let's say I'm prepping up,
which I also remove if it's there.
And then so in vs code,
I can like all these things at the same time.
Okay. If you use like the usual notepad,
you can remove them one by one like that to
be vs quote on windows.
I just need to press control then down
to a one course or in multiple lines.
And then I select this, I just did it.
So now I take this text without the time,
uh, timestamps, I take it and paste
it to Ortiz to anchor it
and then add links here. So these are the links that,
uh, uh, uh,
sense some of these links should already be in a YouTube
video
put down. It should also be like,
at least. So now you see when I do control V it basic like
in one line. So of course it can, it's like this.
What I usually do is I do control shift.
So then it sorts it like that. I still need to edit it a
little bit.
And finally, I also take these two things and
put them at . So
I'm, this is the format. So first we talked about coma,
then line break. Then this is a bulleted list
with things we talked about, then links that speaker sense.
Also bulleted list in this too.
And yeah, the publication date is Friday.
So we'll have this. Yeah,
I have it here. So I think repeat this here too.
Yeah. So this should be today.
And then CSUN is the same as previous and then three,
this would be for say, so this one is season seven,
episode four, published on 11 February books
here to anchor. So I select 11 and then it should be 7:00 PM
central European time. So for your, probably to be a different time.
So it's 7:00 PM central European time click confirm and
season number. And this is from here.
So seven and then,
um, yes, right now I don't, uh,
I'll probably record a separate video later to have it
be so dark right now we can just leave it like that.
Don't think I need to do anything else.
So it's five, right? No, it's four.
It is four. Yeah.
And I click schedule and
then a forgot to results. They should see that.
Yeah. This episode about career coaching with Lindsay is scheduled for
today. And then ideally,
as I said, the moment the pilot is here.
We should go ahead and put this on,
uh, end core and scheduled and what we might not
have. So maybe this, um, the editor,
our pastor, and we don't have, uh,
at the time codes yet, we still go here,
click on new episode, we upload the file,
which has gone there. We talked about section and we put the links with,
uh, uh, yeah, the link sometime with ScaleIO,
which has don't have, um, uh,
we talked about section and we add this later into it this later.
Yeah. You can just click on this then.
Is this the edit button? And we add these things
here. I think I even might have this call
to edit podcasts. I don't remember if I recorded
this.
Um, yeah. I don't know. Maybe you saw this all today.
Hey. Yeah.
It's we don't need to it because we don't change it.
Yeah. This is how we schedule, um,
podcast episodes with inquiry.
And then what I will need to do now is after this episode
is scheduled for me to,
uh, to create this page here,
podcast page, it's a little bit technical so far now,
uh, you will probably not need to do this.
Maybe I will create some form that you will need to,
um, if you in, and then I will execute your comments on
my end to make it easier for me to generate it.
But for now, this is what you need to do.
So this are your videos to Encore and
yeah, it's all.