Published in your, uh,
in your podcast episode and this one career coaching and cleansing a
short how to fill the form for this month.
So then I executed a script to side and this way it created this
page to now have this with,
uh, yeah. Now I want to,
um, make an announcement about this on LinkedIn.
I want to tell everyone that,
Hey, this podcast episode is now available.
So what I do for that is I have this notion page that tech
crowd to share with you.
So this
customer, those customers I'll
share it with you.
So this is just for taking notes.
So I will share this link with you. What they do now is
this is the announcement they make. No it's boring.
They use the same announcement every time outspent,
and then do want more to know more about Katie here from
quit looking into the Eastern data
talks club, podcast episode, to share your experience.
And then now we need to list things with Dr.
Wild, take him from there,
take them from the transcript,
tick this dot and a edit in front of,
in front of the bullet points. And it should be dot
diamond or whatever it is, then space then think.
Yeah. After the TB box,
the link
in
the name of Z. Oh yeah, your name and here.
So is this the announcement now I have copied this psycho to LinkedIn create
a post in,
um, from the DNC, uh,
it, and of course your name and then LinkedIn automatically suggests I
need to link data docs as well.
And then, uh, basically to me,
this is a company that the company is well.
Yeah, of course you might not know this. Uh,
it's fine. I will just, uh, if I see something like this,
I say, Hey, by the way, this is the company kind of rethink this
as well. And then again here,
um, that's
it, I'll just click some
business call. I make announcements about a podcast.