so again for hi again for all the process documents i
want at the beginning a description of why
we need this not what the document describes but why we need process documents
why we need to uhm change uh to add somebody on
the website or like whatever like not just so this is
how so or what like this describes what contain the document
contains but i want to understand when and why uh i want to use
this document and all the process documents have to have this i have
mentioned that many times so this is a good starting point but
what i actually wanted to see is a document that describes not the process
document about creating process documents but a document that describes
how process documents should be created uhh well i see that this sounds very
similar but like more like a template
or like what exactly they should contain not the actions they should- sequence of
actions you take to create a process document which is also useful and we
should keep it but what the process document should contain like in
all the loom videos i sent you previously uhh i don't want to repeat
myself like you should go through these videos and listen to what i said
and note this down in a document in a google document and
we will use this document to understand how our process
documents should look like what they should contain what information is important what
is not important because right now i see that we add a lot of
information that is kind of redundant mmm like for example sometimes
we have the same thing here the same thing here and then the same
thing here at the end and actually like i think we
forgot to have a loom video this one doesn't
have a loom video so this is fine um but yeah like describes the
structure of the document describes what should be here so
so that it should not only describe what the document
contains but when to use it and add some examples so then
let's say Feleria wants to create a process document she would open this document
and understand what exactly- she needs to do and what kind of content she
needs to put in not just take screenshots hmm
yeah please start a document and mention all the things I mentioned
in the previous rooms if you have to re-watch them re-watch them but like
I need to- uhh because I think with this document it
will be clearer how our documents will look like so our documentation
will become better and I want to actually
comment this hmm so proceed to loom or like
I don't understand what this actually means umm
not so sometimes like first you get a loom link
from me right and this loom link you receive through telegram
or through the to-do list not necessarily the to-do list if I
add this to the to-do list it's there but it might be not there
right so if you need to Thank you.
to say that to the loom link provided to be directed this is very
confusing so please still write that um next proceed
to datadox google drive and click on the process folder and
click on the folder There we go. Umm.
We also need a guideline like what kind of categories we have and how
do we select to which category we put.
Right? It could be a different document that we link but we need to
have a dista description. So let's say if somebody who does
not know well this thing, or let's say Valeria wants to play for the
document, how will she know to which category to put.
So we need a description of each category.
In a. . document somewhere. So then you open this description and you see
okay this document goes here. Uhh
then create a copy of a template.
Okay umm.
So the template is already,
we need to recreate the template because like if we need to change page
setup to make sure that it's pageless then it makes umm means that the
template is uhh not pageless.
And we need to rework the template too.
So I would suggest that we delete all the templates that you have and
create only one in the root in the process.
We call it template. And uhh like let me just do
it here. We'll create a template.
You will start putting the actual content there as uhh
template as you also put the,
ehm ehm ehm let me just let me also create it.
So this is what I was talking about. Uhh,
let's call it process documents,
documents guide.
So I want to create these guidelines.
And some things that you mentioned here creating process
documents. We can put there. So then if the template is already pageless then
we don't need to step. Right? Umm.
Edit. This is.
Yeah, context why we need to do this.
Umm.
Yeah okay you actually mentioned what uhh like I think the-
This is- we should have this at the beginning.
So this is not a process document about creating process documents.
It's a document that describes how process documents should look like.
So what I have in mind is not a step-by-step thing,
but more like an- some edit.
Document uhh that people can read.
Not a sequence I have fractions. To understand what a good document should contain.
Just start with something and then we will iterate.
And then we can also keep this thing.
Uh, take screenshots and also instead of taking screenshots also
sometimes you might need to go to the actual system and instead
of taking screenshots from the video. Take screenshots from that system.
Also mention that. Uh.
Ahh.
Yeah, this is good. So like,
as far as the process document about creating process documents uh,
goals. It's- good with a few exceptions,
a few things I mentioned, but this is good.
Like, we definitely need to have this document.
Just at the beginning I want to uh,
maybe this is how we- we don't need the- Alright, let's
do this. Let's remove
that one and just keep this one. Just add more information here and then
add step-by-step instructions. So I want to have good
examples uh of content.
I want like a description of what a good document contains.
Please re-watch the videos and like everything I mentioned there put
in the document in writing. And then when it comes
to the template let's have only one template here.
I think I should call it process document template so it's not confusing.
And remember I asked you to create an index for templates too.
It's still not there. Please do this.
Mmm.
Okay. Pause that.
Process document.
So here we will create a template.
And the reason I add underscore.
So it is the first one. In the.
This list.
And what you do is you make a copy here.
And then you move this copy to.
Thank you. One of the folders,
right? Let's say we want to move to the air table.
So then instead of having templates that could be outdated in each
of the folders, we will.
Where is it?
Where did it actually go?
Here? Okay,
so instead of having this copy of the copy of the copy of the
copy, just remove all these copies and let's have.
uhh this template,
we create a copy of the template and we move the copy of
the template to the process document,
to the bread one folder.
Mm. Okay,
and I assure that all the documents are indexed,
like. Like for example,
where's the punctation? Yeah,
like. Make sure that all the process documents are in the index,
because I see documents that are not in the index,
even though they should be. So make sure that they are there.