Um, hi, I wanted to show you how I reach out to people.
So, um, somebody recommended your ex-colleague
and I wanted to invite him.
So what could I do is say from this link?
So it's in LinkedIn,
so for LinkedIn, whatever, we'll do a whole press connect and a note and
then write,
and then I'll write about
what the
cost and the meal,
and then
I'll
change it. So I invite,
so I sent an invite to him and then I included
message click send,
and yeah, hopefully now he replies.
Then if he doesn't, we'll see how actually to reach out to him.
And here, what I wanted to show you is sometimes people may comment to
reach out to other people. And what I usually do is,
uh, give a bit of context and Ty mentioned people who
recommended, and that usually helps.