So I wanted to comment on remove the small talk.
So usually when we start five minutes before the event,
there is some conversation going on. But this conversation is not useful for
the audience. That's why we keep it. So at some point,
I start sharing the screen and say Hi everyone,
welcome to our event. This event is brought to you by DataDogsClub,
which is a community of people who love data.
Basically, you need to find this thing when they share this screen and then
when I say that, like, Hi, this event is brought to you by DataDogsClub,
and you cut everything before that.
Uh, sometimes very infrequently,
occasionally, I might not say these words,
I might not share the screen. Then you will need to use your judgment
to find the place when the talk actually starts,
you can always confirm with me, but in 99% of the cases,
Hi everyone, The events start with that,
at least podcasts, episodes, and webinars.
Workshops, and course videos are a little bit different,
so then you will learn this,
and then probably we should keep a document where we write how exactly
you determine whether the event started or not,
and if before was a small talk, um,
so please create a document for that. So for this particular event,
we don't need to do anything because it has been edited already.
For new ones, you will need to do this so we will have one
next week, right, with Rachel, so then you will need to do that.
For this one, it's already good.