Hi, uh, sometimes we help other communities,
uh, to promote their events. So for example, here,
this is our meetup. And then this on this meetup,
we cross post to, we create another event,
um, from envelopes community, they have an event and we also create the same
kind of event. So this is actually an in-person event,
uh, where it is, uh, there is this others,
right? So this is, uh,
this is already created. This has already our group,
right? So I want to show you how to do this.
So there is a, uh, also an event and they asked us to cross
promote their event. So this is what I want to do now.
So I will start with copying the details so
I can get the details and copy them here.
Now pay attention to the line rate breaks here.
So like these say yes.
Um, um,
no, no, this should be fine.
Then I already, I already saved the image,
so I just want to evolve this. So it is the image that I
saved. I, now
we need to copy the data. So the data is July five.
Oops. Um,
6 30, 6 32.
Oops, let me just close this deal.
It's for three hours. So,
Um, yeah, I think here,
um,  so then again,
you would be this planet labs,
Germany. Let me check if it actually,
it actually can find it. Yeah.
And this one we of course need to make sure that the address is
the same one. Yes.
The address is the same one. So this is not an online event.
And then yeah, we need to also check this COVID safety measures.
So the event will be indoors.
So indoor. Oops.
Um, it doesn't seem like mosques are required or COVID workstations are required.
Otherwise I think that it will be same.
Um, yeah. Now we need to,
to do the title.
So the title is, um,
I think it's a speaker 9 billion women in data,
and then we need to, uh, on this. So we need to follow the
same pattern here. So you see like first it's the name and
then in parenthesis, this one.
So I want to do something like basic, um,
meal,
right? I think this is the name of the community,
female tech leaders. Yeah.
So I think that's all.
Yeah, no, I'm going to just,
um, I think I need to add the cost.
So the cost is this one.
I don't know if he's in the group,
she's probably not see.
Yeah. I wanted to add here as she's not in the group.
So I cannot add her as a host.
Yeah, I think I
just hit publish.
Okay. Let's call you cross post events from other communities.