Um, so the speaker moved the event.
So now I want to show, how will we move them up?
So there will be an event today, but we decided to move it to
March. So for that, what I do is first day,
I did this on Eventbrite. So I go to click on this and
it takes forever to load. Okay. Now basic
basically I think this is where I set the date.
Yeah. And here in basic info,
we'll change it to March. So this is the date where,
uh, where we're mood. So it's 1st of March 5:00 PM as well.
Um, okay, so now  got
adjusted automatically. If it's not,
we need to adjust mine. Then I click save.
So that is sufficient for Eventbrite.
Then we need to do the same or meet up to go to meet
up. Then this is a Steven today that we need to change.
So those are tools.
Uh, and then again,
there's choose a different, I chose a different date here.
1st of March. I don't think I need to change anything else here.
Should I just click save changes? Then one other thing is
I also need to adjust it in the calendar.
So it is a public calendar that people use for
subscribing to the events.
So this is the event that we have in the Google calendar and here
in Devon, who also need to change the lead it's 1st of March,
you see it can get adjusted automatically.
So everything safe and subscribe to this cousin that will also have that.
So I think we can see that now it's here.
And yeah, so,
uh, this event, I didn't announce it on LinkedIn.
So that's why, um, if it was announced on LinkedIn and we would need
to edit it there as well. So here we will not need this.
And then the last thing we need to adjust it to the website.
So on the website, it says the 1st of February,
so we need to edit this. That is the link,
this get up pages. We need to click on this link.
So we will have a different version of a website in some time,
but now this is what he use. So maybe when there is a different
version now for the Curtis, a different video right now.
Yeah. We need to go to data. Then there is this events,
the TMO, and I need to click it.
So here, this events for February are here actually.
So they can also need to put them this ones.
So this is actually in January.
So what would it, yeah, just
to keep it a little bit more organized,
then the events for February are,
so this one is a little bit here and
then there are no events for March. So now move it a little
bit. So create a section here,
court, March, and then I will edit there and then I will
change two to three. Okay.
So ideally this is all you need to do.
Six year. I did a bit of arrangement typically.
I don't think you would need to say to that. Um,
so here it just changed the date. Um,
I don't need to change anything else here.
Now, when I scroll all the way down and
then just click can be changes.
And then now you trued out my declare update to the website.
So if I go to two actions that we'll see that you
see right now in this, there is a task of updating the website.
So it's cute Tinder cure.
Yeah. Now it's running. So it's doing some technical things that are not
important, but yeah, the important thing it's,
it's a progress. Then it takes
a, as you see one minute, 10 seconds,
oh, slightly more than one minute to,
uh, for this to change. So you play at eight now.
It will not be changed still. So it needs a bit of time.
Okay. It's still in progress. I think it needs a couple more seconds.
Can click on this actually to see what's going on. Yeah.
So it has finished. So now it's doing this employee to stop.
Yeah. So once we have D*** here in the website should be outdated and
she is doing the point.
Oh cool.
And now I can just reload it. And I see that this
thing moved to 1st of March.
So this is how you move the events. Uh,
you speak your, uh,
MOOCs, uh, the .