I want to show how to schedule videos in this particular case,
I'm going to schedule a open-source spotlight video,
this one. So I'm going to click on details.
And first of all, time code, this was like a placeholder.
This is the place where time calls will go.
So we don't need that. Um,
yeah. Then for open source spotlight, we need to select playlist playlist
should be open source spotlight done.
Then PTO then, uh,
to I click here,
visibility clicks, Cato, and I'm going to schedule it
for today 5:00 PM.
And this is central European time. And
I just click down. So now scheduled.
Yeah, I think that's all I needed to do was,
uh, sorry. Now we don't have a 10 table when exactly we should,
but at least this typically happens on Wednesdays.
So, so typically it happens on Wednesdays.
Uh, for example, the next one, this aim open source
spotlight about aim. Once we have time codes and
links from the speaker, we will release it for
the next Wednesday. Yeah.
Which is 23, 20
third. I will not go in.
I am not going to release it right now.
So once we have 10 calls, then we can schedule it.
Okay. Some things, this is how your schedule
will be just.