I think it's a good idea. We,
so when I ask you, please schedule something for tomorrow for
open source spotlights specifically. Um,
so when you do this, you on August kiddo,
and this is actually
Have
This thing here, usually what's the next thing we
do. Uh, whereas the travel board,
Our Trello board opensource, we ask the guests to
share the email, uh, the event with
Recording with their network.
So, um, here, because usually 5:00 PM
central European time, you're usually sleeping during this time and
I'd like them to receive the email immediately after it is
published. So what we can do here is,
uh, schedule And
email. Um,
the link I think are,
I think, yes. Yeah.
Maybe we don't do this as a separate meeting,
uh, a separate item,
but this one, Um,
Hmm.
Yeah. So here we'll have a template. So the way you can do this,
so you write it, have a mold,
send it, this is just an example. So you would apply it and
then you sent schedule sound like,
of course you need to The link
and then you in everything,
And then you just do a schedule. And if I ask you to schedule
it for tomorrow, select the date and time.
So for example, tomorrow,
Yeah, you'll probably need to do translation translation.
Um, but yeah, let's say if you or eat for 17 or
5:00 PM, then you can scale all the email email or 17 0 5.
So then you just schedule sound, and then they will get the email immediately
after the recording costs life. So they,
if they receive it, they can already share it with pain network because
it's hugely helpful for YouTube when at
the beginning, right. Immediately after it gets more views.
So if they share after we publish,
it's actually with her, by the way,
and notice that,
uh, like after,
if you have a colon, there should be no space.
Please pay attention to the patient.
Yeah. So this is how you can schedule emails,
um, about open source spotlight after scheduling the
YouTube link.
Now you can also add where you can create a process doc
and edit here. So I'll have this doc
and then we already have a template. And then in this document,
please link the template as well. Okay.