Hi, I wanted to show you how to schedule social media posts.
I think you have access to them through us.
So here in, you'd go to this calendar icon And
you have a calendar you can select it is,
this is my time zone in GMT plus two.
Um, so for example,
eight, 8:00 AM. Usually I announce LinkedIn posts.
Yeah. Posts, and then I can select an account.
And here you select, for example,
this data talks club LinkedIn account,
And now we need to write a text and for the text we
had promotion in the,
in the newsletter. So I want to show you
also how to, uh,
announce how to post these promotions to social media as well.
So just copy the title,
Then copy the content.
And then I copy the text here and
all right. Interlink
And also, I
think I'd say sufficient. Also we have visual
here, so we'll save it safely.
Oops.
So I see if the image, And then I hear
select file to upload. So then the usual is used
here
And I just clicks Cato. So this is how we schedule posts
to LinkedIn with quotes, and then we want to schedule another post
to Twitter. So I usually do this for Twitter.
I think 3:00 PM work, but for
LinkedIn usually in morning. Um,
so for Twitter afternoon works,
whether she's here. And we said that, wait,
there is no, I think only 2, 2 83
account. So the records,
they separate video, but yeah, this is how you get
at all posts on LinkedIn, how to promotions.
So please make a process document.
And next time when we have some promotionals in the newsletter,
then yeah, this is how we do this.