Um, so remember this, we need,
so give away the book. So now I want to select the winners.
So I copy this hero.
So I go to this tutor, select directions,
and then we have select winners here.
I, um, I click around for three
euros here that I just copied from here,
and then they can run workflow. So know it will take
a bit of time to actually run this either.
Let's give it a bit of time. Um,
oh, it shouldn't be too long.
Yeah. Like here, what it's doing. Exactly.
It's not super important, but yeah, we see that it finished now
we'll go back and we see that there
is this folder winners and there is this suite.
So this is the Euro, just in case they copied there.
There is no nothing else, but this,
but yeah, just this up.
And, uh, 10, 10 minutes.
Um, we say we give five copies.
So we just, from these five, we get stop the
top five and decide the winners or the book.
And what I will do now is something like,
uh,
uh, I don't remember
what I wrote last time. I think last time we did some texts,
um,
DM me and
um, last time it was something now on the spot.
Yeah. Let's so this is the message. So we will actually do this,
not from my account. Uh, maybe I will also ask you to do it
from my account, but now, uh, but probably you will do this from not
from my account, but from data docs,
but I can't. So I think in the previous
email, I in the previous gave you the template.
Yeah. Depending on. So I'll just think about this a little bit,
how to phrase it better. But the important part here is this is how
you select, so this is how you select
the winners for in giveaways.