Hi, so I want to show you how to send emails with
sponsorship, it's not a sponsorship tag,
but like with our media kit. So there is the link,
I will send you this link right now,
or I will include it.
I will get, I guess I'll add it to the loom video.
So this is the link I usually send to potential sponsors that describes what
the community is about and what kind of things we can offer to
potential sponsors. And this guy is a potential
sponsor. So what I want to do is send him an email
that, with this thing basically.
Uhm, and I want in the future you to help me do that.
So what we can say is eh hey name,
so hey Jim following up and then here
we would insert on that,
usually it would be our conversation in LinkedIn or our conversation
in Slack or whatever, here is the document
that describes things we can potentially do together,
please take a look and let me know if anything there is interesting
for you. So in this case,
let us know, so when you write instead of writing,
let me know, let us know.
And then perhaps, so since the email will be from you,
you can say, hey Jim, following up on our conversation from LinkedIn,
I want to send you this document, uhm,
one more time. Hey Jim,
I'm Francis from DataDocsClub and
I wanted to follow up on the conversation we started in LinkedIn and
we want to send you this document that describes things that we can potentially
do together yeah,
if you want to talk more about anything there please let us know.
So that would be the template, we will reiterate on that,
but please send it to Jim.
Why it's him? Jim. Uhm,
it's probably Jim, not him, because like J and H are close.
So send it to Jim at hopsworks.ie
and send this document. And I will include the links in the comments of
this sloom. And yeah,
before sending this, run it by me,
then let's create a template.
And then we will send sometimes like
I reach out to somebody and they say okay send an email and then
I'll just ask you to do that.