Yeah, another thing. So we send sometimes invoices,
like I need to make invoices, um,
not in keynote, but outside. So for that,
uh, me open, uh, drive,
I will show you. So then what's is already prepared.
Uh, we'll make a separate video to show you how to make
this invoices. Um,
right now under the invoice is already there. So just go to the Arabs,
um, invoices and here,
you know, this, uh, Nvidia GTC invoice.
So they already have help in ways, and this is what the theft
in the invoice. So the reason I need to
make this in ways outside of, you know,
here's me, Cosentino I cannot make invoices in USD in dollars
in phenomenal. I can only do them in Euro,
in euros, but Nvidia works with,
um, USD only. So they don't work with them on with yours.
So this is the invoice I have. So you can see that actually the
format here of the invoices is month 10.
So she is D slash one. So it's like 1, 2, 3, 4 every month.
So let's say it would have something,
uh, 10, uh, in October it will be also something like one issue
day to be.
Um, Hmm. So let me just at
there's um,
we have, because it's August, so make it a,
Hmm. Actually, I don't know. I think they have,
yeah, I think they asked me to send the invoice on the day of
the promotion, so I will need to do send it on a Keith,
but clearly in g-mail we can schedule it.
So here you see on next. So probably I can also,
yeah, I can do this as well, but yeah, you will be doing this
strong g-mail so advocacy.
This is my Datadog's popping. Well, not Gmail.
Um, yeah, so let me, you should, anyways,
so we will send it on the 5th of September,
but typically you would put today's date and send it immediately without the delay.
That's Lisa stain wise. And then what I do is I download this invoice
in PDF. Um,
I open it
and I go to Dropbox and in Dropbox or yeah,
there's paper work and income invoices.
So this is a, the invoices we send to companies and I actually already
have this in the west. So you see that the form is,
uh, it's it's, uh,
this is the same invoice section on unloaded and I already in this folder.
So that's the same one.
And, uh, yeah, so the forum is because it's not paid yet.
It's underscore then the month, then the company I'm here GTCs and just the
kind of service theme they want.
Okay. So what I do now with this is I take this in a
voice and yeah,
I think, um, so there, this is unusual.
So usually you don't need to do this, but here they asked that,
uh, please send to all your invoices with the key or number reference in
PDF format. So I don't know if they mean that I should reference key
or number in PDF inside or just here.
So I did mention it here, so right.
Please find a voice or
Attach it
To that. But I don't know. Maybe they meant that I need to add
this PO somewhere here. Again,
this is not typical. So you don't need to put this insight in the
process document, but here,
I just want to show you the flow of what happens if the invoice
is outside of, you know what,
since I'm doing it here, let me do it.
So I'll,
I don't know. I'll put it here maybe.
Yeah,
Well, I'm going to do it here so they will hopefully figure this out.
So I had done loaded again
and then I go to the invoices
and I will replace the spawn.
So
We would replace it with this one. Um,
let me make sure that it actually, yeah,
so it has this deal reference here and
yeah. So now lets me touch it.
Um, or just leasing media,
Hold on.
And then right now I will send it a it,
so date. So it would
be this one and date,
um, let's say,
um, no, so they are based in the states,
so probably it will be already pays for them.
Okay. Yeah. Let me check.
Uh, so again, this PO stuff is unusual,
but they have some email to which sentence,
the invoice. Then Susan wrote me this.
So I included her in CC, but my a mark is the person who
I actually got in touch to about promotion.
So that's why he's also in CC, um,
score.
Okay. So I think that's enough. So just send it.
Yeah. Um, again here,
the main thing I wanted to show you is how you,
and yet, uh, that we actually have this folder invoices
in this folder, we have invoices outside of,
you know, then we need to send this invoice.
You follow the same procedure as previously with genome,
except you download this and a, you put this to the invoices,
folder, invoices, income invoices.
So I will tell you more later, what exactly is all the structure
is because we don't only have the invoices that are,
um, we're on Google drive. We also have you see,
maybe I'll tell you right now. So you see, we have this plus thing.
So this plus is already paid invoices.
And so this is, was from ,
but yeah, I, this month soon,
I think it's actually tomorrow. Yeah. Tomorrow I will be preparing tax
report. So I will talk more about what we have here.
Exactly. Okay. So.