Yeah, I almost forgot to send the tax support.
So I wanted to show you how to do this. Uh,
so last time we prepare to,
right, so now, um,
I want to show you how to send it to my accountants.
So not a leak. So this is a secure email and,
um, the Tiana
is, so this is your email.
You don't need to remember here emails because I am made in UCC.
So you will see this. So you need to create an email
with this subject. So data talks about club then the month,
month, August, 2022.
And then, uh, what you need to do is you go to the support,
you select this one. So from columns a to column F
alright, so these work, and then it includes here.
Um, so we already prepared the
archive, so I will do the archive right now.
So then just that, okay. Remember the button is data talks club last
year, minus month. So my touching.
Okay.
And I think that's all right.
So, uh, they have a table and they have the zebra.
So yeah, I am sent to now.
Yeah. So this is how we send reports.
You account for bookkeeping.