Okay. So where do they work? So we will need to send some things
to the attendees. So I wanted to show you how to send emails to
people, to sign up for a workflow. So what are the workflow?
And then we are getting,
let's see, they keep changing it's and
yeah, it's managed to attendees emails,
um, event in
UML,
um, the work
or buy a lots
of columns there.
This will be different for when we need to send
something. Let me just make it a bit
larger.
The workshops I'm going to be your
female stuff.
I don't think it's actually needed. So I
will send a chest event to myself to see.
So for the workshop, I guess that is enough.
So I will just send it right now.
Sometimes we might send it like one day before it starts or something like
this, but, um, yeah,
so I will just send it. So
now this email,
and let's make a copy of the text because I also now want
to show you about the same thing in,
But,
Um, they send it to myself,
so copy it and
then this, and yeah,
so members who RSVP and,
and I will call it message.
I'm done.
Yeah, I dunno.
Yeah.
So this is how you sent messages, emails to our
events.