Also wanted to explain what this company's is.
I think I did talk about this last time.
So when we add companies, you see that this is empty,
right? So these are the companies that we just added.
So we need to add status. So if we don't have status for them,
they become prospects. So just put,
start those prospects actually Jet Brains.
I think we add, we have Jet brains already,
so let me quickly check if we have Jet.
Yeah, so lemme see this one.
Jet Brains. Um,
yeah, I'll see how to, to merge them later.
Um, yeah, but for now,
so what we can do apart from the brains,
I think I can just remove them because they don't have any content assigned
to them. I can just remove them.
Uh, yeah.
So you can, um, for them actually for weights and biases,
we already have it's established content contact.
For the rest it is,
um, status is,
uh, prospect, right?
So we haven't contacted them. And then for text,
you probably, I don't know,
I don't know how much you can put this here for contacts,
probably not much too. But what you can put here is the relevancy based
on, based on the relevancy of the content,
right? So you can just put here the relevance of the company and then,
uh, fill in this information. So for example,
in the website on that I just showed you,
we have the information about the website. Maybe you can have,
you can find their LinkedIn account too,
Twitter account too, Uh, GI up,
not important, just to have a way to find them quickly if,
uh, we want to find people who work there.
So have enough website and LinkedIn is useful.
Um, and then for contacts, uh,
we will cover that later. Hmm.
Okay. Yeah, I think that's,
uh, that's all. Yeah,
for text. Um, uh,
I'm still thinking how useful texts are. Maybe we'll just,
uh, drop them later.