So just wanted to say a few words about,
uh, what to do with this when we accidentally have her wrong company here.
So this one is not, um, let me close it.
So I found that, uh, this, that this company is APA Kaka,
but it's actually not, uh, the right company.
So we need to go here to this.
Um, um, so right now I want to show you how we or
how we merge two records into one, right?
So here in this record, we have content and if we had people,
uh, contacts the procedure or deals,
the procedure would be the same. So I want to merge this two and
get rid of, uh, the Kafka record.
Record. So I go to the content here and change
company from oops,
from Kafka to Confluent.
Why do we have to Confent?
Yeah, you will do this with, uh, this content,
right?
So the direct Confluence. So we will need to merge them and,
uh, please do this with Confent. So now,
um, yeah, I updated it to Confent. And yeah,
by the way, when you do this with Confluent, you see that,
uh, there are two of them, or you cannot see it here,
but one has, uh, web,
web address, but web here, the other dozens.
So you all need to merge that too. Okay.
So that I did, and since we don't have any other,
uh, contacts, content, uh,
deals, we can just go ahead and where is it now?
I think I can just go back and then I see it,
and here in the dots we can just delete it,
right? So you will need to do it with the confent that has one,
two,