Hi. So just wanted to ask you about a few
things. So first, um,
so this clouds see there, for example, you edit them and yeah,
so this is the company, right? So because you were going through the conference,
usually when you click on a, a link,
so that, let me open it. So when you go through the conference and
then there is, uh, this Microsoft Azure for example,
right? So you click on this and then you have a link.
So please, when you do this,
you let me, Microsoft Azure.
So when you do this, get this link from here and
put it also here,
right? So then we have, um, the,
um, the website. I don't know why it's,
uh, Australian. Oh,
maybe it doesn't matter. Um,
yeah, so please, when you fill this in,
um, add the links and that
will help me than easier add text later so I can click on these
things and then, um,
see what kind of text I should add to these companies.