Um, pain. So regarding the to-do list.
So you, so for this is things
that are done, so you keep them,
and it was something like this,
right. And this turned out to be a bit confusion
for the script. So it started inserting these things here.
So what I want to ask you next time.
So they, if you want to hide them to first move them
like this, so just like drag and drop.
So you just put them here,
like for this great thing and step up and
then, alright. And then now everything
that is done already, uh,
on top, so all of them are together and then
everything that is not done is here.
Yeah. So I think it's, um, this way it's easier and then it's not
confusing for the script. So the scape always here
at the end. So it was tying it to the middle.
Let me see. It was trying to write something to the middle.
Um, yeah. So better to like put things that
I've done. Um, so for example,
you've finished this one, just knock them up and then write
them.