. Um, so we're running out of money on a Revolut account,
so Revolut, um, I typically use Revolut for online payment,
uh, because they don't have, um, like if I use Phenome,
there are some fees. Anyways, so there is,
uh, this Revolut account, and maybe you actually saw that recently there was
a transaction, MailChimp transaction.
Uh, yeah, you see this from relu.
Um, so now I want to,
Uh,
To move some money to Relu. So this is how I do it.
So first of all, we copy this is the bank account from Revolu,
and then I go to the main one and move some money there.
So that's probably, um,
no, it's already here. So I think what you should do instead is not
taking this, uh, Avon, but Right.
Alex, that's me. Yeah.
And this is the same. Oh, no, it's not the same actually.
Um,
yeah, we need to make sure that this is this one because,
um, like this one is business and the previous one was not business.
I think, um, probably we need to,
um, remove the old one. Okay. I want to move 3000 there and
yeah, just want to make sure it's the right one.
And I just pay now,
so I will ask you to do this sometimes.
So let me confirm it.
Okay. So this is how you transfer money to our revenue account.
Uh, let me check if I should or
Yeah, I'll do this offline. I'll don't need to record this.
I want to remove the other, uh,
my other account so it doesn't come up in search.
But yeah, so just in case copy Ivan,
when do this.