uh so I tried to take a look at this and the problem
is what I showed you so the problem is you see this not found
authors for these emails and this is the problem and
I made the error messages a bit more um
how to say like previously it was not saying which person
it was trying to find so you see here in the logs in large
it says check in the person and read the trial like this and then
says person for file and the petrela already exists which means that if we
go to the log's club then I
think it's people it's like hidden and we type andy petrela
we see him right because he already
did something before so we already have a
profile this is why so it exists that is why
we do not process it here right?
and,
and the status is not processed so we skip it what I can do
is maybe just make it done so next time its not processed but
umm, there is this process document processing
people who are already on the website so it was uHHHH sometime
before and we can see here and the engi
paterla already exists but later we see engi
paterla if- is not found right so it exists but not found
at the same time and we have a process document how to process people
who are already on the website and this is what you should do so
we already have a process document please just go through this process document
and rerun one more time and maybe also change
this process document to add what I just described so the symptoms like how
you can see that this is indeed the problem so and the symptoms are
umm.
it already exists but here you see in the logs that it's
not found and here if we go to this data docs
club slash people we can see this person there right so these are the
symptoms. And then it's uhh that's why we need to go through
this document. And then on a separate note I want you also
like for this document we need to umm umm
rework it a little bit. So first.
I want all the process document we have and we will do this when
we go through all this document index.
Is if it's page it has pages we need to turn
it into pageless. Umm.
So this is. All we do it page set up pageless.
And then we remove all these page breaks.
I don't know if I already showed you that but when
we revise. It's the process documents we need to do that
for all the documents that we have.
We remove page breaks.
Alright so you will modify it.
This document would also add the,
the context, right? Like we discussed.
You will add to why when we need this document.
And just follow through this document and you will be able to resolve the
problem.