Hi, so the reason we did not see that in
our Phenom that they paid is because they are
the money is in the merchant account So this is like usually this is
what we see when I go to Revolut but then I go to merchant
and this is the money, right?
So we can see that this is the payment from them.
And we can see the processing team.
So right so the invoice was for five.
Thousand, but we needed to pay this amount so we need to
also declare this as an expense And i'm
pretty sure this is not the first time I record this video But
um, so please check if we already have a process document And if we
do update it if we don't create a new one,
so the first process document would be for creating
these bookkeeping documents Um for declaring the the piece.
All right, so we need to declare them And I think
this is how we do it. We just go and print And
in print we see we have this right so here we have this process
entity So right now you just save it Let me
Save it as pdf And then uhm yeah You save it and
you send it to that email Or Yeah
I think this is what we do Like we do with other invoices So
let me just put I'll put it on pause and then I'll do that
Okay, I saved this document It should appear
In our uhm
How do you call it? Bookkeeping uhm
No, it should appear a bit later.
I'll check it So then um the second process document I want
you to create And again, please check.
Uh, if we already have that, I think I think this is not the
first time I'm recording this video So you click withdraw Oh
f*** Yeah,
I guess I'll do this later Uhm
Yeah, I don't know, what is that?
So I'll do this later and then yeah,
in the meantime, please check if we already have process document for that