So I wanted to show you how to update videos in this github repository.
So this github repo is for the course and
we have different modules here. So let's me first open the playlist where you
upload the videos. So in this playlist,
so this is the playlist and we have this
video right. Previously we had um
this one, oh sorry, so here we still if
so what I did is um this is the repo and then I just
clicked on the first module because we are here it's one 1.2 which means
we need to go to the first module and I just scroll down and
we have the these links right and now if I open it it will
go to the old video. Hi everyone in this video I want to
show you how to configure it. I don't know if you hear the recording
here but like there's this ding sound and then it's not as loud
as this one. In this video I want to show.
Yeah. So this is the new one and that was the one is the
old one. So what we want to do is to replace these
links. All right.
So this is the link. So let's scroll to 1.2.
This is 1.2.
Right. And here we have this link.
So I will send it to, uh,
to, you know, Telegram. So you have it.
Okay,
so this is the link. And there are two places.
The first one First, there are two things that we need to care about.
So the first is this parameter.
So that starts with a question mark B equals.
else. this is the video, and the second one is the playlist.
So for this course, for LLMZoomCamp,
this is the ID of this playlist. You can see it here.
So this is the link, right?
So this is the video, and this is the playlist.
So for this one, we don't change the playlist.
We just take the link and we update.
The link here, right? We update it here and we update it here,
right? So this is the the second video.
We also need to update it for the third.
Let me just do that. I'll do it here. Oops.
Hi everyone. Welcome back. I'll,
uh, I'll do it here so we don't,
uh, so I don't wait till you update it.
Again, we'll just update it in two places.
Now for,
Welcome back. Let us update
before. So this one for,
two? Very common question.
This is saying new one, right?
1.5
Welcome back Thank you.
Welcome back to
Okay, so this is how you update it and also when
when I sent you a new video, I'll show how to do it.
When I sent you a new video, you first go to the proper module,
then you click edit,
and then now you find the place where to put it.
And here you see video, here is nothing,
video. So if there is video,
we just replace the the word video with this. If there is nothing, we
put it directly under the caption,
under the the title. Okay,
so now let us use this one.
And the this is the
this is the link. So for the second module,
please finish it. Please do it for all the videos we uploaded.
And create a process document for that. So for LLM course,
it's like that. For other courses,
it's a little bit different, but also when we need,
I'll show you how to do that.
Okay, so this is how you update the links to the course
videos in the course repository.