Hi. So you just,
it's this thing, a new event,
visualizing mission to,
um, have table for them. Say,
I wanted to show you how you can actually add this yourself to the
website. I created something that will
let you at this yourself. So go to the,
get help page of the website. It looks plump,
uh, GitHub ,
I'll send you this link and then you go to
options and then in actions use to generate
all and hear engineering.
You click around and then confirm,
and then it will take some time. So it will take a couple of
minutes. I can see that the previous thing around two minutes,
three minutes. So it takes a bit of time,
but yeah. Now after doing this,
um, yeah, you, you don't need to wait for me to have this
with, uh, uh, itself.
Um, maybe I will show you how to actually check that things
are edit correctly.
So will not call here. I would go to the previous round that just
want to show you how it looks like.
So here you need to click on this genital.
And then, uh, from all those things,
there are a bunch of jobs. Most of them prepare the environment.
This is a bit technical. So anyways,
you are interested in this thing,
this may call, and then you see that it
says processed zero people. So this is the form first processes
in this table. This form people,
that's the first group. That's all the people.
Then it processes books. Um,
so before previously, when I run with zero people edit zero and
zero, edit this podcast
either. It was actually a podcast and it's one,
this processed one podcast,
and then it processed zero events. So you actually
don't need to go here.
Everything should be fine. Um,
but just in case, um,  can
see what is running. So this is the thing I just executed right now.
Um, yeah, I just finished. And then if you go to make all right
now and say protest one
event, this the event,
it took this event from here from
this. And yeah.
Now if we can back to the main,
uh, there is a new commit.
So it's coming from GitHub actions and you
don't need to do this. All you need to do is just click a
button, but this is a bit more information to double check.
Maybe that things work. Um,
yeah, you see that this thing was added and now
in the website is being updated.
And once this thing just pages built and deployment,
then, then yeah,
it will have an updated version
this point.
Okay. Completed. So now if we,
if we, sorry.
Yeah, we'll have visualizing machine learning. So in summary,
what you need to do is automate your document and
process document. You go into actions,
you select generate, and you click workflow.
That's pretty much it. And then the rest is just a bit more
information. You don't need to document it right now.
If you want to see if things progressed,
you go to January and click
my call here to see what actually it protest some,
they just call you do this. And if this thing,
one of the steps is red becomes red,
then we'll not be able to produce an event.
Then you will need to let me know that something is important.
So I will probably receive an email. It's something that's broken.
And just in case, if let's say you run and then five minutes after
that, you come back and you see in actions that,
that it's all right. So something like this,
right? And then you just think, okay,
let's hold.