So the problem is with a bunch of videos that I recorded.
In particular all first module except the very first video.
So starting from 1.2 and the first module from
the second module. They all have
uhm they are quite uh silent,
very quiet, you can hear it.
And at the beginning there is this ding,
you hear it too, right? Usually in loom for some reasons you always have
that. So this is annoying.
And that's why we will use the tool that I built.
You, this is the file I sent you.
Start so that there are two components like the uhm the the
user interface and the terminal. First you select the file you want to edit.
So this is the uhm the file.
When you browse it automatically detects by how much you need to increase the
volume. And also this is not automatic but
this is at the beginning this ding sound you want to cut.
it. So this is from where we start.
So usually you don't need to change it if there is this ding.
If there is no ding then you put it to zero,
right? So first you do a test run.
Click process and then it's complete and then there
is a new file only for one minute.
Hey everyone, in this video I want to show you how to configure your
environment. You hear that it's much louder in this part you will give
call up you can just run things locally for the second module google and
access to a machine with gpu now let
me go back I remove the test run click process so
test run is just for testing now it actually redo redo
is redoing the whole video so when it's
over we will see like a
sign that it's over.
So it will take a bit of time.
So it's over and we have the new file.
Hi everyone, in this video I want to show REST manager.
Yeah, so this is louder and we
don't have this ding sound. And then,
just in case,
so you will need to do this for all the files.
And if you need to select the next one,
you again do the same thing. Let's say this is the next one.
Now it will analyze it. And yeah,
it thinks it needs to increase it a little bit.
But yeah, so this is how you do it.
You of course don't do this This is just an example that this is
how you proceed with the next one. And quickly show you how you download
videos from YouTube.
You probably know that. But just in case,
you go to YouTube, to YouTube and go to a video
that we're interested in and we will need to do this
one, this one, this one, so we don't need to do it.
1.1 but the rest from LLMZoomCamp except
the new ones that I sent today we need to do this and
let's say for this one this is how we download the
videos. If we don't have a process document for downloading videos from YouTube I
think we do but if we don't please create it and
also please create a process document for using this tool but
only after you complete and re-upload all the videos.
So this is how you do it for this video.
So again, first test run, you check that things work.
Welcome back, this is Mo, And,
This is how you do it. So now, let me show you how to
close it. Oops.
Okay, so please create a doc,
process document. Two process documents,
one for the tool, one for downloading videos,
if we don't have them, this yet,
and then also do it for all the videos I showed,
and so we need to download the video,
apply the tool, and pre-upload the video,
and also first remove the video from the playlist,
this is important, first remove the video from the playlist,
then upload the new one, and if everything is fine,
after you re-upload all that, you don't delete them first,
you let me know, I check, and then you delete the old videos.
So this is what we do, and please do it as soon as possible,
we want to finish it before Monday, because on Monday this course starts,
and we need the first module be ready.
Okay, thank you very much. So first you do this,
then you give me a check-in, then you create process documents,
you send me the process documents, and then that's roughly the plan.
Yep, thanks.