So I also wanted to show you right now,
I'm filling in the form for Ellen.
And she said, it's fine to use your picture from LinkedIn.
But I noticed that LinkedIn and there is this,
uh, firing save by corporate image and
then it will spell it. So this is not what
I do in this case. Go to Google and then type
personal name and then,
okay.
Um, yeah, if there's an upside for you
and that's Jeff's picture, so then I I'll say this picture,
it's the same picture has it.
And then I do the same thing cause I do with pictures,
which is, um, I guess we need to them,
so we don't need, we don't need this square pictures,
so then let me make
it a square.
Shouldn't be in the sentence.
Okay. Now it's clear and it is,
do you want to know that maybe work?
Okay. Yeah. And that looks not
Okay. Just want to make sure that this is actually the same issue.
She's so probably to take
on other stuff.
Yeah. So this may be fine.
It's okay.
Like that is fine. I think so it looks similar
to that. Yeah. So the summary is LinkedIn.
Sometimes it's this thing stipes or whatever,
and I don't want to have them on the website as well.
Um, that's why I tried to paint this picture of the same feature somewhere
and then use that.