Hi, I wanted to show you alter.
We have in the shared folder and workshops.
So what we have here is a description of workshops,
and then there is a template. So this is a template to use for
creating workshops. And workshop is something that is similar to webinars,
except it's more, hands-on waiting only
one of them to, or channel.
There has been only one.
Yeah, because it just one, but we'll plan to have more of them.
They're very similar to webinars and the flow.
If I open the board,
I think the floor is mostly
the same. So I don't think we need to create like a server separate
template, but maybe the will we will,
but what these webinars do not have,
the workshops is this template maybe actually will
need to create a similar template for webinars as well.
So I think it's useful.
Yeah. So this is a description of a workshop,
so it will have title subtitle and date time and so on.
So for the description for, for the workshop,
usually it's, uh, maybe longer than the workshop and
yeah, there is, this is something that we will send to the
instructors, what the workshop to feel in.
And now I ordered the one, so there will be a workshop with soda.
So actually it will be 26th of April and then yeah.
Working title sort of core, but who'll be something different and
this is something I want to send to them right now.
And then, um, ask them to appeal the scene.
We will kill this together. And then based on that,
we will later create, maybe it's actually a good idea to do
something like this for events, or maybe it's a bit cumbersome.
I don't know. But for workshops may want to try
this for workshops and see how it goes, and then maybe we can do
something similar for webinars as well.
Okay. So in summary, um,
before that it's workshops, we have a template here and I
just click on this one, make a copy.
Then like in the same way as we do with podcast,
um, I click on this,
uh, uh, the copy, modify the title and,
um, send it to, uh,
to the speaker, to being stuck with this book. I will do it right
now. Actually. I need to create another one.
So let me
Your,
yeah. So template template here
for March. Let me check,
uh, time is correct.
May 17th. So
let me just
name and company.
And now I will send these two documents,
uh, based on this,
because we plan to do, do you live in ours with them?
So we'll send, um,
I'll send links to,
um, these companies for that. And so we'll take it from there.
So yeah, these are the templates for webinars for work.