Hi. I hope you're feeling better.
So I finally took some time to work a bit on
our CRM and the invoices section.
Because remember we have this problem of not following up with
invoices and then it's a mess.
So like, we don't remember who should pay
and what is due, at least in my mind it's difficult.
So what you suggested is to create a table in
the CRM, which is what I did. So we have a deal table,
which I did not change. It's the same deal as before.
And, yeah, by the way, we need to create invoices for this match,
I think. Anyways so what I wanted to do
in this video is to explain what I was thinking when creating this table
and how to use it. So, hopefully,
yeah, it will,
I'll make it easier. Okay,
sorry, not distracted. Anyways,
so I will take this invoice from Weights and Biases,
because it's an interesting one. There was one deal,
but four invoices, because we have invoices in different installments.
So I want to show you how do we feel in this invoice,
but then the rest will be pretty similar. And this is actually the first
time I am doing this here, so we will
figure it out right now.
So the first thing I do is put the invoice number here in this
section, in this column. Then notice for the node,
I would put this goal sponsorship second installment.
So maybe there is not always,
we don't always need the node, but I think for most cases we might.
So date sent is, I don't remember when
we send it, but let's say it will be 1306,
so this is the data. But it actually should be the date when we
send the invoice to the email.
Alright, so I will put 13 of,
what is June? But yeah, it's when we send the invoice.
13 of June. The due date is one
month after that yeah I think they actually paid it I
don't remember when they paid it so we can go to phenome and check
when they pay. So status is paid.
And then let me take a moment to explain the statuses.
So I've put four statuses to create,
created, sent and paid. So to create is,
so for example, we already made a deal.
For example, we think okay like there will be four installments we know
that there will be four installments for a deal.
And when we then
we can already create like a voice, like four different invoices without a number
here. Already put a note and not feeling
everything except like status to create.
And then also here we
will, let me, so here this is the link to
the deal. So here we will need to match with
the deal. So these deals come from this table,
right? So for all the deals we need to make the,
to find the deal of course. And let's wait some biases,
right? There should be more intuitive
numbers. Custom sponsorship package.
We need to work on on that custom sponsorship this
one So we need to come up with better names for deals,
so it's easier to find. But we link the record from here.
So then automatically we see what's the company,
the, I don't know why we need, I don't know why we need to
know it, let me just remove it. So we need,
we know the company and we know the contact, right?
Automatically from here. And by the way,
the contact now is different for rates and biases.
Please update it. And then for the invoice,
so in this case, I think I am confusing you.
So let's finish this one. And then I will talk about the
status to create, right? So for this one,
I finish and then I attach the invoice.
So the invoice is this one, I already saved it.
So this is the invoice.
So then we always have the the file,
right? So see that this is the file.
And in some cases when we
need to update the invoice, we just update the,
yeah, update it. So I don't know if we need to add money here.
So maybe not, because we don't really need to use it for accounting
or anything. It's more like for keeping track of what is paid,
what is not. And what we need to create.
So we don't forget to send in an invoice.
So date paid, I will put some arbitrary number here.
Let's say, I don't,
I think they were on time. So maybe double check this.
Go to film. We can actually here,
see here. Hmm,
it was quite late. So it was 30.
Not quite late, but they were a little bit late.
So yeah, this is how we do it. We need to,
like, this is already paid. And then for this weights
and biases, so let me show you this to create one.
So it's also weights and biases,
right? So we don't have an invoice. And by the way,
we should create. It right now, third installment,
right? So we see that we need to create this invoice for weights
and biases. And let me actually already create a duplicate
because we need also a fourth installment.
So already we have we know that like for this deal,
there are some in voices that we still need to create and
still, need to well,
you know, send. Let me also group like that.
So then we already see,
like, every time we create a record. So we,
oops, click here to add a new voice.
We feel all this in and then it will go automatically to one of
the statuses, right? So I think it's more or less clear.
If it's not, yeah, let's talk about that.
Okay. So we need to create. So what I want you to do now
is go through all the invoices and all the deals for this year only.
Don't go to the previous year and fill in this table.
Right. And then I will take a look at this and see maybe we
forgot something and then maybe if you can think
of what can be the deal here.
So this one is more like not a name, but more like a comment.
I don't know. We need to think by the way,
what is this?
We might be interested with the one topic of getting started with data access
management. What is that?
Anyways yeah,
please fill this in and then we will see how it goes.
Maybe we will need to adapt it. So that's all.