Okay. Actually, I already have this video using Figma for creating even banners.
So in this video, I show how to create that.
But, uh, I also, I wanted to do this again because for
this event, um, if I go to  website,
so for this website,
AB testing, the cower is this
one? No, this is the
old one. So I want to create like in a new format and for
that, I'll need to go to Figma.
I will need to also give you access to that.
If you don't care for an accountant Figma, you will need to create it.
Yeah. I think this one,
no, this is not the right one.
Yeah. I think this, this is it.
So let me look locate, and then I will
send you a copy of this thing.
So we'll call it data talks,
event binders, core funders.
So I'll share a link. So you don't need to actually
I've put this to the document, but yeah,
I think I will need to, to have your email,
once you register it in Figma.
Um, okay. I'll copy the link anyways.
So this will be the link that we'll send to you and
conduce. Yeah. So don't need these things.
Yeah. So I just want to give the things that we actually need for
events. Um,
the costs
and I will get off this one as well.
Okay. So this was a forecast.
It was up. Uh, so for YouTube or podcasts resort,
I need to this one. Oops.
And then for webinars, we'll need this one.
Oops. And for open source
spotlight, this one,
this would be the cover. So,
and then the rest, I will leave them aside for now.
Oops.
Okay. I think I need to move them one by one.
Yeah. So we don't need them right now.
So forget about them two.
We need these three.
Come on. Okay.
Yeah. So there's three podcasts and spotlight
larger. Um, so the one we just heard was
a B testing and then
yeah. Usually if part of this shouldn't be blue.
I don't know why it's not undo. Uh,
I don't know why. Yeah. I know why it's not blue because I just
typed this. I don't know which one,
which part to make blue now, maybe I'll just select AB testing as
well. Yeah. To do this,
a new go to field. And then there are two costs that we can
select or if it's just one, so you can click on this and then
in document cloud color also suggest this one or
you can alternatively put 1 61 61 16 hex here and
yeah. So shouldn't be also centered.
Yeah. So yeah, you don't need to remember it next time you edited.
It will be centered I think. And now we need the name.
So yeah, the name is, uh,
Um, I don't know why it's coping.
Yeah.
And then, uh, yeah,
don't like it because it's, there's a lot of anticipation,
but for now we can just go with, you know, with that.
And then, um, I have coughs pictures here.
Yeah, of course. So here then I would just save
this image to my downloads from the website and
I will walk here two foot tall.
Uh, yeah, this control is here.
So then the few is image and then I will replace it with the,
which I just download it and
yeah. So no, let
me, yeah, probably I will make it a little bit larger.
No, 15.
Yeah. That's ups and this one.
Yeah. Like that. And now,
so I'll click on this thing now and expert PNG.
Yeah. And then now I will put it back to you and was it
118? So next time when I think here it's
100 8179.
So next time if the title is long,
um, then yeah, it'll be shorter in the future.
Like is it's properly centered. Yeah.
I think now it is properly set, but it must be excreted.
Um, so I won't look to hundreds of 15 year expertise
and then to make sure that the next time when you have an event
title, that is the one, we have an event title that is a longer,
it's not too big. Okay.
So this is the picture and that
we validate that who will applaud to you?
Um, yeah, because it was a podcast event.
And then if it was ever been there in Danville,
would you use this one? Okay.
So now let me update this one and
click save.
Yeah. So this is how you update Figma,
uh, w this is how you update cover with using a template from Figma.
So in the future, I want to generate this automatically,
but, uh, it will probably take me some time to do is to automate
this. Um, yeah. So for now we can just replace it with Figma.
So we'll send you this link and next time you can
just use these things to oh yeah.
For the covers.